24 WORDTAG I-ORG EU
19463 WORDTAG O _RARE_
84 WORDTAG I-MISC German
30 WORDTAG O call
3382 WORDTAG O to
5 WORDTAG O boycott
78 WORDTAG I-MISC British
7362 WORDTAG O .
31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
5640 WORDTAG I-PER _RARE_
16 WORDTAG I-LOC BRUSSELS
125 WORDTAG O 1996-08-22
1093 WORDTAG O The
31 WORDTAG I-ORG European
45 WORDTAG I-ORG Commission
1846 WORDTAG O said
2036 WORDTAG O on
285 WORDTAG O Thursday
553 WORDTAG O it
840 WORDTAG O with
5 WORDTAG O advice
9 WORDTAG O consumers
53 WORDTAG O until
6 WORDTAG O scientists
11 WORDTAG O determine
45 WORDTAG O whether
13 WORDTAG O mad
12 WORDTAG O cow
35 WORDTAG O disease
71 WORDTAG O can
525 WORDTAG O be
12 WORDTAG O sheep
142 WORDTAG I-LOC Germany
1496 WORDTAG O 's
7 WORDTAG O representative
7221 WORDTAG O the
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
8 WORDTAG O veterinary
22 WORDTAG O committee
255 WORDTAG O Wednesday
78 WORDTAG O should
26 WORDTAG O buy
757 WORDTAG O from
42 WORDTAG O countries
132 WORDTAG O other
144 WORDTAG O than
133 WORDTAG I-LOC Britain
9 WORDTAG O scientific
1095 WORDTAG O was
2178 WORDTAG O "
137 WORDTAG O We
106 WORDTAG O do
97 WORDTAG O n't
61 WORDTAG O support
92 WORDTAG O any
40 WORDTAG O such
114 WORDTAG O because
163 WORDTAG O we
28 WORDTAG O see
6 WORDTAG O grounds
1406 WORDTAG O for
7275 WORDTAG O ,
50 WORDTAG O chief
106 WORDTAG O spokesman
17 WORDTAG I-PER van
9 WORDTAG I-PER der
199 WORDTAG O told
2994 WORDTAG O a
85 WORDTAG O news
6 WORDTAG O briefing
209 WORDTAG O He
32 WORDTAG O further
10 WORDTAG O study
8 WORDTAG O required
2789 WORDTAG O and
98 WORDTAG O if
62 WORDTAG O found
767 WORDTAG O that
29 WORDTAG O action
24 WORDTAG O needed
41 WORDTAG O taken
716 WORDTAG O by
10 WORDTAG O proposal
282 WORDTAG O last
89 WORDTAG O month
7 WORDTAG O Commissioner
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fischler
36 WORDTAG O ban
5 WORDTAG O spinal
29 WORDTAG O human
8 WORDTAG O animal
21 WORDTAG O food
6 WORDTAG O chains
6 WORDTAG O highly
7 WORDTAG O specific
18 WORDTAG O move
25 WORDTAG O health
15 WORDTAG O proposed
1106 WORDTAG I-MISC _RARE_
16 WORDTAG O measures
471 WORDTAG O after
32 WORDTAG O reports
122 WORDTAG I-LOC France
159 WORDTAG O under
25 WORDTAG O conditions
143 WORDTAG O could
29 WORDTAG O contract
2846 WORDTAG O (
11 WORDTAG I-MISC BSE
2846 WORDTAG O )
356 WORDTAG O --
155 WORDTAG O But
53 WORDTAG O agreed
7 WORDTAG O review
538 WORDTAG O his
9 WORDTAG O standing
124 WORDTAG O officials
12 WORDTAG O questioned
602 WORDTAG O as
122 WORDTAG O there
125 WORDTAG O only
6 WORDTAG O slight
19 WORDTAG O risk
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Spanish
121 WORDTAG O Minister
26 WORDTAG I-PER de
561 WORDTAG O had
83 WORDTAG O earlier
38 WORDTAG O accused
930 WORDTAG O at
507 WORDTAG O an
17 WORDTAG O farm
14 WORDTAG O ministers
131 WORDTAG O '
86 WORDTAG O meeting
3617 WORDTAG O of
105 WORDTAG O through
13 WORDTAG O dangerous
5 WORDTAG O Only
7 WORDTAG O backed
346 WORDTAG O are
74 WORDTAG O due
56 WORDTAG O issue
75 WORDTAG O early
110 WORDTAG O next
57 WORDTAG O make
26 WORDTAG O senior
501 WORDTAG O have
35 WORDTAG O long
368 WORDTAG O been
31 WORDTAG O known
23 WORDTAG O similar
330 WORDTAG O which
689 WORDTAG O is
28 WORDTAG O believed
12 WORDTAG O cattle
18 WORDTAG O feed
5 WORDTAG O containing
7 WORDTAG O waste
19 WORDTAG O farmers
24 WORDTAG O denied
10 WORDTAG O danger
346 WORDTAG O their
389 WORDTAG O but
11 WORDTAG O expressed
17 WORDTAG O concern
258 WORDTAG O government
15 WORDTAG O avoid
36 WORDTAG O might
34 WORDTAG O across
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Europe
12 WORDTAG O What
8 WORDTAG O extremely
28 WORDTAG O how
52 WORDTAG O going
80 WORDTAG O take
75 WORDTAG O lead
3748 WORDTAG I-ORG _RARE_
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
27 WORDTAG O chairman
50 WORDTAG I-PER John
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lloyd
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jones
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bonn
557 WORDTAG O has
37 WORDTAG O led
15 WORDTAG O efforts
33 WORDTAG O public
15 WORDTAG O consumer
10 WORDTAG O confidence
3390 WORDTAG O in
36 WORDTAG O March
54 WORDTAG O report
7 WORDTAG O illness
8 WORDTAG O eating
10 WORDTAG O beef
5 WORDTAG O imported
293 WORDTAG O year
27 WORDTAG O nearly
84 WORDTAG O half
38 WORDTAG O total
13 WORDTAG O imports
207 WORDTAG O It
31 WORDTAG O brought
82 WORDTAG O tonnes
157 WORDTAG O some
197 WORDTAG O 10
303 WORDTAG O percent
20 WORDTAG O overall
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hendrix
11 WORDTAG O draft
14 WORDTAG O almost
362 WORDTAG O $
93 WORDTAG I-LOC LONDON
198 WORDTAG O A
8 WORDTAG O rare
309 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S.
28 WORDTAG O sold
14 WORDTAG O auction
53 WORDTAG O late
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Florida
7 WORDTAG O restaurant
18 WORDTAG O paid
23 WORDTAG O pounds
5 WORDTAG O piece
61 WORDTAG I-LOC London
10 WORDTAG O hotel
84 WORDTAG O At
74 WORDTAG O end
20 WORDTAG O January
42 WORDTAG I-MISC English
55 WORDTAG O city
1814 WORDTAG I-LOC _RARE_
582 WORDTAG O he
10 WORDTAG O threw
5 WORDTAG O sheet
24 WORDTAG O paper
160 WORDTAG O into
5 WORDTAG O audience
100 WORDTAG O where
214 WORDTAG O also
14 WORDTAG O snapped
314 WORDTAG O up
55 WORDTAG O 16
7 WORDTAG O items
531 WORDTAG O were
58 WORDTAG O put
109 WORDTAG O former
439 WORDTAG O who
8 WORDTAG O lived
111 WORDTAG O him
86 WORDTAG O They
20 WORDTAG O included
21 WORDTAG O black
11 WORDTAG O mother
6 WORDTAG O box
31 WORDTAG O used
7 WORDTAG O store
21 WORDTAG O drugs
52 WORDTAG I-MISC Australian
19 WORDTAG O bought
37 WORDTAG O died
8 WORDTAG O aged
37 WORDTAG O 27
91 WORDTAG I-LOC China
66 WORDTAG O says
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Taiwan
6 WORDTAG O atmosphere
83 WORDTAG O talks
9 WORDTAG I-LOC BEIJING
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Taipei
68 WORDTAG O visit
39 WORDTAG I-LOC Ukraine
109 WORDTAG O President
284 WORDTAG O this
147 WORDTAG O week
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Beijing
45 WORDTAG O hours
25 WORDTAG I-MISC Chinese
127 WORDTAG O state
16 WORDTAG O media
144 WORDTAG O time
36 WORDTAG O right
71 WORDTAG O political
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Foreign
29 WORDTAG I-ORG Ministry
79 WORDTAG I-ORG Reuters
687 WORDTAG O :
10 WORDTAG O necessary
31 WORDTAG O opening
46 WORDTAG O authorities
15 WORDTAG O State
49 WORDTAG O quoted
52 WORDTAG O top
5 WORDTAG O negotiator
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tang
5 WORDTAG O telling
9 WORDTAG O visiting
124 WORDTAG O group
8 WORDTAG O rivals
37 WORDTAG O hold
8 WORDTAG O Now
349 WORDTAG O two
19 WORDTAG O sides
44 WORDTAG O ...
7 WORDTAG O overseas
5 WORDTAG O edition
5 WORDTAG I-ORG People
34 WORDTAG I-ORG 's
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Daily
74 WORDTAG O saying
72 WORDTAG O foreign
37 WORDTAG O ministry
13 WORDTAG O interview
10 WORDTAG O read
8 WORDTAG O comments
56 WORDTAG O gave
164 WORDTAG O no
30 WORDTAG O details
10 WORDTAG O why
11 WORDTAG O considered
6 WORDTAG O renegade
22 WORDTAG O province
11 WORDTAG O opposed
128 WORDTAG O all
6 WORDTAG O gain
71 WORDTAG O international
18 WORDTAG O rival
25 WORDTAG O island
15 WORDTAG O towards
24 WORDTAG O goal
80 WORDTAG O held
83 WORDTAG O set
109 WORDTAG O official
52 WORDTAG O agency
23 WORDTAG O executive
10 WORDTAG O vice
24 WORDTAG I-ORG Association
14 WORDTAG I-ORG for
10 WORDTAG I-ORG the
99 WORDTAG O July
19 WORDTAG O car
9 WORDTAG O registrations
56 WORDTAG O pct
13 WORDTAG O yr
220 WORDTAG O /
5 WORDTAG I-LOC FRANKFURT
7 WORDTAG O motor
9 WORDTAG O vehicles
35 WORDTAG O period
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Federal
48 WORDTAG O office
199 WORDTAG O new
10 WORDTAG O cars
9 WORDTAG O registered
121 WORDTAG O 1996
16 WORDTAG O passenger
29 WORDTAG O figures
22 WORDTAG O increase
6 WORDTAG O decline
63 WORDTAG O 1995
11 WORDTAG O registration
33 WORDTAG O rose
39 WORDTAG O growth
5 WORDTAG O partly
19 WORDTAG O increased
75 WORDTAG O number
13 WORDTAG O buying
14 WORDTAG O abroad
92 WORDTAG O while
6 WORDTAG O manufacturers
20 WORDTAG O domestic
49 WORDTAG O demand
9 WORDTAG O weak
21 WORDTAG O federal
11 WORDTAG O posted
17 WORDTAG O gains
13 WORDTAG O numbers
14 WORDTAG I-ORG AG
163 WORDTAG O won
15 WORDTAG O slightly
154 WORDTAG O more
42 WORDTAG O quarter
9 WORDTAG O together
5 WORDTAG I-ORG General
45 WORDTAG O came
216 WORDTAG O second
50 WORDTAG O place
15 WORDTAG O figure
7 WORDTAG O Third
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Ford
186 WORDTAG O or
5 WORDTAG O fewer
23 WORDTAG O compared
46 WORDTAG O fell
27 WORDTAG O TO
7 WORDTAG O PM
25 WORDTAG O FOR
10 WORDTAG I-LOC ATHENS
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Greek
76 WORDTAG O party
5 WORDTAG O bureau
5 WORDTAG O green
15 WORDTAG O light
56 WORDTAG O Prime
9 WORDTAG I-PER Costas
8 WORDTAG I-PER Simitis
8 WORDTAG O snap
77 WORDTAG O elections
306 WORDTAG O its
44 WORDTAG O general
18 WORDTAG O secretary
45 WORDTAG O reporters
14 WORDTAG O announcement
17 WORDTAG O cabinet
46 WORDTAG O later
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitris
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kontogiannis
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Athens
70 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsroom
7 WORDTAG O +301
7 WORDTAG O 3311812-4
19 WORDTAG O sets
21 WORDTAG I-MISC C$
71 WORDTAG O 100
280 WORDTAG O million
24 WORDTAG O bond
47 WORDTAG O following
45 WORDTAG O announced
35 WORDTAG O manager
6 WORDTAG O PRICE
6 WORDTAG O PAY
6 WORDTAG O DATE
5 WORDTAG O BP
11 WORDTAG O =
7 WORDTAG I-ORG S&P
10 WORDTAG I-LOC UK
16 WORDTAG I-MISC GERMAN
6 WORDTAG O 7.0
37 WORDTAG O PCT
7 WORDTAG O 2001
7 WORDTAG O NOTES
24 WORDTAG I-ORG London
14 WORDTAG O +44
21 WORDTAG O 171
20 WORDTAG O 542
24 WORDTAG O 300
5 WORDTAG O 1999
20 WORDTAG I-ORG International
1243 WORDTAG O -
8 WORDTAG O LAST
55 WORDTAG O FIRST
972 WORDTAG O 2
19 WORDTAG I-MISC ENGLISH
392 WORDTAG O 5
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Syria
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Service
34 WORDTAG O Aug
10 WORDTAG O waiting
63 WORDTAG O 24
63 WORDTAG I-LOC Israel
8 WORDTAG O plays
117 WORDTAG O down
10 WORDTAG O fears
62 WORDTAG O war
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JERUSALEM
84 WORDTAG O peace
40 WORDTAG O current
136 WORDTAG O between
18 WORDTAG O appeared
9 WORDTAG O storm
12 WORDTAG O ambassador
27 WORDTAG I-LOC Washington
8 WORDTAG O conducted
21 WORDTAG O negotiations
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Radio
17 WORDTAG O looked
42 WORDTAG O like
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Damascus
19 WORDTAG O wanted
23 WORDTAG O talk
12 WORDTAG O rather
15 WORDTAG O fight
6 WORDTAG O appears
35 WORDTAG O me
84 WORDTAG O still
306 WORDTAG O they
8 WORDTAG O definitely
5 WORDTAG O tense
7 WORDTAG O assessment
25 WORDTAG O here
31 WORDTAG O term
416 WORDTAG O will
5 WORDTAG O replaced
49 WORDTAG I-MISC Israeli
8 WORDTAG O envoy
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Egypt
9 WORDTAG O right-wing
6 WORDTAG O politician
36 WORDTAG O sent
26 WORDTAG O message
7 WORDTAG O via
10 WORDTAG O committed
21 WORDTAG O open
37 WORDTAG O without
59 WORDTAG O what
60 WORDTAG O called
38 WORDTAG O campaign
236 WORDTAG O against
47 WORDTAG O television
91 WORDTAG O reported
16 WORDTAG O recently
43 WORDTAG O test
13 WORDTAG O fired
19 WORDTAG O arms
9 WORDTAG O ready
9 WORDTAG O enter
37 WORDTAG O Foreign
50 WORDTAG I-PER David
12 WORDTAG I-PER Levy
133 WORDTAG O since
10 WORDTAG I-PER Benjamin
25 WORDTAG I-PER Netanyahu
76 WORDTAG O took
86 WORDTAG O June
6 WORDTAG O retain
11 WORDTAG B-LOC _RARE_
9 WORDTAG O captured
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Middle
27 WORDTAG I-LOC East
271 WORDTAG O over
23 WORDTAG O 1991
30 WORDTAG O despite
38 WORDTAG O previous
20 WORDTAG O February
27 WORDTAG O coming
291 WORDTAG O out
19 WORDTAG O bad
536 WORDTAG O not
55 WORDTAG O good
25 WORDTAG O full
32 WORDTAG O must
63 WORDTAG O very
49 WORDTAG O those
20 WORDTAG O become
5 WORDTAG O prisoners
20 WORDTAG O expect
31 WORDTAG O face
8 WORDTAG O answer
67 WORDTAG O our
51 WORDTAG O want
5 WORDTAG I-PER God
28 WORDTAG O No
260 WORDTAG O one
6 WORDTAG O signal
24 WORDTAG O source
7 WORDTAG O confirm
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cairo
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
57 WORDTAG I-LOC States
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Moscow
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Polish
18 WORDTAG O diplomat
5 WORDTAG O nurses
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Libya
32 WORDTAG O trying
44 WORDTAG O return
108 WORDTAG O home
37 WORDTAG O working
45 WORDTAG I-MISC African
68 WORDTAG O country
43 WORDTAG O This
7 WORDTAG O true
5 WORDTAG O Up
27 WORDTAG O today
25 WORDTAG O kept
169 WORDTAG O her
31 WORDTAG O received
35 WORDTAG O embassy
19 WORDTAG O charge
17 WORDTAG O telephone
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Poland
7 WORDTAG O labour
330 WORDTAG O would
11 WORDTAG O send
89 WORDTAG O team
6 WORDTAG O probe
9 WORDTAG O prompted
180 WORDTAG O about
45 WORDTAG O work
30 WORDTAG O estimated
13 WORDTAG O 800
33 WORDTAG O Two
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Iranian
55 WORDTAG O opposition
54 WORDTAG O leaders
60 WORDTAG O meet
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Baghdad
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hassan
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BAGHDAD
29 WORDTAG O An
6 WORDTAG O exile
25 WORDTAG O based
68 WORDTAG I-LOC Iraq
6 WORDTAG O vowed
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Iran
33 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurdish
54 WORDTAG O rebels
7 WORDTAG O attacked
45 WORDTAG O troops
12 WORDTAG O inside
105 WORDTAG O statement
63 WORDTAG O leader
26 WORDTAG O met
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdistan
19 WORDTAG I-ORG Democratic
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Party
104 WORDTAG I-ORG of
25 WORDTAG O rebel
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurds
25 WORDTAG O continue
6 WORDTAG O stand
40 WORDTAG O side
20 WORDTAG O movement
29 WORDTAG O level
16 WORDTAG O cooperation
5 WORDTAG O heavily
6 WORDTAG O targets
53 WORDTAG O northern
6 WORDTAG O pursuit
31 WORDTAG O guerrillas
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqi
25 WORDTAG O areas
25 WORDTAG O outside
37 WORDTAG O control
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Patriotic
25 WORDTAG I-ORG PUK
17 WORDTAG I-ORG KDP
41 WORDTAG O main
14 WORDTAG O factions
46 WORDTAG O forces
8 WORDTAG O ousted
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Kuwait
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
15 WORDTAG I-MISC War
25 WORDTAG O parties
23 WORDTAG O broke
53 WORDTAG O weekend
70 WORDTAG O most
15 WORDTAG O serious
41 WORDTAG O fighting
36 WORDTAG O ceasefire
5 WORDTAG O shelling
16 WORDTAG O positions
38 WORDTAG O region
53 WORDTAG O near
27 WORDTAG O border
74 WORDTAG O days
82 WORDTAG O killed
15 WORDTAG O wounded
38 WORDTAG O attack
11 WORDTAG O Both
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Turkey
21 WORDTAG O air
23 WORDTAG O land
5 WORDTAG O strikes
38 WORDTAG O own
6 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.-led
28 WORDTAG O force
46 WORDTAG O southern
32 WORDTAG O possible
25 WORDTAG O attacks
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Saudi
5 WORDTAG O riyal
31 WORDTAG O rates
20 WORDTAG O steady
20 WORDTAG O quiet
20 WORDTAG O summer
57 WORDTAG O trade
17 WORDTAG O spot
53 WORDTAG O dollar
7 WORDTAG O deposit
9 WORDTAG O mainly
21 WORDTAG O dealers
6 WORDTAG O kingdom
56 WORDTAG O There
8 WORDTAG O changes
143 WORDTAG O market
18 WORDTAG O dealer
201 WORDTAG O three
56 WORDTAG O months
84 WORDTAG O 1/2
117 WORDTAG O six
5 WORDTAG O 5/8
12 WORDTAG O funds
47 WORDTAG I-PER Arafat
24 WORDTAG O flight
46 WORDTAG I-LOC West
32 WORDTAG I-LOC Bank
39 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinian
12 WORDTAG I-PER Yasser
9 WORDTAG O permission
10 WORDTAG O fly
18 WORDTAG O territory
14 WORDTAG O ending
10 WORDTAG O brief
12 WORDTAG O crisis
25 WORDTAG O problem
95 WORDTAG O president
17 WORDTAG O aircraft
5 WORDTAG O pass
106 WORDTAG O expected
15 WORDTAG O travel
149 WORDTAG O before
192 WORDTAG O Monday
27 WORDTAG O scheduled
35 WORDTAG O prime
55 WORDTAG O minister
6 WORDTAG I-PER Shimon
15 WORDTAG I-PER Peres
59 WORDTAG O town
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Ramallah
5 WORDTAG O venue
13 WORDTAG O changed
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Gaza
18 WORDTAG O stop
8 WORDTAG O keeping
10 WORDTAG O cancelled
8 WORDTAG I-ORG PLO
5 WORDTAG O civilian
6 WORDTAG O affairs
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bridge
5 WORDTAG O crossing
24 WORDTAG I-LOC Jordan
23 WORDTAG O decided
7 WORDTAG O flying
10 WORDTAG O lifted
8 WORDTAG O schedule
32 WORDTAG O free
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinians
5 WORDTAG O barred
34 WORDTAG O planned
7 WORDTAG O helicopter
17 WORDTAG O attempt
13 WORDTAG O defeated
54 WORDTAG O May
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Afghan
5 WORDTAG I-LOC UAE
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
9 WORDTAG O guards
5 WORDTAG I-LOC DUBAI
11 WORDTAG O Three
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Arab
95 WORDTAG I-MISC Russian
6 WORDTAG O hostages
5 WORDTAG O escaped
8 WORDTAG O militia
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Afghanistan
42 WORDTAG O few
11 WORDTAG O Our
9 WORDTAG O Their
102 WORDTAG O them
10 WORDTAG O documents
85 WORDTAG O added
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamic
68 WORDTAG O seven
181 WORDTAG O Friday
18 WORDTAG O board
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kandahar
18 WORDTAG O hand
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Red
7 WORDTAG O possibly
212 WORDTAG O Tuesday
22 WORDTAG O When
42 WORDTAG O asked
98 WORDTAG O back
75 WORDTAG O capital
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul
30 WORDTAG O That
10 WORDTAG O headquarters
7 WORDTAG O controlled
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rabbani
46 WORDTAG O men
15 WORDTAG O currently
106 WORDTAG O did
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Russians
23 WORDTAG O firm
9 WORDTAG O republic
11 WORDTAG O hostage
37 WORDTAG B-MISC _RARE_
31 WORDTAG O forced
9 WORDTAG O cargo
37 WORDTAG O plane
97 WORDTAG O August
9 WORDTAG O shipment
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Albania
12 WORDTAG O evidence
59 WORDTAG O military
14 WORDTAG O crew
16 WORDTAG O diplomatic
7 WORDTAG O attempts
36 WORDTAG O failed
23 WORDTAG O armed
18 WORDTAG O doing
7 WORDTAG O regular
66 WORDTAG O left
155 WORDTAG O Sunday
10 WORDTAG I-PER Saddam
5 WORDTAG O meets
88 WORDTAG I-LOC Russia
6 WORDTAG I-PER Zhirinovsky
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hussein
6 WORDTAG I-PER Vladimir
8 WORDTAG O maintain
13 WORDTAG O newspapers
80 WORDTAG O during
44 WORDTAG O parliament
8 WORDTAG O calling
12 WORDTAG O immediate
7 WORDTAG O lifting
7 WORDTAG O embargo
13 WORDTAG O imposed
20 WORDTAG O 1990
33 WORDTAG O press
36 WORDTAG O help
40 WORDTAG I-ORG U.N.
13 WORDTAG O sanctions
17 WORDTAG O blamed
8 WORDTAG O establishment
10 WORDTAG O ties
50 WORDTAG O economic
12 WORDTAG O resume
17 WORDTAG O visited
17 WORDTAG O twice
15 WORDTAG O Last
34 WORDTAG O October
15 WORDTAG O invited
11 WORDTAG O attend
5 WORDTAG O referendum
8 WORDTAG O presidency
6 WORDTAG O extended
134 WORDTAG O years
24 WORDTAG O PRESS
24 WORDTAG O DIGEST
71 WORDTAG O 22
22 WORDTAG O These
41 WORDTAG O leading
34 WORDTAG O stories
19 WORDTAG O verified
37 WORDTAG O these
36 WORDTAG O does
16 WORDTAG O vouch
16 WORDTAG O accuracy
7 WORDTAG O democratic
24 WORDTAG I-MISC Turkish
78 WORDTAG O part
7 WORDTAG O fair
19 WORDTAG O November
104 WORDTAG O 12
6 WORDTAG O rice
8 WORDTAG O arrives
17 WORDTAG O port
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Gulf
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Lebanon
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Beirut
7 WORDTAG O threats
10 WORDTAG O serve
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
9 WORDTAG O Speaker
9 WORDTAG O preparing
17 WORDTAG O battle
10 WORDTAG O ..
9 WORDTAG O prepared
30 WORDTAG O law
5 WORDTAG O violation
6 WORDTAG O incidents
7 WORDTAG O occurred
5 WORDTAG O Financial
85 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistan
24 WORDTAG O step
45 WORDTAG O election
15 WORDTAG O list
11 WORDTAG O violations
14 WORDTAG O live
10 WORDTAG O calls
18 WORDTAG O range
11 WORDTAG O mixed
29 WORDTAG I-LOC CHICAGO
15 WORDTAG O futures
7 WORDTAG O cent
44 WORDTAG O higher
59 WORDTAG O lower
6 WORDTAG O livestock
28 WORDTAG O analysts
23 WORDTAG O continued
33 WORDTAG O strong
37 WORDTAG O cash
32 WORDTAG O markets
8 WORDTAG O prompt
7 WORDTAG O bullish
13 WORDTAG O However
30 WORDTAG O likely
59 WORDTAG O prices
18 WORDTAG O evening
46 WORDTAG O ahead
9 WORDTAG O Cash
52 WORDTAG O record
7 WORDTAG O amount
19 WORDTAG O traded
18 WORDTAG O debt
47 WORDTAG O hit
73 WORDTAG O results
61 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc
7 WORDTAG O mean
45 WORDTAG O loss
5 WORDTAG O 1.2
14 WORDTAG O fiscal
42 WORDTAG O 1997
388 WORDTAG O first
127 WORDTAG O company
43 WORDTAG O began
1418 WORDTAG O 1
86 WORDTAG O 30
17 WORDTAG O par
20 WORDTAG O value
9 WORDTAG O outstanding
9 WORDTAG I-PER Philip
28 WORDTAG O financial
18 WORDTAG O officer
18 WORDTAG O child
10 WORDTAG O care
19 WORDTAG O offered
9 WORDTAG O opportunity
9 WORDTAG O reduce
35 WORDTAG O average
32 WORDTAG O interest
20 WORDTAG O costs
11 WORDTAG O improve
37 WORDTAG O future
28 WORDTAG O earnings
5 WORDTAG O RESEARCH
5 WORDTAG O ALERT
15 WORDTAG O starts
19 WORDTAG O analyst
35 WORDTAG O started
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southern
49 WORDTAG I-ORG New
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp
6 WORDTAG O outperform
9 WORDTAG O rating
53 WORDTAG O price
13 WORDTAG O target
25 WORDTAG O 45
6 WORDTAG O estimate
71 WORDTAG O per
43 WORDTAG O share
30 WORDTAG O immediately
37 WORDTAG O available
44 WORDTAG O closed
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Data
5 WORDTAG O Q2
53 WORDTAG O net
9 WORDTAG O rises
12 WORDTAG O Summary
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Financial
171 WORDTAG O In
8 WORDTAG O Thousands
6 WORDTAG O except
14 WORDTAG O data
8 WORDTAG O Six
14 WORDTAG O Jul
45 WORDTAG O 31
6 WORDTAG O Income
5 WORDTAG O Data
26 WORDTAG O Total
11 WORDTAG O Revenue
6 WORDTAG O Operating
5 WORDTAG O 599
24 WORDTAG O Net
7 WORDTAG O Jan
5 WORDTAG O 93
36 WORDTAG O give
8 WORDTAG O backing
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Le
30 WORDTAG I-LOC PARIS
12 WORDTAG O afternoon
29 WORDTAG O daily
6 WORDTAG O dated
44 WORDTAG O 23
14 WORDTAG O seeking
10 WORDTAG O residence
40 WORDTAG O rights
60 WORDTAG O say
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alain
8 WORDTAG I-PER Juppe
8 WORDTAG O proposals
38 WORDTAG O strike
106 WORDTAG O day
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Paris
17 WORDTAG O church
14 WORDTAG O rally
8 WORDTAG O 8,000
5 WORDTAG O nationalist
14 WORDTAG O truce
44 WORDTAG O night
67 WORDTAG I-MISC French
137 WORDTAG O points
31 WORDTAG O industry
19 WORDTAG O competition
9 WORDTAG O failure
26 WORDTAG O keep
6 WORDTAG O trends
14 WORDTAG O Secretary
20 WORDTAG O union
9 WORDTAG O social
14 WORDTAG O unrest
45 WORDTAG O weeks
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Paris
24 WORDTAG O 42
114 WORDTAG O 21
26 WORDTAG O 53
18 WORDTAG O 81
8 WORDTAG O lift
42 WORDTAG O oil
17 WORDTAG O output
16 WORDTAG O water
5 WORDTAG O wells
120 WORDTAG O off
6 WORDTAG O reopened
6 WORDTAG O operator
8 WORDTAG O 30,000
10 WORDTAG O barrels
6 WORDTAG O bpd
24 WORDTAG O according
22 WORDTAG O problems
61 WORDTAG O newsroom
69 WORDTAG O 50
17 WORDTAG O 41
33 WORDTAG O April
11 WORDTAG O surplus
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
91 WORDTAG O billion
9 WORDTAG O markka
6 WORDTAG I-LOC HELSINKI
42 WORDTAG I-LOC Finland
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Board
28 WORDTAG O exports
5 WORDTAG O Trade
9 WORDTAG O balance
32 WORDTAG O 96
9 WORDTAG O 95
5 WORDTAG O import
13 WORDTAG O revised
14 WORDTAG O export
43 WORDTAG I-ORG Bank
5 WORDTAG O 3.2
8 WORDTAG O monthly
56 WORDTAG O behind
12 WORDTAG O customs
220 WORDTAG O when
15 WORDTAG O joined
51 WORDTAG O start
945 WORDTAG O 0
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Dutch
18 WORDTAG O sale
26 WORDTAG I-LOC AMSTERDAM
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Finance
13 WORDTAG O raised
50 WORDTAG O sales
99 WORDTAG O September
86 WORDTAG O being
49 WORDTAG I-MISC GMT
21 WORDTAG O guilders
61 WORDTAG O close
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Amsterdam
13 WORDTAG O +31
100 WORDTAG O 20
14 WORDTAG O 504
10 WORDTAG O 5000
20 WORDTAG I-LOC BONN
6 WORDTAG O animals
8 WORDTAG O cleared
14 WORDTAG O done
12 WORDTAG O quickly
307 WORDTAG O I
6 WORDTAG O concrete
24 WORDTAG O too
48 WORDTAG O many
7 WORDTAG O holes
26 WORDTAG O know
5 WORDTAG O filled
7 WORDTAG O ensure
11 WORDTAG O protection
6 WORDTAG O dealing
6 WORDTAG O erupted
29 WORDTAG O use
11 WORDTAG O suspect
5 WORDTAG O experts
34 WORDTAG O members
33 WORDTAG O given
20 WORDTAG O question
25 WORDTAG O After
16 WORDTAG O admitted
8 WORDTAG O link
6 WORDTAG O fatal
6 WORDTAG O equivalent
6 WORDTAG O worldwide
11 WORDTAG O takes
9 WORDTAG O GOLF
14 WORDTAG O SCORES
131 WORDTAG O AT
6 WORDTAG I-MISC WORLD
8 WORDTAG I-MISC OF
7 WORDTAG I-LOC AKRON
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Ohio
13 WORDTAG O Scores
48 WORDTAG I-MISC World
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Series
20 WORDTAG I-MISC of
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Golf
122 WORDTAG O round
105 WORDTAG O 70
25 WORDTAG O course
52 WORDTAG O players
28 WORDTAG O unless
18 WORDTAG O stated
66 WORDTAG O 66
51 WORDTAG I-PER Paul
7 WORDTAG I-PER Billy
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mayfair
87 WORDTAG I-LOC Japan
75 WORDTAG O 68
23 WORDTAG I-PER Steve
91 WORDTAG O 69
6 WORDTAG I-PER Justin
58 WORDTAG I-PER Mark
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tim
12 WORDTAG I-PER Davis
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anders
81 WORDTAG I-LOC Sweden
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nick
6 WORDTAG I-PER Phil
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mickelson
14 WORDTAG I-PER Greg
10 WORDTAG I-PER Norman
130 WORDTAG I-LOC Australia
85 WORDTAG O 71
5 WORDTAG I-PER Els
76 WORDTAG I-LOC South
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Africa
19 WORDTAG I-PER Scott
58 WORDTAG O 72
12 WORDTAG I-PER Rose
9 WORDTAG I-PER Fred
8 WORDTAG I-PER Sven
23 WORDTAG I-PER Alexander
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tom
52 WORDTAG O 73
6 WORDTAG I-PER Brad
14 WORDTAG I-PER Craig
16 WORDTAG I-PER Stewart
53 WORDTAG O 74
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costantino
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rocca
98 WORDTAG I-LOC Italy
55 WORDTAG O 75
21 WORDTAG I-PER Jim
28 WORDTAG O 76
24 WORDTAG O 77
17 WORDTAG I-PER Wayne
12 WORDTAG O 79
132 WORDTAG O SOCCER
17 WORDTAG O BEAT
25 WORDTAG O 2-1
14 WORDTAG I-ORG F.C.
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloria
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bistrita
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Romania
335 WORDTAG O beat
28 WORDTAG O halftime
25 WORDTAG O 1-1
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malta
94 WORDTAG I-MISC Cup
120 WORDTAG O match
24 WORDTAG O leg
16 WORDTAG O preliminary
23 WORDTAG O Scorers
9 WORDTAG I-ORG La
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbert
8 WORDTAG O 24th
52 WORDTAG O Attendance
9 WORDTAG O 4-2
25 WORDTAG O aggregate
6 WORDTAG O qualified
8 WORDTAG O RACING
67 WORDTAG I-LOC YORK
124 WORDTAG I-LOC England
5 WORDTAG O Sir
17 WORDTAG O landed
70 WORDTAG O victory
68 WORDTAG O 25
22 WORDTAG O chance
14 WORDTAG O veteran
14 WORDTAG I-PER George
33 WORDTAG O short
42 WORDTAG O head
5 WORDTAG O deny
5 WORDTAG O trained
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henry
19 WORDTAG I-PER Chris
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Prix
12 WORDTAG I-MISC '
24 WORDTAG O winner
16 WORDTAG O finished
107 WORDTAG O third
42 WORDTAG O away
23 WORDTAG O 7-4
36 WORDTAG O fourth
46 WORDTAG O may
81 WORDTAG O now
14 WORDTAG O aimed
81 WORDTAG O season
10 WORDTAG O sprint
57 WORDTAG O race
5 WORDTAG O reluctant
62 WORDTAG O go
29 WORDTAG O result
23 WORDTAG O never
72 WORDTAG O so
17 WORDTAG O thought
29 WORDTAG O better
8 WORDTAG O wait
12 WORDTAG O bit
10 WORDTAG O longer
15 WORDTAG O am
12 WORDTAG O daughter
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jack
9 WORDTAG O gone
8 WORDTAG O search
9 WORDTAG O success
78 WORDTAG O around
7 WORDTAG O disappointed
16 WORDTAG O feel
70 WORDTAG O well
84 WORDTAG O metres
106 WORDTAG O just
99 WORDTAG O RESULTS
24 WORDTAG O Result
61 WORDTAG O run
112 WORDTAG O five
47 WORDTAG O km
94 WORDTAG O 1.
95 WORDTAG O 2.
95 WORDTAG O 3.
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jason
7 WORDTAG I-PER Weaver
8 WORDTAG O Eight
10 WORDTAG O ran
15 WORDTAG O owned
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Park
7 WORDTAG O sterling
31 WORDTAG O TENNIS
5 WORDTAG I-MISC TOSHIBA
5 WORDTAG I-MISC CLASSIC
5 WORDTAG I-LOC CARLSBAD
16 WORDTAG I-LOC California
7 WORDTAG O 1996-08-21
85 WORDTAG O Results
5 WORDTAG O 450,000
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Toshiba
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Classic
34 WORDTAG O tennis
54 WORDTAG O tournament
25 WORDTAG O prefix
24 WORDTAG O denotes
28 WORDTAG O seeding
15 WORDTAG O Second
11 WORDTAG I-PER Arantxa
19 WORDTAG I-PER Sanchez
11 WORDTAG I-PER Vicario
110 WORDTAG I-LOC Spain
5 WORDTAG I-PER Naoko
17 WORDTAG O 1-6
117 WORDTAG O 6-4
117 WORDTAG O 6-3
581 WORDTAG O 4
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kimiko
7 WORDTAG I-PER Date
100 WORDTAG O 6-2
63 WORDTAG O 7-5
259 WORDTAG O 7
19 WORDTAG O 4-6
155 WORDTAG O 8
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nathalie
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tauziat
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wang
20 WORDTAG I-MISC CUP
95 WORDTAG I-LOC New
38 WORDTAG I-LOC York
55 WORDTAG I-PER Michael
16 WORDTAG I-PER Chang
7 WORDTAG I-PER Sergi
6 WORDTAG I-PER Bruguera
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joyce
930 WORDTAG O 3
22 WORDTAG O 3-6
47 WORDTAG I-PER Martin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damm
57 WORDTAG I-LOC Czech
62 WORDTAG I-LOC Republic
343 WORDTAG O 6
7 WORDTAG I-PER El
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Morocco
14 WORDTAG O 5-7
15 WORDTAG O 3-0
11 WORDTAG O retired
5 WORDTAG I-PER Karol
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kucera
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovakia
74 WORDTAG O 7-6
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kenny
11 WORDTAG O spoke
17 WORDTAG O leaving
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackburn
37 WORDTAG O club
22 WORDTAG O premier
65 WORDTAG O league
27 WORDTAG O title
5 WORDTAG O mutual
7 WORDTAG O confessed
50 WORDTAG O taking
85 WORDTAG O division
63 WORDTAG O local
58 WORDTAG O newspaper
28 WORDTAG O holiday
62 WORDTAG O same
12 WORDTAG O opinion
36 WORDTAG O little
32 WORDTAG O If
25 WORDTAG O opened
50 WORDTAG O my
7 WORDTAG O stayed
45 WORDTAG O way
9 WORDTAG O let
53 WORDTAG O get
16 WORDTAG O job
60 WORDTAG O then
40 WORDTAG O past
112 WORDTAG O 15
24 WORDTAG O director
5 WORDTAG O football
50 WORDTAG O CRICKET
6 WORDTAG I-MISC COUNTY
7 WORDTAG I-MISC CHAMPIONSHIP
5 WORDTAG O Close
65 WORDTAG O play
16 WORDTAG O scores
13 WORDTAG O four-day
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Championship
21 WORDTAG O cricket
91 WORDTAG O matches
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Durham
23 WORDTAG O 326
22 WORDTAG I-PER D.
15 WORDTAG I-PER S.
9 WORDTAG I-PER Campbell
52 WORDTAG O ;
23 WORDTAG I-PER G.
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Somerset
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
8 WORDTAG O 85
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Colchester
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloucestershire
8 WORDTAG O 280
17 WORDTAG I-PER J.
17 WORDTAG I-PER Russell
40 WORDTAG O 63
32 WORDTAG I-PER A.
23 WORDTAG O 52
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Essex
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cardiff
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Kent
7 WORDTAG I-PER Walker
34 WORDTAG O 59
89 WORDTAG O v
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Glamorgan
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Leicester
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicestershire
18 WORDTAG I-PER P.
6 WORDTAG O 108
64 WORDTAG O 67
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Sussex
20 WORDTAG I-PER N.
6 WORDTAG O 145
5 WORDTAG I-PER V.
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wells
19 WORDTAG O 51
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Northamptonshire
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Trent
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Nottinghamshire
5 WORDTAG O 107
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Surrey
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Warwickshire
6 WORDTAG I-PER Giles
19 WORDTAG O 57
6 WORDTAG I-PER W.
25 WORDTAG I-PER Khan
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Worcestershire
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Headingley
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yorkshire
16 WORDTAG I-PER C.
13 WORDTAG I-PER White
5 WORDTAG I-PER Moxon
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Lancashire
21 WORDTAG I-LOC ENGLAND
14 WORDTAG O V
20 WORDTAG I-LOC PAKISTAN
7 WORDTAG O FINAL
13 WORDTAG O TEST
8 WORDTAG O SCOREBOARD
8 WORDTAG O Scoreboard
71 WORDTAG O final
20 WORDTAG I-LOC The
19 WORDTAG I-LOC Oval
75 WORDTAG O innings
11 WORDTAG I-PER Atherton
74 WORDTAG O b
28 WORDTAG I-PER Waqar
28 WORDTAG I-PER Younis
28 WORDTAG I-PER Mushtaq
49 WORDTAG I-PER Ahmed
16 WORDTAG O 44
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hussain
40 WORDTAG O c
18 WORDTAG I-PER Saeed
17 WORDTAG I-PER Anwar
13 WORDTAG I-PER Thorpe
7 WORDTAG O lbw
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mohammad
37 WORDTAG I-PER Akram
33 WORDTAG O 54
12 WORDTAG I-PER Crawley
8 WORDTAG I-PER Knight
47 WORDTAG O 17
21 WORDTAG I-PER Lewis
34 WORDTAG I-PER Wasim
9 WORDTAG I-PER Salisbury
16 WORDTAG O Extras
36 WORDTAG O wickets
5 WORDTAG O 278
15 WORDTAG O Fall
15 WORDTAG O To
15 WORDTAG O bat
19 WORDTAG I-PER R.
28 WORDTAG I-PER Croft
17 WORDTAG I-PER Cork
26 WORDTAG I-PER Mullally
16 WORDTAG O Bowling
30 WORDTAG O date
19 WORDTAG I-PER Aamir
22 WORDTAG I-PER Sohail
15 WORDTAG I-PER Ijaz
12 WORDTAG I-PER Inzamam-ul-Haq
13 WORDTAG I-PER Salim
13 WORDTAG I-PER Malik
12 WORDTAG I-PER Asif
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mujtaba
13 WORDTAG I-PER Moin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Akam
48 WORDTAG O IN
5 WORDTAG I-MISC SCOTTISH
8 WORDTAG O SQUAD
13 WORDTAG O AFTER
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Everton
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ferguson
40 WORDTAG O scored
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Manchester
48 WORDTAG I-ORG United
13 WORDTAG O picked
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Scottish
30 WORDTAG O squad
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Rangers
23 WORDTAG O striker
51 WORDTAG O another
60 WORDTAG O man
17 WORDTAG O form
117 WORDTAG O four
29 WORDTAG O named
17 WORDTAG O qualifier
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Austria
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vienna
9 WORDTAG O served
18 WORDTAG O jail
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Scotland
5 WORDTAG O caps
19 WORDTAG O December
44 WORDTAG O 1994
14 WORDTAG I-PER Brown
19 WORDTAG O 've
24 WORDTAG O great
12 WORDTAG O scoring
15 WORDTAG O moment
9 WORDTAG O successful
14 WORDTAG O ON
48 WORDTAG O OF
9 WORDTAG O THIRD
8 WORDTAG O lunch
10 WORDTAG O WITH
13 WORDTAG I-LOC MANCHESTER
36 WORDTAG I-LOC Ireland
19 WORDTAG O midfielder
40 WORDTAG O signed
35 WORDTAG O champions
58 WORDTAG O deal
76 WORDTAG O game
22 WORDTAG I-PER Alex
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CANADIAN
26 WORDTAG I-MISC OPEN
13 WORDTAG I-LOC TORONTO
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Canadian
71 WORDTAG I-MISC Open
14 WORDTAG I-PER Daniel
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nestor
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Canada
34 WORDTAG I-PER Thomas
14 WORDTAG I-PER Muster
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mikael
9 WORDTAG I-PER Tillstrom
5 WORDTAG I-PER Goran
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ivanisevic
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Croatia
14 WORDTAG O 6-7
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ferreira
15 WORDTAG I-PER Marcelo
9 WORDTAG I-PER Rios
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Chile
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kenneth
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Denmark
7 WORDTAG I-PER MaliVai
12 WORDTAG I-PER Washington
21 WORDTAG I-PER Todd
9 WORDTAG O 7-3
17 WORDTAG I-PER Philippoussis
13 WORDTAG I-PER Marc
7 WORDTAG I-PER Rosset
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Switzerland
11 WORDTAG O 8-6
167 WORDTAG O 9
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cedric
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pioline
11 WORDTAG O 7-1
12 WORDTAG I-PER Patrick
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
120 WORDTAG O 11
7 WORDTAG I-PER Alberto
75 WORDTAG O 6-1
8 WORDTAG I-PER Petr
6 WORDTAG I-PER Korda
8 WORDTAG I-PER Francisco
5 WORDTAG I-PER Vacek
119 WORDTAG O 13
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stoltenberg
9 WORDTAG I-PER Woodbridge
10 WORDTAG I-PER O'Brien
7 WORDTAG I-PER Black
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Zimbabwe
11 WORDTAG O 7-2
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bohdan
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ulihrach
14 WORDTAG I-PER Andrea
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henman
5 WORDTAG O walkover
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
10 WORDTAG O provincial
11 WORDTAG O fast
7 WORDTAG O professional
8 WORDTAG I-MISC EUROPEAN
5 WORDTAG I-LOC TIRANA
55 WORDTAG I-MISC European
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Winners
14 WORDTAG O qualifying
75 WORDTAG O soccer
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tirana
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chemlon
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Humenne
29 WORDTAG O 0-0
67 WORDTAG O minute
8 WORDTAG O 54th
10 WORDTAG O 5,000
105 WORDTAG O win
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ruch
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chorzow
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Wales
46 WORDTAG O 1-0
7 WORDTAG O 47th
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Larnaca
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Cyprus
31 WORDTAG O 2-0
5 WORDTAG O 60th
24 WORDTAG O penalty
6 WORDTAG O 5-1
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Lithuania
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sion
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Nyva
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Estonia
10 WORDTAG O 3,000
6 WORDTAG O Aggregate
12 WORDTAG O score
13 WORDTAG O 2-2
57 WORDTAG O goals
27 WORDTAG O rule
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Norway
19 WORDTAG O 10th
10 WORDTAG I-PER Jan
7 WORDTAG O 5-2
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Bulgaria
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovenia
6 WORDTAG O 58th
9 WORDTAG O 25,000
8 WORDTAG O 4-3
5 WORDTAG O penalties
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vaduz
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Latvia
7 WORDTAG O 90th
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Luxembourg
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dynamo
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Sparta
11 WORDTAG O 4-0
6 WORDTAG O 26th
5 WORDTAG O 19th
6 WORDTAG O 80th
6 WORDTAG O 86th
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hearts
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Star
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Yugoslavia
5 WORDTAG O 59th
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Hapoel
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Moldova
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Hungary
6 WORDTAG O 1,500
10 WORDTAG O OUT
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BUDAPEST
18 WORDTAG O drew
25 WORDTAG O tie
128 WORDTAG O played
12 WORDTAG O 4-1
7 WORDTAG O 15th
5 WORDTAG I-PER Andreas
8 WORDTAG O CHAMPIONSHIP
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Brazilian
47 WORDTAG O championship
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Atletico
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SYDNEY
29 WORDTAG O captain
7 WORDTAG I-PER Newcombe
17 WORDTAG O resignation
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Wimbledon
68 WORDTAG O champion
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Davis
31 WORDTAG O coach
11 WORDTAG I-PER Tony
9 WORDTAG O determined
6 WORDTAG O events
9 WORDTAG O lose
14 WORDTAG O look
15 WORDTAG O giving
9 WORDTAG O someone
7 WORDTAG O else
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Sydney
100 WORDTAG O world
11 WORDTAG O Under
12 WORDTAG O leadership
12 WORDTAG O winners
8 WORDTAG O slipped
5 WORDTAG O Since
9 WORDTAG O doubles
9 WORDTAG O partner
13 WORDTAG O wins
16 WORDTAG O losses
5 WORDTAG O selected
5 WORDTAG O semifinalist
41 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympic
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Croatian
37 WORDTAG O best
15 WORDTAG O described
7 WORDTAG O faced
6 WORDTAG O 1986
10 WORDTAG O beaten
59 WORDTAG O ago
56 WORDTAG O Men
59 WORDTAG O singles
5 WORDTAG O 9/16
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Korea
6 WORDTAG O 15-7
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malaysia
6 WORDTAG I-PER Abdul
5 WORDTAG O 3/4
17 WORDTAG I-PER Van
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Netherlands
11 WORDTAG O 15-11
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Indonesia
12 WORDTAG O 15-6
8 WORDTAG O 15-8
13 WORDTAG O 15-12
54 WORDTAG O Women
5 WORDTAG O 11-6
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Zealand
26 WORDTAG O 'S
6 WORDTAG O DRAW
38 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.
73 WORDTAG I-LOC NEW
38 WORDTAG O draw
15 WORDTAG O championships
15 WORDTAG O beginning
6 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S
7 WORDTAG I-LOC National
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Tennis
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Centre
8 WORDTAG I-PER Pete
16 WORDTAG I-PER Sampras
64 WORDTAG O vs.
11 WORDTAG I-PER Adrian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magnus
44 WORDTAG O vs
9 WORDTAG O Qualifier
12 WORDTAG I-PER Andrei
6 WORDTAG I-PER Roberto
7 WORDTAG O ------------------------
8 WORDTAG I-PER Christian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grant
8 WORDTAG I-PER Fernando
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Brazil
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kafelnikov
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johansson
20 WORDTAG I-PER Medvedev
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fleurian
102 WORDTAG O 14
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costa
11 WORDTAG I-PER Jonathan
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bernd
9 WORDTAG I-PER Stefan
8 WORDTAG I-PER Edberg
21 WORDTAG I-PER Richard
5 WORDTAG I-PER Krajicek
11 WORDTAG I-PER Andre
9 WORDTAG I-PER Agassi
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombia
16 WORDTAG I-PER Carlos
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kevin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kim
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nicolas
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Ecuador
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alami
9 WORDTAG I-PER Enqvist
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
71 WORDTAG I-LOC Belgium
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Bahamas
17 WORDTAG I-PER Stich
5 WORDTAG I-PER Adams
8 WORDTAG I-PER Javier
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Argentina
5 WORDTAG I-PER Stefano
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Venezuela
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jeff
33 WORDTAG O BASEBALL
11 WORDTAG I-LOC BALTIMORE
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Baltimore
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Orioles
22 WORDTAG I-PER Johnson
8 WORDTAG O miss
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Seattle
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Mariners
31 WORDTAG O hospital
8 WORDTAG O treated
16 WORDTAG I-PER William
17 WORDTAG O adding
36 WORDTAG O released
8 WORDTAG I-PER Andy
8 WORDTAG O manage
8 WORDTAG O absence
12 WORDTAG I-ORG California
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Angels
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Columbia
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Hospital
13 WORDTAG O blood
59 WORDTAG O eight
5 WORDTAG O seasons
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Baltimore
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Cincinnati
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Reds
20 WORDTAG I-MISC National
49 WORDTAG I-MISC League
33 WORDTAG I-ORG York
106 WORDTAG O games
7 WORDTAG O pull
27 WORDTAG O within
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yankees
55 WORDTAG I-MISC American
5 WORDTAG I-MISC East
16 WORDTAG I-MISC MAJOR
41 WORDTAG I-MISC LEAGUE
40 WORDTAG O STANDINGS
7 WORDTAG O WEDNESDAY
14 WORDTAG O GAMES
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Baseball
32 WORDTAG O standings
32 WORDTAG O tabulate
102 WORDTAG O lost
38 WORDTAG O winning
25 WORDTAG O percentage
8 WORDTAG I-MISC AMERICAN
16 WORDTAG I-MISC EASTERN
48 WORDTAG I-MISC DIVISION
23 WORDTAG O W
27 WORDTAG O L
20 WORDTAG O GB
30 WORDTAG I-ORG NEW
30 WORDTAG I-ORG YORK
17 WORDTAG I-ORG BALTIMORE
25 WORDTAG O 58
16 WORDTAG I-ORG BOSTON
59 WORDTAG O 64
9 WORDTAG O .496
15 WORDTAG I-ORG TORONTO
5 WORDTAG O .457
16 WORDTAG I-ORG DETROIT
13 WORDTAG O 82
47 WORDTAG O 28
16 WORDTAG I-MISC CENTRAL
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CLEVELAND
30 WORDTAG I-ORG CHICAGO
17 WORDTAG I-ORG MINNESOTA
14 WORDTAG O .500
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MILWAUKEE
57 WORDTAG O 60
5 WORDTAG O .469
16 WORDTAG I-ORG KANSAS
17 WORDTAG I-ORG CITY
44 WORDTAG O 18
16 WORDTAG I-MISC WESTERN
15 WORDTAG I-ORG TEXAS
16 WORDTAG I-ORG SEATTLE
29 WORDTAG O 61
15 WORDTAG I-ORG OAKLAND
38 WORDTAG O 62
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CALIFORNIA
7 WORDTAG O THURSDAY
22 WORDTAG O AUGUST
16 WORDTAG O SCHEDULE
8 WORDTAG I-LOC BOSTON
7 WORDTAG I-LOC KANSAS
15 WORDTAG I-LOC CITY
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MINNESOTA
8 WORDTAG I-MISC NATIONAL
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ATLANTA
23 WORDTAG O 46
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MONTREAL
14 WORDTAG I-ORG FLORIDA
15 WORDTAG I-ORG PHILADELPHIA
15 WORDTAG I-ORG HOUSTON
17 WORDTAG I-ORG ST
15 WORDTAG I-ORG LOUIS
6 WORDTAG O .504
16 WORDTAG I-ORG CINCINNATI
14 WORDTAG I-ORG PITTSBURGH
29 WORDTAG I-ORG SAN
14 WORDTAG I-ORG DIEGO
6 WORDTAG O .543
17 WORDTAG I-ORG LOS
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ANGELES
15 WORDTAG I-ORG COLORADO
44 WORDTAG O 65
15 WORDTAG I-ORG FRANCISCO
8 WORDTAG I-LOC COLORADO
7 WORDTAG I-LOC ATLANTA
8 WORDTAG I-LOC HOUSTON
5 WORDTAG I-LOC LOS
5 WORDTAG I-LOC ANGELES
21 WORDTAG I-LOC SAN
9 WORDTAG I-LOC FRANCISCO
7 WORDTAG O Baseball
8 WORDTAG O CAPS
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Chicago
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Milwaukee
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Oakland
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Texas
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Toronto
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Florida
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Pittsburgh
52 WORDTAG I-ORG St
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Louis
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Philadelphia
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Montreal
5 WORDTAG I-LOC CLEVELAND
9 WORDTAG O two-run
26 WORDTAG O homer
26 WORDTAG O inning
8 WORDTAG O rallied
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cleveland
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Indians
5 WORDTAG O rubber
9 WORDTAG O three-game
31 WORDTAG O series
17 WORDTAG O With
10 WORDTAG O pitch
26 WORDTAG O tried
24 WORDTAG O big
13 WORDTAG O crowd
33 WORDTAG O shot
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rodriguez
20 WORDTAG O double
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johnny
7 WORDTAG I-PER Terry
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kennedy
39 WORDTAG O 40
39 WORDTAG O nine
9 WORDTAG O meetings
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Western
19 WORDTAG O teams
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Central
10 WORDTAG O extra
22 WORDTAG O ninth
23 WORDTAG O single
5 WORDTAG O save
29 WORDTAG O got
19 WORDTAG O allowing
40 WORDTAG O hits
5 WORDTAG O walks
7 WORDTAG O strikeouts
5 WORDTAG O scoreless
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dean
6 WORDTAG O 30th
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ripken
7 WORDTAG O solo
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bobby
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bonilla
10 WORDTAG O three-run
16 WORDTAG O seventh
43 WORDTAG O power
58 WORDTAG O runs
31 WORDTAG O fifth
11 WORDTAG O bottom
6 WORDTAG O starter
8 WORDTAG O blast
49 WORDTAG O allowed
10 WORDTAG O relief
13 WORDTAG I-MISC RBI
35 WORDTAG O cut
27 WORDTAG O straight
8 WORDTAG O homers
20 WORDTAG O dropped
10 WORDTAG O row
8 WORDTAG O became
8 WORDTAG O major-league
12 WORDTAG O history
21 WORDTAG O 34
10 WORDTAG O scattered
12 WORDTAG O debut
29 WORDTAG O each
8 WORDTAG I-PER Derek
7 WORDTAG O settled
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jimmy
14 WORDTAG O interim
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Boston
15 WORDTAG I-PER Mike
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Sox
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Athletics
10 WORDTAG O owns
19 WORDTAG O career
5 WORDTAG O bases
6 WORDTAG O loaded
43 WORDTAG O went
14 WORDTAG O walk
5 WORDTAG O stole
9 WORDTAG O homered
17 WORDTAG O drove
9 WORDTAG O capped
15 WORDTAG O eighth
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Tigers
9 WORDTAG I-ORG White
11 WORDTAG O consecutive
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kansas
19 WORDTAG I-LOC City
16 WORDTAG I-PER Juan
5 WORDTAG I-PER Guzman
5 WORDTAG O span
9 WORDTAG O earned
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Minnesota
5 WORDTAG O five-run
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Brewers
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Twins
20 WORDTAG I-PER Jose
28 WORDTAG I-ORG PSV
17 WORDTAG O WIN
5 WORDTAG I-PER Cocu
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Eindhoven
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NEC
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nijmegen
7 WORDTAG O kick
75 WORDTAG O minutes
5 WORDTAG I-PER Nilis
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Ajax
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Amsterdam
21 WORDTAG O defence
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NAC
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Breda
14 WORDTAG I-MISC DUTCH
46 WORDTAG O DIVISION
9 WORDTAG O SUMMARY
13 WORDTAG O 11th
26 WORDTAG O Halftime
5 WORDTAG O 1-2
15 WORDTAG O RESULT
7 WORDTAG I-LOC GENEVA
46 WORDTAG O 26
5 WORDTAG O recalled
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jorge
6 WORDTAG O finals
10 WORDTAG O clearly
12 WORDTAG O progress
6 WORDTAG O beyond
6 WORDTAG O phase
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Euro
6 WORDTAG I-MISC 96
7 WORDTAG O Squad
8 WORDTAG I-PER Marco
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Grasshoppers
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
8 WORDTAG I-PER Antonio
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Milan
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Borussia
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Dortmund
12 WORDTAG O ATHLETICS
7 WORDTAG O RECORD
7 WORDTAG O 40,000
15 WORDTAG O THE
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Brussels
14 WORDTAG O grand
7 WORDTAG O prix
6 WORDTAG O athletes
5 WORDTAG O glass
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Belgian
28 WORDTAG O pay
11 WORDTAG O organisers
18 WORDTAG O rounds
11 WORDTAG O ever
48 WORDTAG O already
8 WORDTAG O records
13 WORDTAG O broken
48 WORDTAG O women
19 WORDTAG O 1,000
13 WORDTAG O ROUND
34 WORDTAG O Leading
7 WORDTAG O golf
5 WORDTAG I-PER Broadhurst
10 WORDTAG I-PER Raymond
22 WORDTAG I-PER Ian
7 WORDTAG I-PER Woosnam
7 WORDTAG I-PER Roe
9 WORDTAG I-PER Carl
12 WORDTAG I-PER Stephen
6 WORDTAG I-PER Lawrie
10 WORDTAG I-PER Max
5 WORDTAG I-PER Carter
10 WORDTAG I-PER Lee
8 WORDTAG I-PER Miguel
9 WORDTAG I-PER Angel
13 WORDTAG I-PER Gary
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eales
16 WORDTAG I-PER Williams
10 WORDTAG I-PER Andrew
29 WORDTAG I-PER Robert
6 WORDTAG I-PER Marcus
12 WORDTAG I-PER Pedro
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linhart
10 WORDTAG O additional
6 WORDTAG I-MISC UEFA
8 WORDTAG O headed
5 WORDTAG O rankings
13 WORDTAG O account
7 WORDTAG O factors
48 WORDTAG O including
7 WORDTAG O red
43 WORDTAG O national
7 WORDTAG O allocated
8 WORDTAG O places
65 WORDTAG O 4.
64 WORDTAG O 5.
64 WORDTAG O 6.
53 WORDTAG O 7.
50 WORDTAG O 8.
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Belarus
37 WORDTAG O 9.
33 WORDTAG O 10.
8 WORDTAG O 13.
6 WORDTAG O 15.
7 WORDTAG O 16.
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Portugal
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Greece
12 WORDTAG O MATCH
14 WORDTAG I-LOC COLOMBO
224 WORDTAG O police
25 WORDTAG O ground
36 WORDTAG O tour
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Sri
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Lanka
5 WORDTAG O youth
13 WORDTAG O limited
35 WORDTAG O overs
11 WORDTAG O includes
71 WORDTAG I-LOC India
11 WORDTAG O promised
15 WORDTAG O presence
10 WORDTAG O policemen
27 WORDTAG O making
20 WORDTAG O ethnic
27 WORDTAG O violence
7 WORDTAG O balls
5 WORDTAG O fours
105 WORDTAG O made
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SOFIA
26 WORDTAG O One
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Romanian
15 WORDTAG O others
30 WORDTAG O injured
16 WORDTAG O bus
9 WORDTAG O collided
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Bulgarian
42 WORDTAG O morning
27 WORDTAG O road
11 WORDTAG O towns
31 WORDTAG O woman
12 WORDTAG I-PER Maria
18 WORDTAG O 35
13 WORDTAG O accident
5 WORDTAG I-ORG OJ
30 WORDTAG O *
10 WORDTAG O Note
5 WORDTAG O contents
6 WORDTAG O displayed
34 WORDTAG O order
5 WORDTAG O printed
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Journal
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Regulation
6 WORDTAG O invitation
19 WORDTAG O tender
7 WORDTAG O refunds
14 WORDTAG O white
10 WORDTAG O certain
5 WORDTAG O payments
24 WORDTAG O system
5 WORDTAG O producers
9 WORDTAG O values
5 WORDTAG O END
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Home
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Health
21 WORDTAG O appeal
30 WORDTAG I-ORG U.S.
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Court
43 WORDTAG O decision
5 WORDTAG O reimbursement
11 WORDTAG O previously
7 WORDTAG O regarding
6 WORDTAG O related
16 WORDTAG O community
7 WORDTAG O personnel
11 WORDTAG O continues
18 WORDTAG O believe
16 WORDTAG O majority
17 WORDTAG O terms
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Medicare
8 WORDTAG O program
9 WORDTAG O resolution
5 WORDTAG O recorded
11 WORDTAG O reserve
9 WORDTAG O equal
8 WORDTAG O revenue
15 WORDTAG O ruled
50 WORDTAG O court
5 WORDTAG O dispute
6 WORDTAG O pleased
12 WORDTAG O significant
6 WORDTAG O toward
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsdesk
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Capital
5 WORDTAG O div
11 WORDTAG O distribution
57 WORDTAG O rate
7 WORDTAG O quarterly
11 WORDTAG O improved
55 WORDTAG O ended
33 WORDTAG O declared
5 WORDTAG O partnership
22 WORDTAG O unit
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Best
9 WORDTAG O sees
38 WORDTAG I-ORG Co
5 WORDTAG O Chairman
5 WORDTAG O Chief
6 WORDTAG O retailer
16 WORDTAG O annual
25 WORDTAG O even
8 WORDTAG O emerged
20 WORDTAG O always
5 WORDTAG O particularly
71 WORDTAG O you
12 WORDTAG O something
8 WORDTAG O stores
23 WORDTAG O fall
9 WORDTAG O closing
53 WORDTAG O plan
16 WORDTAG O states
19 WORDTAG O For
35 WORDTAG O 29
103 WORDTAG O 1996-08-23
9 WORDTAG O researchers
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Swedish
11 WORDTAG O born
19 WORDTAG O caught
6 WORDTAG O developed
14 WORDTAG O cases
9 WORDTAG I-LOC of
9 WORDTAG O delivered
5 WORDTAG O 1949
33 WORDTAG O children
10 WORDTAG O wrote
16 WORDTAG O medical
6 WORDTAG O sometimes
5 WORDTAG O require
14 WORDTAG O surgery
7 WORDTAG O pain
7 WORDTAG O weight
20 WORDTAG O involved
9 WORDTAG O especially
15 WORDTAG O often
10 WORDTAG O cause
7 WORDTAG O Most
37 WORDTAG O high
5 WORDTAG O baby
10 WORDTAG O All
18 WORDTAG O key
13 WORDTAG O industrial
9 WORDTAG O Following
17 WORDTAG O survey
11 WORDTAG I-ORG British
8 WORDTAG O AUG
13 WORDTAG O book
21 WORDTAG O stocks
17 WORDTAG O goods
9 WORDTAG O expectations
11 WORDTAG O above
7 WORDTAG O normal
11 WORDTAG O below
30 WORDTAG O companies
5 WORDTAG O representing
12 WORDTAG O employees
7 WORDTAG O brokers
10 WORDTAG O built
9 WORDTAG O 1989
5 WORDTAG O buyers
5 WORDTAG I-MISC No
22 WORDTAG O Some
11 WORDTAG O subject
5 WORDTAG O pills
7 WORDTAG O cholesterol
5 WORDTAG O finds
12 WORDTAG O show
11 WORDTAG O doctors
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Oxford
13 WORDTAG I-ORG University
176 WORDTAG O people
7 WORDTAG O benefit
6 WORDTAG O garlic
27 WORDTAG O levels
5 WORDTAG O 900
29 WORDTAG O groups
9 WORDTAG O receiving
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Royal
8 WORDTAG O Several
13 WORDTAG O pressure
15 WORDTAG O either
16 WORDTAG O special
23 WORDTAG O trial
9 WORDTAG O makes
13 WORDTAG O address
16 WORDTAG O whole
6 WORDTAG O affect
5 WORDTAG O gives
9 WORDTAG O aid
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Caribbean
14 WORDTAG O 39
17 WORDTAG O development
40 WORDTAG O much
9 WORDTAG O population
11 WORDTAG O living
26 WORDTAG O south
7 WORDTAG O fled
27 WORDTAG O times
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Plymouth
41 WORDTAG O north
15 WORDTAG O provide
17 WORDTAG O track
16 WORDTAG O programme
39 WORDTAG O area
7 WORDTAG O active
38 WORDTAG O recent
9 WORDTAG O shown
15 WORDTAG O remain
108 WORDTAG O she
25 WORDTAG I-PER Bill
7 WORDTAG O World
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Grand
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Slam
32 WORDTAG O seed
16 WORDTAG I-PER Graf
5 WORDTAG O aiming
25 WORDTAG O able
40 WORDTAG O major
8 WORDTAG O begins
10 WORDTAG O opens
5 WORDTAG O crown
6 WORDTAG I-PER Basuki
8 WORDTAG O ceremony
59 WORDTAG O both
7 WORDTAG O holders
13 WORDTAG O rising
22 WORDTAG O defeat
12 WORDTAG O While
5 WORDTAG O semifinal
10 WORDTAG O star
5 WORDTAG O tested
18 WORDTAG O probably
6 WORDTAG O repeat
8 WORDTAG O landing
19 WORDTAG O sixth
7 WORDTAG O avoided
8 WORDTAG O possibility
10 WORDTAG O quarter-finals
5 WORDTAG O ranked
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Czech
8 WORDTAG I-PER Monica
12 WORDTAG I-PER Seles
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anne
6 WORDTAG I-PER Miller
10 WORDTAG O victim
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Austrian
23 WORDTAG O seeded
11 WORDTAG O faces
27 WORDTAG O playing
33 WORDTAG O yet
6 WORDTAG O unfortunate
8 WORDTAG O first-round
7 WORDTAG O popular
6 WORDTAG O affair
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Frenchman
21 WORDTAG O injury
8 WORDTAG O runner-up
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anke
12 WORDTAG I-PER Huber
6 WORDTAG I-PER Conchita
16 WORDTAG I-PER Martinez
7 WORDTAG I-PER Lindsay
8 WORDTAG I-PER Davenport
15 WORDTAG O looking
9 WORDTAG O opponents
5 WORDTAG I-PER Amanda
8 WORDTAG I-PER Coetzer
22 WORDTAG O young
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hingis
10 WORDTAG O clash
6 WORDTAG I-PER Jana
5 WORDTAG I-PER Novotna
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Sydney
13 WORDTAG O 61-2
9 WORDTAG O 9373-1800
12 WORDTAG I-ORG RTRS
11 WORDTAG O worked
17 WORDTAG O along
5 WORDTAG O unseeded
10 WORDTAG O Other
15 WORDTAG O hour
26 WORDTAG O 55
30 WORDTAG O point
24 WORDTAG O break
6 WORDTAG O compatriot
6 WORDTAG O 13th
9 WORDTAG O knew
34 WORDTAG O service
8 WORDTAG O serving
21 WORDTAG O really
6 WORDTAG O chances
12 WORDTAG O every
31 WORDTAG O come
7 WORDTAG O Playing
9 WORDTAG O maybe
6 WORDTAG O difference
22 WORDTAG O deficit
7 WORDTAG O surprise
23 WORDTAG O 32
5 WORDTAG O quick
25 WORDTAG O arrived
13 WORDTAG O And
28 WORDTAG O soon
25 WORDTAG O 'm
9 WORDTAG O fought
6 WORDTAG O hoped
14 WORDTAG O tight
13 WORDTAG O helped
6 WORDTAG O Soccer
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Korean
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SEOUL
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Anyang
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Puchon
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Suwon
39 WORDTAG O Standings
51 WORDTAG O drawn
9 WORDTAG O D
6 WORDTAG O G
5 WORDTAG O F
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chonan
6 WORDTAG O outbreak
9 WORDTAG O kills
47 WORDTAG O central
20 WORDTAG O staff
9 WORDTAG O People
11 WORDTAG O appear
8 WORDTAG O 160
51 WORDTAG O miles
9 WORDTAG O southeast
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Nigerian
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Liberia
16 WORDTAG O General
15 WORDTAG O commander
29 WORDTAG O latest
25 WORDTAG O civil
18 WORDTAG O officers
9 WORDTAG O dozen
6 WORDTAG O accords
17 WORDTAG O difficult
5 WORDTAG O painful
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Nations
8 WORDTAG O observers
9 WORDTAG O travelling
22 WORDTAG O western
15 WORDTAG O delayed
15 WORDTAG O shooting
6 WORDTAG O highway
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anthony
13 WORDTAG O finally
11 WORDTAG O faction
126 WORDTAG O Saturday
5 WORDTAG O breaking
6 WORDTAG O disarmament
16 WORDTAG O 10,000
15 WORDTAG I-ORG West
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Guinea
5 WORDTAG O prayer
7 WORDTAG I-MISC West
8 WORDTAG O repeatedly
22 WORDTAG O radio
22 WORDTAG O dead
10 WORDTAG O reason
31 WORDTAG O clear
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Organisation
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Islamic
7 WORDTAG O prayers
40 WORDTAG O army
21 WORDTAG O ordered
5 WORDTAG O crackdown
21 WORDTAG O seized
31 WORDTAG O death
17 WORDTAG O 1993
5 WORDTAG O bottle
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JOHANNESBURG
15 WORDTAG O boy
19 WORDTAG O girl
23 WORDTAG O whose
30 WORDTAG O old
28 WORDTAG O prison
9 WORDTAG O son
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Island
8 WORDTAG O winter
25 WORDTAG O letter
5 WORDTAG O ordinary
18 WORDTAG O post
7 WORDTAG O age
6 WORDTAG O reply
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlantic
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
5 WORDTAG O belonging
20 WORDTAG O couple
12 WORDTAG O front
5 WORDTAG O garden
23 WORDTAG O house
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Johannesburg
20 WORDTAG O His
14 WORDTAG O body
5 WORDTAG O parents
5 WORDTAG O unclear
14 WORDTAG O enough
6 WORDTAG O becoming
6 WORDTAG O m
6 WORDTAG O Current
5 WORDTAG I-ORG NBH
18 WORDTAG O bln
23 WORDTAG O %
10 WORDTAG O Government
9 WORDTAG O 1998
22 WORDTAG I-ORG &
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Moody
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Investors
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Japan
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Agency
7 WORDTAG O flow
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Budapest
21 WORDTAG O 36
6 WORDTAG O die
17 WORDTAG I-LOC MOSCOW
35 WORDTAG O least
17 WORDTAG O separatist
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Chechen
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Grozny
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Interfax
6 WORDTAG O command
34 WORDTAG I-LOC Chechnya
20 WORDTAG O 200
5 WORDTAG I-ORG interior
5 WORDTAG I-ORG ministry
20 WORDTAG O mission
27 WORDTAG O confirmed
42 WORDTAG I-PER Lebed
7 WORDTAG O chief-of-staff
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aslan
10 WORDTAG I-PER Maskhadov
43 WORDTAG O agreement
5 WORDTAG O noon
5 WORDTAG O letters
11 WORDTAG O threatening
6 WORDTAG O explained
41 WORDTAG O money
11 WORDTAG O residents
8 WORDTAG O lives
9 WORDTAG O nearby
7 WORDTAG O railway
8 WORDTAG O station
21 WORDTAG O school
16 WORDTAG O books
36 WORDTAG O case
25 WORDTAG O poor
16 WORDTAG O family
7 WORDTAG O trouble
41 WORDTAG O index
10 WORDTAG O pts
19 WORDTAG O sign
14 WORDTAG I-PER Boris
47 WORDTAG I-PER Yeltsin
53 WORDTAG O security
6 WORDTAG O renewed
9 WORDTAG O document
5 WORDTAG O negotiated
24 WORDTAG O village
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Itar-Tass
5 WORDTAG O provided
5 WORDTAG O aide
26 WORDTAG O completed
30 WORDTAG O showed
5 WORDTAG O nominee
24 WORDTAG O returned
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Kremlin
7 WORDTAG O two-day
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosnia
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Sarajevo
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Bosnian
9 WORDTAG O federation
16 WORDTAG O common
6 WORDTAG O taxes
6 WORDTAG O kuna
20 WORDTAG O mark
20 WORDTAG O currency
14 WORDTAG O introduced
46 WORDTAG I-ORG and
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbian
5 WORDTAG O mines
9 WORDTAG O According
9 WORDTAG O mine
6 WORDTAG O briefly
19 WORDTAG O overnight
5 WORDTAG O planes
5 WORDTAG O artillery
17 WORDTAG O although
11 WORDTAG O heard
6 WORDTAG O speaking
11 WORDTAG O flew
7 WORDTAG O firing
14 WORDTAG O anything
10 WORDTAG O separatists
6 WORDTAG O halt
14 WORDTAG O threatened
6 WORDTAG O bombing
12 WORDTAG O assault
30 WORDTAG O passengers
8 WORDTAG O rescued
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Colombian
9 WORDTAG O coast
5 WORDTAG I-LOC BOGOTA
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Coast
14 WORDTAG O boat
14 WORDTAG O missing
29 WORDTAG O trip
7 WORDTAG O fuel
7 WORDTAG O sea
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Argentine
5 WORDTAG I-LOC BUENOS
5 WORDTAG I-LOC AIRES
5 WORDTAG O iron
34 WORDTAG O production
5 WORDTAG O cold
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Peru
10 WORDTAG O kill
6 WORDTAG O terrorist
18 WORDTAG O sources
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoist
30 WORDTAG O small
6 WORDTAG O northeast
7 WORDTAG O propaganda
25 WORDTAG O centre
5 WORDTAG O By
22 WORDTAG O 1992
8 WORDTAG O activities
14 WORDTAG O guerrilla
22 WORDTAG O cost
18 WORDTAG O damage
5 WORDTAG O 1980
16 WORDTAG O Former
9 WORDTAG I-PER Brunswijk
9 WORDTAG O custody
26 WORDTAG O charged
6 WORDTAG O attempted
18 WORDTAG O murder
22 WORDTAG O turned
24 WORDTAG O himself
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pinas
5 WORDTAG O mining
27 WORDTAG O 56
19 WORDTAG O 90
13 WORDTAG O east
8 WORDTAG O showing
13 WORDTAG O cuts
25 WORDTAG O wife
31 WORDTAG O charges
5 WORDTAG O merely
24 WORDTAG O less
7 WORDTAG O regime
13 WORDTAG O conflict
10 WORDTAG O 500
16 WORDTAG O caused
13 WORDTAG O thousands
11 WORDTAG O neighbouring
6 WORDTAG O 1980s
5 WORDTAG O eventually
6 WORDTAG O Despite
5 WORDTAG O businessman
11 WORDTAG O interests
19 WORDTAG O saw
10 WORDTAG O leads
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Thai
10 WORDTAG O heroin
7 WORDTAG I-LOC BANGKOK
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Hong
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Kong
50 WORDTAG O arrested
10 WORDTAG O kg
5 WORDTAG O searched
39 WORDTAG O Police
48 WORDTAG O several
7 WORDTAG O street
8 WORDTAG O baht
10 WORDTAG O Officials
9 WORDTAG O detained
5 WORDTAG O pending
8 WORDTAG O formal
6 WORDTAG O follows
7 WORDTAG O nations
5 WORDTAG O consulate
6 WORDTAG O colony
25 WORDTAG O sell
19 WORDTAG O issues
13 WORDTAG O include
43 WORDTAG O plans
15 WORDTAG O pact
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Tibet
5 WORDTAG O exiled
9 WORDTAG O conservative
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Palestinian
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Information
11 WORDTAG O written
6 WORDTAG O critics
6 WORDTAG O self-rule
17 WORDTAG O deals
7 WORDTAG O anyone
19 WORDTAG O legal
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Amman
7 WORDTAG O owner
7 WORDTAG O copies
6 WORDTAG O citizen
8 WORDTAG O accord
38 WORDTAG O On
6 WORDTAG O confiscated
5 WORDTAG O insisted
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Authority
5 WORDTAG O strategy
5 WORDTAG O freedom
6 WORDTAG O resulted
5 WORDTAG O mistakes
6 WORDTAG O explain
7 WORDTAG O journalists
14 WORDTAG O banned
5 WORDTAG O sure
7 WORDTAG O selling
39 WORDTAG O think
13 WORDTAG O ?
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Jewish
13 WORDTAG O handed
8 WORDTAG O parts
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Istanbul
7 WORDTAG I-LOC CAIRO
34 WORDTAG O airport
21 WORDTAG O fire
5 WORDTAG O taxi
9 WORDTAG O onto
23 WORDTAG O line
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mohamed
36 WORDTAG O conference
7 WORDTAG O instead
6 WORDTAG O yards
5 WORDTAG O aviation
14 WORDTAG O noted
6 WORDTAG O pilot
7 WORDTAG O Its
30 WORDTAG O private
13 WORDTAG O wants
15 WORDTAG O nothing
23 WORDTAG I-MISC Sudanese
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Egyptian
11 WORDTAG O militants
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mubarak
11 WORDTAG O speech
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslem
21 WORDTAG I-ORG Security
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Council
10 WORDTAG O flights
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Khartoum
12 WORDTAG O incident
14 WORDTAG O effect
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Sudan
6 WORDTAG O fails
11 WORDTAG O cannot
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Ethiopia
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Front
22 WORDTAG O far
18 WORDTAG O relations
98 WORDTAG O shares
5 WORDTAG O shed
5 WORDTAG O profit-taking
6 WORDTAG O amid
22 WORDTAG O volume
9 WORDTAG O trillion
28 WORDTAG O rise
65 WORDTAG O profit
12 WORDTAG O session
11 WORDTAG O gained
11 WORDTAG O Shares
7 WORDTAG O Of
9 WORDTAG O stable
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Miss
10 WORDTAG I-PER Machado
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Mexico
6 WORDTAG O questions
7 WORDTAG O claims
10 WORDTAG O crash
45 WORDTAG O 19
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Los
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Angeles
7 WORDTAG O attended
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc.
12 WORDTAG O drop
17 WORDTAG O losing
7 WORDTAG O 112
5 WORDTAG O blocked
5 WORDTAG O appearance
24 WORDTAG O stage
31 WORDTAG O She
20 WORDTAG O stay
5 WORDTAG O returning
19 WORDTAG O Sept
11 WORDTAG O alleged
7 WORDTAG O putting
9 WORDTAG O fine
8 WORDTAG O happened
5 WORDTAG O associated
5 WORDTAG O routine
8 WORDTAG I-PER Kevorkian
9 WORDTAG O suicide
6 WORDTAG O bringing
10 WORDTAG O suffering
6 WORDTAG O multiple
14 WORDTAG O emergency
8 WORDTAG O room
5 WORDTAG I-PER Patricia
8 WORDTAG I-PER Smith
6 WORDTAG O midday
7 WORDTAG O attending
14 WORDTAG O starting
7 WORDTAG O doctor
11 WORDTAG O lawyer
17 WORDTAG O husband
12 WORDTAG O father
11 WORDTAG I-PER James
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Texas
7 WORDTAG I-PER Judith
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Massachusetts
18 WORDTAG O suffered
18 WORDTAG O life
8 WORDTAG O Rating
22 WORDTAG O As
8 WORDTAG O Sale
8 WORDTAG O Amount
8 WORDTAG O Date
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Municipal
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Desk
6 WORDTAG O 212-859-1650
10 WORDTAG O jailed
10 WORDTAG O sentenced
13 WORDTAG I-PER Lauck
9 WORDTAG O base
7 WORDTAG O abuse
8 WORDTAG O struggle
8 WORDTAG O network
11 WORDTAG O material
11 WORDTAG O judge
7 WORDTAG O greatest
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Nazi
6 WORDTAG O slaughter
12 WORDTAG O millions
5 WORDTAG O complex
7 WORDTAG O prosecutor
9 WORDTAG O demanded
10 WORDTAG O five-year
6 WORDTAG O satisfied
7 WORDTAG O sentence
26 WORDTAG O illegal
5 WORDTAG O laws
8 WORDTAG O produce
8 WORDTAG O magazines
5 WORDTAG O Interior
16 WORDTAG O biggest
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrats
10 WORDTAG O suit
11 WORDTAG O spent
9 WORDTAG O nor
8 WORDTAG O extradition
7 WORDTAG O truth
7 WORDTAG O actions
9 WORDTAG O carried
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Socialist
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Workers
20 WORDTAG O name
6 WORDTAG O magazine
11 WORDTAG O request
13 WORDTAG O convicted
7 WORDTAG O organisations
17 WORDTAG O arrest
5 WORDTAG O arrangements
10 WORDTAG O quite
11 WORDTAG O monitors
10 WORDTAG O carry
21 WORDTAG I-ORG Department
17 WORDTAG O deputy
5 WORDTAG I-ORG TV
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Algerian
14 WORDTAG O suspected
22 WORDTAG O killing
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Algeria
6 WORDTAG O Security
15 WORDTAG O sought
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Catholic
22 WORDTAG O bomb
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Algiers
12 WORDTAG O 50,000
10 WORDTAG O 110
7 WORDTAG O foreigners
6 WORDTAG O radical
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamists
9 WORDTAG O commanding
7 WORDTAG O flown
11 WORDTAG O table
8 WORDTAG O shows
11 WORDTAG O airports
5 WORDTAG O association
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Berlin
6 WORDTAG O 202
5 WORDTAG O 4.4
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Frankfurt
9 WORDTAG O 1.5
6 WORDTAG O 3.5
5 WORDTAG O TOTAL
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Air
10 WORDTAG O research
5 WORDTAG O Not
29 WORDTAG O forecast
14 WORDTAG O performance
14 WORDTAG O EPS
6 WORDTAG O Dividend
5 WORDTAG O Fax
93 WORDTAG I-PER Clinton
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ballybunion
12 WORDTAG O fans
27 WORDTAG I-LOC Chicago
6 WORDTAG O resort
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Irish
13 WORDTAG I-LOC America
5 WORDTAG I-PER Dick
31 WORDTAG I-MISC Democratic
26 WORDTAG O convention
8 WORDTAG O bring
7 WORDTAG O addressed
6 WORDTAG O packed
35 WORDTAG O us
11 WORDTAG I-PER Frank
29 WORDTAG O process
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ischinger
17 WORDTAG O seek
9 WORDTAG O solution
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cooperation
8 WORDTAG I-ORG in
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Europe
25 WORDTAG I-ORG OSCE
6 WORDTAG O personal
8 WORDTAG O threat
18 WORDTAG O positive
13 WORDTAG O responsible
6 WORDTAG O global
26 WORDTAG O nuclear
24 WORDTAG O treaty
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Delhi
6 WORDTAG O intended
6 WORDTAG I-PER Gujral
7 WORDTAG O block
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Geneva
13 WORDTAG O entering
7 WORDTAG O signing
20 WORDTAG O weapons
10 WORDTAG O bilateral
26 WORDTAG O position
5 WORDTAG O clause
5 WORDTAG O Asked
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Assembly
9 WORDTAG O cross
16 WORDTAG O fact
6 WORDTAG O weapon
8 WORDTAG O concerns
6 WORDTAG O impossible
6 WORDTAG O option
23 WORDTAG O carrying
11 WORDTAG O tests
13 WORDTAG O accept
5 WORDTAG I-LOC DHAKA
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Dhaka
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangladesh
5 WORDTAG O importance
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mia
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Commonwealth
6 WORDTAG O Affairs
7 WORDTAG I-PER Liam
11 WORDTAG I-PER Fox
6 WORDTAG O arriving
13 WORDTAG O injuries
6 WORDTAG O complained
8 WORDTAG O wrist
14 WORDTAG O act
6 WORDTAG O seriously
9 WORDTAG O reasons
22 WORDTAG O important
24 WORDTAG O leave
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Nepal
6 WORDTAG O governments
11 WORDTAG I-ORG House
5 WORDTAG O matter
10 WORDTAG O investigation
5 WORDTAG O outcome
8 WORDTAG O connection
40 WORDTAG O business
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Kashmir
17 WORDTAG O polls
7 WORDTAG O Home
9 WORDTAG O planning
7 WORDTAG O troubled
5 WORDTAG O seems
6 WORDTAG O 1987
12 WORDTAG O direct
10 WORDTAG O create
17 WORDTAG O among
10 WORDTAG O growing
26 WORDTAG O independence
7 WORDTAG O hopes
16 WORDTAG O 20,000
8 WORDTAG O Over
6 WORDTAG O engineering
22 WORDTAG O banks
8 WORDTAG O edged
6 WORDTAG O sharply
23 WORDTAG O investors
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Stock
25 WORDTAG I-ORG Exchange
6 WORDTAG O turnover
5 WORDTAG O taka
19 WORDTAG O remained
14 WORDTAG O unchanged
8 WORDTAG O recovered
6 WORDTAG O edge
6 WORDTAG O ratio
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Reserve
6 WORDTAG I-ORG India
19 WORDTAG O governor
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rangarajan
5 WORDTAG O maintained
9 WORDTAG O reduced
23 WORDTAG O having
14 WORDTAG O supply
6 WORDTAG O increasing
8 WORDTAG O stood
5 WORDTAG O commitment
9 WORDTAG O response
13 WORDTAG O gross
14 WORDTAG O product
10 WORDTAG O GDP
11 WORDTAG O real
21 WORDTAG I-PER Mother
21 WORDTAG I-PER Teresa
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Nobel
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Peace
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Prize
18 WORDTAG O hope
6 WORDTAG O love
6 WORDTAG O nun
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Albanian
23 WORDTAG O need
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Roman
5 WORDTAG O missionary
5 WORDTAG O intensive
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Indian
15 WORDTAG O heart
8 WORDTAG O 86
19 WORDTAG O condition
8 WORDTAG O task
6 WORDTAG O alone
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Calcutta
5 WORDTAG O grew
18 WORDTAG O 80
6 WORDTAG O highest
6 WORDTAG O award
8 WORDTAG O Her
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vatican
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Missionaries
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Charity
17 WORDTAG O More
9 WORDTAG O delegates
8 WORDTAG O elect
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Rome
6 WORDTAG O receive
7 WORDTAG O failing
9 WORDTAG O stopped
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Serbia
13 WORDTAG O religious
13 WORDTAG O begin
14 WORDTAG O approved
11 WORDTAG O training
9 WORDTAG O missionaries
19 WORDTAG O rest
9 WORDTAG O 150
14 WORDTAG O homes
5 WORDTAG O destitute
7 WORDTAG O founded
6 WORDTAG O forecasts
12 WORDTAG O boost
7 WORDTAG I-PER Bernard
17 WORDTAG I-ORG News
31 WORDTAG I-ORG Ltd
6 WORDTAG O 1995/96
21 WORDTAG O profits
10 WORDTAG O film
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Day
9 WORDTAG O 1996/97
5 WORDTAG O From
10 WORDTAG O begun
6 WORDTAG O motion
6 WORDTAG O picture
19 WORDTAG O orders
10 WORDTAG O advertising
14 WORDTAG O shareholders
19 WORDTAG I-MISC A$
8 WORDTAG I-MISC US$
57 WORDTAG O cents
6 WORDTAG O Analysts
9 WORDTAG O disappointing
8 WORDTAG O outlook
13 WORDTAG I-ORG First
6 WORDTAG O offset
10 WORDTAG O operations
15 WORDTAG O hard
11 WORDTAG O operating
6 WORDTAG O cover
13 WORDTAG I-ORG The
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sun
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Times
7 WORDTAG O revenues
5 WORDTAG O arm
17 WORDTAG O operation
10 WORDTAG O hurt
17 WORDTAG I-LOC San
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Francisco
6 WORDTAG O minimum
5 WORDTAG O setting
14 WORDTAG O pulled
36 WORDTAG O 're
7 WORDTAG O internal
19 WORDTAG O declined
40 WORDTAG O budget
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Australia
5 WORDTAG O realised
5 WORDTAG O raising
57 WORDTAG O bank
7 WORDTAG O pledged
5 WORDTAG O effects
14 WORDTAG O activity
10 WORDTAG O generally
12 WORDTAG O long-term
17 WORDTAG O investment
10 WORDTAG O lending
9 WORDTAG I-LOC WELLINGTON
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Zealand
5 WORDTAG O cutting
10 WORDTAG O New
5 WORDTAG O 10.5
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Wellington
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Power
5 WORDTAG O approach
15 WORDTAG O followed
7 WORDTAG O equipment
7 WORDTAG O hunt
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Thailand
14 WORDTAG O launched
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangkok
22 WORDTAG O drug
7 WORDTAG O escape
8 WORDTAG O confident
5 WORDTAG O trafficking
5 WORDTAG O window
6 WORDTAG O climbed
8 WORDTAG O bed
9 WORDTAG O department
11 WORDTAG O prevent
6 WORDTAG O 266
5 WORDTAG O parent
15 WORDTAG I-LOC TOKYO
14 WORDTAG O Year
10 WORDTAG O billions
30 WORDTAG O yen
6 WORDTAG O specified
6 WORDTAG O LATEST
5 WORDTAG O ACTUAL
8 WORDTAG O FORECAST
5 WORDTAG O YEAR-AGO
12 WORDTAG O Sales
21 WORDTAG O 400
14 WORDTAG O NOTE
8 WORDTAG I-MISC HK$
19 WORDTAG O 43
11 WORDTAG O mln
14 WORDTAG I-LOC HONG
14 WORDTAG I-LOC KONG
5 WORDTAG O placed
16 WORDTAG O basis
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hong
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Kong
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Central
5 WORDTAG O 852
5 WORDTAG O applications
6 WORDTAG O believes
6 WORDTAG O respect
6 WORDTAG O safety
5 WORDTAG O Health
6 WORDTAG O maximum
14 WORDTAG O 2000
7 WORDTAG I-LOC JAKARTA
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Indonesian
7 WORDTAG O **
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Jakarta
12 WORDTAG O involving
5 WORDTAG O demonstrators
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Dow
14 WORDTAG O streak
6 WORDTAG O beating
14 WORDTAG O rupiah
42 WORDTAG O trading
23 WORDTAG O offer
5 WORDTAG O subsidiary
5 WORDTAG O loans
18 WORDTAG O management
10 WORDTAG O build
15 WORDTAG O property
5 WORDTAG O projects
18 WORDTAG O worth
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Surabaya
32 WORDTAG O stock
25 WORDTAG O change
5 WORDTAG O lows
6 WORDTAG O Also
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Japanese
27 WORDTAG O pound
26 WORDTAG O gold
7 WORDTAG O closes
6 WORDTAG O ....
20 WORDTAG O AND
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Nikkei
6 WORDTAG O Dec
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CAC-40
11 WORDTAG O marks
5 WORDTAG I-MISC post-Soviet
5 WORDTAG O effectively
8 WORDTAG O blow
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Soviet
17 WORDTAG O largest
8 WORDTAG O initially
7 WORDTAG O accompanied
7 WORDTAG O signs
24 WORDTAG O economy
7 WORDTAG O reforms
8 WORDTAG O doubt
9 WORDTAG O replace
14 WORDTAG O 33
7 WORDTAG O postpone
22 WORDTAG I-ORG NATO
29 WORDTAG O policy
22 WORDTAG O protest
6 WORDTAG O itself
21 WORDTAG O eastern
12 WORDTAG O strategic
14 WORDTAG O though
5 WORDTAG O push
5 WORDTAG O membership
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Western
5 WORDTAG O anniversary
6 WORDTAG O factor
6 WORDTAG O united
23 WORDTAG O complete
9 WORDTAG O example
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazeta
15 WORDTAG O published
7 WORDTAG O language
12 WORDTAG O barter
8 WORDTAG O concerned
7 WORDTAG I-PER Volkova
15 WORDTAG I-ORG State
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Committee
13 WORDTAG O issued
8 WORDTAG O decree
16 WORDTAG O situation
21 WORDTAG O traders
6 WORDTAG O 180
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Union
5 WORDTAG O preferred
8 WORDTAG O systems
7 WORDTAG O various
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Moscow
5 WORDTAG O +7095
5 WORDTAG O 941
5 WORDTAG O 8520
19 WORDTAG O release
9 WORDTAG O version
5 WORDTAG O TV
8 WORDTAG I-PER Brian
7 WORDTAG I-PER De
8 WORDTAG I-MISC the
5 WORDTAG O criticised
5 WORDTAG O batsman
10 WORDTAG O delay
8 WORDTAG O century
21 WORDTAG O rain
7 WORDTAG O improvement
12 WORDTAG O weather
10 WORDTAG O announce
16 WORDTAG O event
5 WORDTAG O unbeaten
5 WORDTAG O bowled
5 WORDTAG O MOTOR
7 WORDTAG I-MISC BELGIAN
9 WORDTAG I-MISC PRIX
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gerhard
6 WORDTAG I-PER Berger
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Benetton
92 WORDTAG O seconds
8 WORDTAG I-ORG McLaren
8 WORDTAG I-PER Jacques
5 WORDTAG I-PER Villeneuve
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Williams
8 WORDTAG I-PER Mika
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hakkinen
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jean
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alesi
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damon
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hill
8 WORDTAG I-PER Schumacher
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Jordan
7 WORDTAG O 11.
5 WORDTAG I-PER Herbert
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sauber
7 WORDTAG O 12.
5 WORDTAG I-PER Olivier
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ligier
5 WORDTAG O [
5 WORDTAG O ]
6 WORDTAG I-PER Karina
7 WORDTAG I-PER Habsudova
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Portsmouth
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Queens
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tranmere
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Grimsby
5 WORDTAG I-ORG East
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Stirling
7 WORDTAG I-PER Gooch
5 WORDTAG O 389
7 WORDTAG I-PER K.
7 WORDTAG O 83
5 WORDTAG O 181
7 WORDTAG O 109
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fairbrother
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pollock
11 WORDTAG O county
5 WORDTAG O returns
8 WORDTAG O 106
6 WORDTAG O 116
15 WORDTAG O wicket
5 WORDTAG O 1-106
5 WORDTAG O 4-95
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesbrough
35 WORDTAG I-MISC Italian
37 WORDTAG O seen
16 WORDTAG O forward
7 WORDTAG O fun
13 WORDTAG O foot
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Chelsea
26 WORDTAG O reached
8 WORDTAG O advanced
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Americans
24 WORDTAG O 2-6
6 WORDTAG O getting
7 WORDTAG O pretty
16 WORDTAG O things
7 WORDTAG O missed
16 WORDTAG O felt
9 WORDTAG O midnight
8 WORDTAG O person
5 WORDTAG O aggressive
7 WORDTAG O affected
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Tour
9 WORDTAG O hitting
19 WORDTAG O ball
23 WORDTAG O lot
7 WORDTAG O shots
15 WORDTAG O mostly
8 WORDTAG I-ORG RUGBY
8 WORDTAG I-ORG UNION
10 WORDTAG O SECOND
7 WORDTAG O check
11 WORDTAG O means
10 WORDTAG O speculation
5 WORDTAG O wing
14 WORDTAG O shortly
8 WORDTAG O seedings
11 WORDTAG O 15-10
6 WORDTAG O 15-9
18 WORDTAG I-PER Rubin
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tennis
22 WORDTAG O player
12 WORDTAG O moved
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mary
7 WORDTAG I-PER McGrath
19 WORDTAG O 47
7 WORDTAG O .531
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Detroit
5 WORDTAG O AS
6 WORDTAG O slam
17 WORDTAG O pair
19 WORDTAG I-PER Brady
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anderson
16 WORDTAG O walked
8 WORDTAG O none
26 WORDTAG O struck
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ken
6 WORDTAG I-PER Edgar
11 WORDTAG O advantage
5 WORDTAG O heading
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Boston
9 WORDTAG I-PER Roger
5 WORDTAG O pinch-hitter
6 WORDTAG O majors
6 WORDTAG O pitched
12 WORDTAG O 0-1
5 WORDTAG O apiece
13 WORDTAG O claimed
8 WORDTAG I-PER Thompson
8 WORDTAG O route
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erik
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fernandez
6 WORDTAG I-LOC LISBON
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sporting
7 WORDTAG I-PER Luis
14 WORDTAG O 3-1
12 WORDTAG O Although
5 WORDTAG O 35th
5 WORDTAG O restored
5 WORDTAG O 38th
5 WORDTAG O 57th
5 WORDTAG O reigning
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Porto
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Benfica
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Portuguese
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Pauli
8 WORDTAG O candidates
8 WORDTAG O produced
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Bundesliga
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Schalke
6 WORDTAG O 64th
5 WORDTAG O thanks
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hansa
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Rostock
12 WORDTAG O WORLD
10 WORDTAG O clocked
8 WORDTAG O SUMMARIES
6 WORDTAG O Summaries
13 WORDTAG I-MISC FRENCH
24 WORDTAG O LEAGUE
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Nancy
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Germain
9 WORDTAG O 15,000
8 WORDTAG I-PER Svetlana
8 WORDTAG I-PER Masterkova
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Zurich
16 WORDTAG O lap
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Mozambique
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mutola
7 WORDTAG O stadium
6 WORDTAG O pushed
8 WORDTAG O capacity
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Atlanta
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Games
8 WORDTAG O plus
5 WORDTAG O 100,000
22 WORDTAG O tabulated
5 WORDTAG O 129
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Trinidad
5 WORDTAG I-PER Cea
5 WORDTAG I-PER Barry
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dennis
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mitchell
9 WORDTAG O present
5 WORDTAG O bright
5 WORDTAG I-PER Donovan
10 WORDTAG I-PER Bailey
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linford
18 WORDTAG I-PER Christie
6 WORDTAG O 1988
5 WORDTAG O sport
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlanta
6 WORDTAG O bronze
6 WORDTAG O medallist
13 WORDTAG O hurdles
5 WORDTAG I-PER Allen
10 WORDTAG I-PER Colin
6 WORDTAG O seemed
10 WORDTAG O finish
6 WORDTAG O faster
7 WORDTAG O speed
9 WORDTAG O stepped
10 WORDTAG O crashed
6 WORDTAG I-PER Michelle
5 WORDTAG I-PER Freeman
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Cuban
5 WORDTAG I-PER Lopez
5 WORDTAG O Seven
8 WORDTAG O medal
5 WORDTAG O settle
5 WORDTAG O 11.00
7 WORDTAG I-MISC GRAND
5 WORDTAG I-PER Natalya
5 WORDTAG I-PER Irina
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Jamaica
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Cuba
8 WORDTAG I-PER Julie
10 WORDTAG I-PER Johan
31 WORDTAG I-LOC Kenya
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Nigeria
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jon
9 WORDTAG I-PER Sarah
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joseph
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Uganda
5 WORDTAG I-PER Frankie
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fredericks
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Namibia
18 WORDTAG I-PER Bob
9 WORDTAG O jump
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Burundi
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Rwanda
5 WORDTAG I-PER Anton
6 WORDTAG O UP
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventus
19 WORDTAG O member
7 WORDTAG O entire
11 WORDTAG O friendly
5 WORDTAG O nominated
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bremen
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jens
11 WORDTAG O however
18 WORDTAG O defender
7 WORDTAG O formally
19 WORDTAG O 'll
6 WORDTAG O themselves
5 WORDTAG I-PER Oliver
5 WORDTAG I-PER Klinsmann
7 WORDTAG O cup
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Legia
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Warsaw
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brugge
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SRI
5 WORDTAG I-LOC LANKA
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Sri
10 WORDTAG O guilty
6 WORDTAG O controversial
5 WORDTAG O excellent
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombo
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Lankan
15 WORDTAG O heavy
5 WORDTAG I-PER Healy
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Angolan
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Unita
9 WORDTAG O joint
15 WORDTAG O administration
7 WORDTAG O installed
7 WORDTAG O timetable
5 WORDTAG O sending
11 WORDTAG O estimates
6 WORDTAG O MON
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Gencor
16 WORDTAG O YR
8 WORDTAG O DIV
7 WORDTAG O N
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Group
5 WORDTAG O falls
6 WORDTAG O Shr
5 WORDTAG O shr
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bureau
5 WORDTAG O 416
21 WORDTAG O discuss
8 WORDTAG O fever
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gold
9 WORDTAG O junior
5 WORDTAG O changing
13 WORDTAG O hands
5 WORDTAG O developments
6 WORDTAG O formed
7 WORDTAG O newsdesk
14 WORDTAG O stake
19 WORDTAG I-LOC WASHINGTON
7 WORDTAG O 8.0
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Securities
9 WORDTAG O holding
5 WORDTAG O holds
5 WORDTAG O investments
14 WORDTAG O large
6 WORDTAG O reach
6 WORDTAG O allow
12 WORDTAG I-ORG American
6 WORDTAG O operate
5 WORDTAG O shift
12 WORDTAG O weekly
10 WORDTAG O add
11 WORDTAG O status
26 WORDTAG O services
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Mideast
6 WORDTAG I-ORG IOC
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Port
5 WORDTAG I-LOC St
19 WORDTAG O options
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Samsung
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Singapore
12 WORDTAG I-ORG LG
10 WORDTAG O worst
6 WORDTAG O Maybe
17 WORDTAG O your
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Arab
9 WORDTAG O field
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Taibe
5 WORDTAG O fields
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Arabs
5 WORDTAG O crowds
12 WORDTAG O thing
5 WORDTAG O promoted
5 WORDTAG I-PER Haj
5 WORDTAG I-PER Yihye
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Jerusalem
8 WORDTAG O treatment
9 WORDTAG O driving
7 WORDTAG O hearing
5 WORDTAG O load
5 WORDTAG O elsewhere
6 WORDTAG O mayor
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Liverpool
14 WORDTAG O C
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rapid
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Vienna
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Old
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Trafford
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Barcelona
10 WORDTAG O suspects
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Rwandan
51 WORDTAG O refugees
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Zaire
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Democracy
5 WORDTAG O blown
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Serb
8 WORDTAG O casualties
20 WORDTAG O find
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbs
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Yugoslav
12 WORDTAG O minority
6 WORDTAG O 200,000
7 WORDTAG O reserves
11 WORDTAG O assets
13 WORDTAG O crime
7 WORDTAG I-LOC WARSAW
8 WORDTAG O organised
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interior
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kohl
5 WORDTAG O sealed
5 WORDTAG O links
8 WORDTAG O materials
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Chechens
6 WORDTAG O fighters
18 WORDTAG O soldiers
10 WORDTAG O effective
6 WORDTAG O relatively
5 WORDTAG O roads
12 WORDTAG O soldier
7 WORDTAG O dark
8 WORDTAG O try
9 WORDTAG I-LOC BELGRADE
5 WORDTAG O aboard
9 WORDTAG O jet
12 WORDTAG O diplomats
10 WORDTAG O ends
10 WORDTAG O powers
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Indians
18 WORDTAG O presidential
5 WORDTAG O palace
14 WORDTAG O different
5 WORDTAG O sectors
8 WORDTAG O elected
5 WORDTAG O platform
22 WORDTAG O nation
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BRASILIA
23 WORDTAG O bid
8 WORDTAG O difficulties
10 WORDTAG O huge
7 WORDTAG O river
12 WORDTAG I-PER Tsang
8 WORDTAG I-PER Ali
10 WORDTAG O Deputy
7 WORDTAG O bread
11 WORDTAG O riots
12 WORDTAG O passed
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ibrahim
5 WORDTAG O spying
26 WORDTAG O comment
5 WORDTAG O assistant
8 WORDTAG O tension
12 WORDTAG O King
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Jordanian
6 WORDTAG O secure
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamist
15 WORDTAG O houses
11 WORDTAG O streets
7 WORDTAG O communist
7 WORDTAG O smaller
11 WORDTAG O clashes
7 WORDTAG O policies
6 WORDTAG O blame
15 WORDTAG O protests
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurd
8 WORDTAG I-LOC ANKARA
12 WORDTAG I-ORG PKK
5 WORDTAG O 12-year-old
8 WORDTAG O autonomy
9 WORDTAG I-PER Davies
5 WORDTAG O contacts
5 WORDTAG O pursue
8 WORDTAG O apparently
6 WORDTAG O intent
5 WORDTAG O sexual
16 WORDTAG O a.m.
20 WORDTAG O girls
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Virginia
16 WORDTAG O entered
5 WORDTAG O sexually
5 WORDTAG O detective
9 WORDTAG O allegedly
7 WORDTAG O stabbed
17 WORDTAG O once
7 WORDTAG O identified
12 WORDTAG I-ORG USDA
6 WORDTAG O monitoring
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dan
6 WORDTAG O corn
13 WORDTAG O purchase
25 WORDTAG O wheat
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Republican
8 WORDTAG O Gov
7 WORDTAG I-PER Weld
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Senate
6 WORDTAG O seat
5 WORDTAG O incumbent
37 WORDTAG O vote
7 WORDTAG O facing
9 WORDTAG O friend
7 WORDTAG O politics
5 WORDTAG O friends
8 WORDTAG O transport
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Dm
9 WORDTAG O 125
6 WORDTAG O inch
6 WORDTAG O mm
5 WORDTAG O showers
5 WORDTAG O isolated
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Corporation
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamil
6 WORDTAG O directed
6 WORDTAG O terrorism
8 WORDTAG O finance
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Liberation
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tamil
8 WORDTAG O king
5 WORDTAG O Premier
5 WORDTAG O giant
8 WORDTAG O neighbours
6 WORDTAG O distance
5 WORDTAG O Queen
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Post
8 WORDTAG O volatility
8 WORDTAG O falling
13 WORDTAG O trader
23 WORDTAG O low
6 WORDTAG O size
5 WORDTAG O perhaps
12 WORDTAG O You
6 WORDTAG O makers
10 WORDTAG O potential
6 WORDTAG O yield
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Goldman
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sachs
7 WORDTAG O warrants
7 WORDTAG O controls
9 WORDTAG I-MISC DEM
7 WORDTAG O X
11 WORDTAG O challenge
15 WORDTAG I-PER Diana
7 WORDTAG O Princess
7 WORDTAG O criminal
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stenning
5 WORDTAG O contest
7 WORDTAG O everything
15 WORDTAG O driver
6 WORDTAG O rider
6 WORDTAG O compensation
8 WORDTAG I-PER Charles
8 WORDTAG O remove
5 WORDTAG O asking
10 WORDTAG O spring
10 WORDTAG O effort
5 WORDTAG I-PER Necmettin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erbakan
10 WORDTAG O B
10 WORDTAG O Turnover
5 WORDTAG O listed
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Index
6 WORDTAG O editorial
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Zenith
21 WORDTAG O plant
5 WORDTAG O set-top
9 WORDTAG O boxes
8 WORDTAG O gets
6 WORDTAG O develop
9 WORDTAG O addition
7 WORDTAG O partners
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp.
7 WORDTAG I-ORG SBC
14 WORDTAG O join
10 WORDTAG O jobs
5 WORDTAG O profitable
5 WORDTAG O retail
13 WORDTAG I-ORG ,
7 WORDTAG O hundreds
9 WORDTAG O comes
12 WORDTAG O candidate
16 WORDTAG O running
5 WORDTAG O Many
6 WORDTAG O involves
5 WORDTAG O word
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Windows
12 WORDTAG I-MISC 95
7 WORDTAG I-LOC SEATTLE
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Microsoft
12 WORDTAG O computer
7 WORDTAG O fallen
12 WORDTAG O software
7 WORDTAG O launch
13 WORDTAG O lines
10 WORDTAG O customers
9 WORDTAG O dollars
16 WORDTAG O building
14 WORDTAG O impact
9 WORDTAG O lawsuit
7 WORDTAG O tied
6 WORDTAG O space
20 WORDTAG O products
8 WORDTAG O handling
6 WORDTAG O technical
9 WORDTAG O corporate
5 WORDTAG O adopted
5 WORDTAG O sweeping
9 WORDTAG O slow
5 WORDTAG O intercepted
5 WORDTAG O everyone
8 WORDTAG O hijacking
21 WORDTAG O hijackers
12 WORDTAG O hijacked
7 WORDTAG O commercial
12 WORDTAG O welfare
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Wisconsin
6 WORDTAG O administrative
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tommy
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Human
12 WORDTAG O reform
5 WORDTAG O acquire
5 WORDTAG O directly
6 WORDTAG O limits
30 WORDTAG O train
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Alaska
5 WORDTAG O boxcar
5 WORDTAG I-PER Phan
8 WORDTAG O agents
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Arkansas
6 WORDTAG O churches
6 WORDTAG O kms
6 WORDTAG O located
10 WORDTAG O investigating
8 WORDTAG O idea
9 WORDTAG O established
8 WORDTAG O scene
5 WORDTAG I-LOC St.
5 WORDTAG O surrounded
8 WORDTAG O cotton
9 WORDTAG O rural
6 WORDTAG O shared
7 WORDTAG O suspicion
6 WORDTAG I-PER Turner
12 WORDTAG O income
5 WORDTAG O short-term
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Calif.
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Systems
12 WORDTAG O 212
6 WORDTAG I-ORG PTT
9 WORDTAG O largely
10 WORDTAG O view
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ING
7 WORDTAG O continuing
6 WORDTAG O sound
13 WORDTAG O weaker
13 WORDTAG O bourse
8 WORDTAG O prospects
11 WORDTAG O first-half
5 WORDTAG O ordering
5 WORDTAG O Socialist
23 WORDTAG O poll
7 WORDTAG O wounds
5 WORDTAG O investigations
9 WORDTAG O H1
9 WORDTAG O Group
19 WORDTAG O traffic
5 WORDTAG O freight
5 WORDTAG O whales
5 WORDTAG O lions
7 WORDTAG O ca
6 WORDTAG O article
5 WORDTAG O model
11 WORDTAG O using
5 WORDTAG I-PER Howard
11 WORDTAG O warned
7 WORDTAG O sharp
12 WORDTAG O spending
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Toyota
29 WORDTAG O workers
6 WORDTAG O 2,000
8 WORDTAG O striking
8 WORDTAG O voted
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Melbourne
9 WORDTAG O assembly
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Niugini
6 WORDTAG O surge
18 WORDTAG O 38
10 WORDTAG O considering
21 WORDTAG O copper
10 WORDTAG O project
14 WORDTAG O students
5 WORDTAG O gathered
7 WORDTAG O staged
8 WORDTAG O violent
11 WORDTAG O university
12 WORDTAG I-LOC North
6 WORDTAG I-MISC S.
10 WORDTAG O intervention
6 WORDTAG O supporting
13 WORDTAG O nil
30 WORDTAG O 48
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Shanghai
5 WORDTAG O stockpile
8 WORDTAG O Just
5 WORDTAG O metal
6 WORDTAG I-ORG China
7 WORDTAG I-ORG CNIEC
10 WORDTAG O Traders
22 WORDTAG O tax
5 WORDTAG O otherwise
9 WORDTAG O spend
7 WORDTAG O moving
7 WORDTAG O exact
6 WORDTAG I-ORG LME
6 WORDTAG O behalf
20 WORDTAG O tonne
14 WORDTAG O secret
5 WORDTAG O owners
5 WORDTAG O posts
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Holdings
8 WORDTAG O construction
18 WORDTAG O exchange
8 WORDTAG O acquisition
6 WORDTAG O maker
9 WORDTAG O yuan
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Promodes
10 WORDTAG O decide
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Metro
7 WORDTAG O discussions
5 WORDTAG O 4221
5 WORDTAG O highlights
7 WORDTAG O fund
9 WORDTAG O council
7 WORDTAG O yesterday
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Merrill
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lynch
66 WORDTAG O 1996-08-24
18 WORDTAG O truck
9 WORDTAG O vehicle
5 WORDTAG O engine
7 WORDTAG O RALLYING
5 WORDTAG I-LOC JYVASKYLA
6 WORDTAG I-PER Juha
7 WORDTAG I-PER Kankkunen
10 WORDTAG O 37
13 WORDTAG O stages
11 WORDTAG I-MISC 1,000
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Lakes
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Rally
5 WORDTAG O prospect
6 WORDTAG I-PER Tommi
9 WORDTAG I-PER Makinen
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mitsubishi
5 WORDTAG O fined
5 WORDTAG O sports
5 WORDTAG O 6.5
5 WORDTAG O boss
5 WORDTAG O pace
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Spaniard
14 WORDTAG O kph
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ferrari
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eddie
5 WORDTAG O Add
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tyrrell
6 WORDTAG O 14.
9 WORDTAG O Did
6 WORDTAG O unnamed
12 WORDTAG O suspended
6 WORDTAG O suspension
7 WORDTAG O +1
8 WORDTAG O +3
6 WORDTAG I-MISC RUGBY
15 WORDTAG O rugby
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Bradford
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Wigan
12 WORDTAG O 78
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Helens
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Warrington
5 WORDTAG O 555
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Sheffield
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Oldham
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Leeds
5 WORDTAG O 398
8 WORDTAG O 325
6 WORDTAG O TITLE
8 WORDTAG O favour
8 WORDTAG O removed
14 WORDTAG I-PER Graham
6 WORDTAG O 88
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Notts
7 WORDTAG O successive
5 WORDTAG O follow
8 WORDTAG I-PER Darren
11 WORDTAG I-PER Gough
10 WORDTAG O 176
9 WORDTAG O Final
6 WORDTAG O Match
12 WORDTAG O abandoned
6 WORDTAG O 111
11 WORDTAG I-PER Irani
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Raith
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Dundee
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Aberdeen
19 WORDTAG O Division
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Queen
11 WORDTAG I-ORG South
9 WORDTAG I-ORG County
23 WORDTAG O Played
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Newcastle
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wednesday
14 WORDTAG I-PER Alan
6 WORDTAG O header
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tottenham
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gianluca
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Arsenal
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Wimbledon
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Bolton
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Norwich
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Charlton
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bromwich
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Crystal
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Palace
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ipswich
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Reading
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southend
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Birmingham
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Stoke
16 WORDTAG I-ORG City
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Swindon
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Vale
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wolverhampton
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Barnsley
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Huddersfield
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bristol
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackpool
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Preston
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rovers
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Swansea
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lincoln
7 WORDTAG I-ORG All
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Blacks
5 WORDTAG O tries
11 WORDTAG I-PER Wilson
6 WORDTAG O replacement
5 WORDTAG I-PER Preston
5 WORDTAG I-PER Zinzan
7 WORDTAG I-PER Brooke
11 WORDTAG I-PER Simon
11 WORDTAG I-ORG (
11 WORDTAG I-ORG )
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Partizan
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Spartak
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Krakow
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Odra
8 WORDTAG I-ORG GKS
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Lodz
5 WORDTAG O BASKETBALL
15 WORDTAG I-ORG San
6 WORDTAG I-MISC KOREAN
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Hyundai
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Haitai
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Hanwha
12 WORDTAG I-ORG OB
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Lotte
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Ssangbangwool
5 WORDTAG O .527
6 WORDTAG O .538
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Heerenveen
5 WORDTAG I-PER Veldman
8 WORDTAG O goalkeeper
5 WORDTAG O defenders
7 WORDTAG O strikers
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Groningen
8 WORDTAG O LEADING
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bastia
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Marseille
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Lille
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Monaco
9 WORDTAG I-PER Smicer
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Lens
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Guingamp
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Nantes
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nice
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rennes
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bordeaux
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Auxerre
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Metz
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Strasbourg
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Havre
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Caen
6 WORDTAG O 70th
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Lyon
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Montpellier
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cannes
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Graafschap
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Doetinchem
8 WORDTAG I-ORG RKC
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Waalwijk
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Willem
8 WORDTAG I-ORG II
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Tilburg
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Fortuna
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sittard
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Rotterdam
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Twente
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Enschede
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Vitesse
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Arnhem
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Utrecht
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Feyenoord
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Roda
7 WORDTAG I-ORG JC
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Kerkrade
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Volendam
8 WORDTAG I-ORG AZ
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Alkmaar
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bochum
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arminia
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bielefeld
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Moenchengladbach
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Karlsruhe
6 WORDTAG O 33rd
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Stuttgart
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Werder
8 WORDTAG I-ORG 1860
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Munich
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bayer
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Leverkusen
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Duesseldorf
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Freiburg
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Cologne
6 WORDTAG I-ORG VfB
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Bayern
6 WORDTAG I-ORG MSV
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Duisburg
19 WORDTAG I-ORG FC
15 WORDTAG I-ORG /
7 WORDTAG I-ORG SV
17 WORDTAG O one-day
12 WORDTAG I-PER Waugh
10 WORDTAG I-PER Tendulkar
5 WORDTAG I-PER Frederic
13 WORDTAG O ransom
5 WORDTAG O tanks
6 WORDTAG O civilians
12 WORDTAG O whom
17 WORDTAG O spokeswoman
14 WORDTAG O role
5 WORDTAG I-PER Prince
5 WORDTAG O Doctors
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Saudi
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Arabia
9 WORDTAG O About
5 WORDTAG O climb
5 WORDTAG O racing
6 WORDTAG O mountain
5 WORDTAG O walking
11 WORDTAG O servants
12 WORDTAG O dismissed
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Labour
8 WORDTAG O firms
5 WORDTAG O demands
7 WORDTAG O wage
5 WORDTAG O Opposition
9 WORDTAG O unions
9 WORDTAG O inflation
5 WORDTAG O camps
5 WORDTAG O genocide
10 WORDTAG O fear
9 WORDTAG O counterpart
8 WORDTAG O skull
6 WORDTAG I-LOC S.
6 WORDTAG O scientist
7 WORDTAG O forest
6 WORDTAG O arrests
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Eritrea
10 WORDTAG O alliance
6 WORDTAG O accuses
5 WORDTAG O accusing
5 WORDTAG O congress
11 WORDTAG O turn
18 WORDTAG O electoral
7 WORDTAG O class
7 WORDTAG O stance
6 WORDTAG O consensus
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Nicaraguan
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Nicaragua
6 WORDTAG I-PER Chamorro
7 WORDTAG O column
6 WORDTAG O wo
6 WORDTAG O split
6 WORDTAG O widespread
7 WORDTAG O activists
5 WORDTAG O communications
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Revolutionary
12 WORDTAG O site
9 WORDTAG O executed
6 WORDTAG O lb
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Movement
8 WORDTAG I-ORG MDS
5 WORDTAG O sentences
7 WORDTAG O judicial
5 WORDTAG O withdrew
7 WORDTAG O camp
13 WORDTAG O west
5 WORDTAG O independent
12 WORDTAG O allegations
7 WORDTAG O grenades
5 WORDTAG O intends
8 WORDTAG O gathering
44 WORDTAG I-PER Dole
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Congress
15 WORDTAG O sex
8 WORDTAG O offers
37 WORDTAG O again
6 WORDTAG O heads
10 WORDTAG O drive
7 WORDTAG O happen
12 WORDTAG I-LOC White
13 WORDTAG I-LOC House
14 WORDTAG O bill
5 WORDTAG O remarkable
5 WORDTAG O offering
17 WORDTAG O demanding
12 WORDTAG O stronger
6 WORDTAG O families
9 WORDTAG O fellow
6 WORDTAG O attention
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Edouard
5 WORDTAG O winds
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ETA
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Basque
8 WORDTAG O mandate
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bossi
6 WORDTAG O ancient
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Corsica
8 WORDTAG O talking
5 WORDTAG I-ORG League
11 WORDTAG O bodies
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stevanin
13 WORDTAG O unable
13 WORDTAG O investigators
5 WORDTAG O paedophile
11 WORDTAG O scandal
7 WORDTAG O kidnapping
9 WORDTAG O throughout
36 WORDTAG I-PER Dutroux
12 WORDTAG O managed
12 WORDTAG O freed
6 WORDTAG O abduction
5 WORDTAG O imprisonment
8 WORDTAG I-PER Bourlet
6 WORDTAG I-PER Melissa
15 WORDTAG O kidnapped
6 WORDTAG I-PER An
6 WORDTAG I-PER Eefje
8 WORDTAG O unknown
5 WORDTAG O Five
5 WORDTAG O Among
13 WORDTAG O information
7 WORDTAG O theft
8 WORDTAG O accepted
7 WORDTAG O hear
5 WORDTAG O inquiry
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rights
5 WORDTAG O cannabis
6 WORDTAG O 7.5
5 WORDTAG O container
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MADRID
5 WORDTAG O supported
6 WORDTAG O neither
7 WORDTAG O margin
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Pakistani
8 WORDTAG O inches
9 WORDTAG O rail
10 WORDTAG O witnesses
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Internet
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Startup
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Java
85 WORDTAG O 1996-08-25
5 WORDTAG I-ORG JavaSoft
7 WORDTAG O venture
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Park
6 WORDTAG O acting
6 WORDTAG O experience
5 WORDTAG O aims
9 WORDTAG O individual
7 WORDTAG O marketing
10 WORDTAG O WINS
5 WORDTAG O style
6 WORDTAG O easy
11 WORDTAG O feet
5 WORDTAG O 12th
12 WORDTAG O defending
28 WORDTAG O 6-0
5 WORDTAG I-MISC LAKES
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Toyota
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Celica
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Ford
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Escort
7 WORDTAG I-PER Eriksson
12 WORDTAG O First
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Honda
6 WORDTAG I-PER King
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Kawasaki
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Yamaha
6 WORDTAG O placings
5 WORDTAG I-MISC McLaren
5 WORDTAG I-MISC GTR
5 WORDTAG O laps
6 WORDTAG O 170
5 WORDTAG I-MISC F
5 WORDTAG O Fastest
5 WORDTAG O drivers
9 WORDTAG I-PER Takeda
9 WORDTAG I-PER Haga
7 WORDTAG I-PER Yoshikawa
10 WORDTAG I-PER Corser
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Ducati
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kocinski
8 WORDTAG I-PER Slight
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fogarty
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aoki
8 WORDTAG O names
5 WORDTAG O strongly
5 WORDTAG O riders
8 WORDTAG O reaching
7 WORDTAG O 521-8
7 WORDTAG O PREMIER
5 WORDTAG O 87
6 WORDTAG O mate
6 WORDTAG O forcing
5 WORDTAG O ONE-DAY
5 WORDTAG I-PER Headley
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Togo
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Nations
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BUCHAREST
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Bucharest
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Dinamo
15 WORDTAG O 49
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Melbourne
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Brisbane
14 WORDTAG I-ORG North
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Queensland
6 WORDTAG O 10-15
5 WORDTAG O .470
6 WORDTAG O reliever
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Seattle
12 WORDTAG O contact
6 WORDTAG O acquired
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Minnesota
12 WORDTAG O 6-5
6 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neill
7 WORDTAG I-ORG St.
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Cardinals
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Diego
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Padres
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlanta
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Braves
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cubs
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Colorado
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Colorado
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Pirates
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Marlins
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Los
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Angeles
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dodgers
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Diego
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Phillies
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Expos
8 WORDTAG O shut
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Francisco
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Giants
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Houston
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Astros
5 WORDTAG I-PER Shane
7 WORDTAG O equaliser
11 WORDTAG O lack
7 WORDTAG O knee
6 WORDTAG I-PER Batistuta
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Fiorentina
6 WORDTAG I-MISC serie
7 WORDTAG I-MISC A
5 WORDTAG O 83rd
6 WORDTAG I-MISC ITALIAN
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Norwegian
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Neuchatel
7 WORDTAG I-MISC TOUR
5 WORDTAG I-PER Montgomerie
14 WORDTAG O CYCLING
9 WORDTAG O cycling
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ferrigato
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lance
10 WORDTAG I-PER Armstrong
5 WORDTAG O narrow
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Briton
11 WORDTAG O 199
7 WORDTAG I-PER Baker
6 WORDTAG O FROM
9 WORDTAG I-PER Ronald
5 WORDTAG I-PER Arnold
5 WORDTAG I-PER Blind
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Press
5 WORDTAG I-PER Azharuddin
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Singer
111 WORDTAG O 1996-08-26
7 WORDTAG O choice
5 WORDTAG O riding
8 WORDTAG I-MISC New
6 WORDTAG O supporters
10 WORDTAG O apartheid
18 WORDTAG O commission
5 WORDTAG O paint
6 WORDTAG O amnesty
5 WORDTAG O tell
7 WORDTAG O abuses
5 WORDTAG O achieve
5 WORDTAG O 1948
6 WORDTAG O express
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Doboj
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslems
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Dayton
7 WORDTAG O refugee
5 WORDTAG O thrown
5 WORDTAG O warning
5 WORDTAG O pullout
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Mexican
6 WORDTAG I-LOC MEXICO
6 WORDTAG O leftist
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Army
6 WORDTAG I-ORG EPR
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Guerrero
5 WORDTAG O Commander
6 WORDTAG O protesters
5 WORDTAG O northwest
6 WORDTAG O dragged
7 WORDTAG O linking
5 WORDTAG O allied
9 WORDTAG O supplies
7 WORDTAG O reveal
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kingdom
7 WORDTAG O finding
12 WORDTAG O democracy
7 WORDTAG I-PER Kabariti
11 WORDTAG O speaker
15 WORDTAG I-PER Weizman
13 WORDTAG O speak
7 WORDTAG O Earlier
5 WORDTAG O cool
6 WORDTAG O education
5 WORDTAG O establish
14 WORDTAG O parliamentary
16 WORDTAG O voters
7 WORDTAG O thin
5 WORDTAG O stations
10 WORDTAG O employee
5 WORDTAG O skilled
6 WORDTAG O contribute
6 WORDTAG I-PER Sandra
8 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neal
7 WORDTAG O customer
7 WORDTAG O agenda
7 WORDTAG O ask
5 WORDTAG O rated
7 WORDTAG O decisions
9 WORDTAG O insurance
10 WORDTAG O fraud
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Salang
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Supreme
5 WORDTAG O postponement
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Central
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hasina
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bogra
13 WORDTAG O ruling
5 WORDTAG O Nearly
6 WORDTAG O drought
7 WORDTAG O regions
5 WORDTAG O diesel
12 WORDTAG O grain
21 WORDTAG O sector
7 WORDTAG O transition
6 WORDTAG O reputation
5 WORDTAG O dictator
7 WORDTAG O quality
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Wheat
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Institute
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Celsius
6 WORDTAG O rainfall
5 WORDTAG O farms
5 WORDTAG O acres
5 WORDTAG O 220
5 WORDTAG O badly
5 WORDTAG O autumn
8 WORDTAG O negative
5 WORDTAG O attributable
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbertson
8 WORDTAG O rand
5 WORDTAG O substantial
5 WORDTAG O shutdown
7 WORDTAG O rains
8 WORDTAG O merger
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Plc
5 WORDTAG O portfolio
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Advanced
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Medical
11 WORDTAG I-ORG IVAC
8 WORDTAG O infusion
5 WORDTAG O therapy
5 WORDTAG I-ORG IMED
7 WORDTAG O plants
7 WORDTAG O 120
6 WORDTAG O expects
13 WORDTAG O delivery
6 WORDTAG O boosted
33 WORDTAG O bonds
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Treasury
7 WORDTAG O secured
6 WORDTAG O hat-trick
5 WORDTAG O decisive
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sharpe
7 WORDTAG I-PER Botham
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesex
15 WORDTAG I-PER Morris
5 WORDTAG O BY
5 WORDTAG O FRIENDLY
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Costa
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Rica
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Mauritius
10 WORDTAG O crude
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gabon
5 WORDTAG O legs
8 WORDTAG O postponed
5 WORDTAG O swimming
7 WORDTAG I-PER Popov
5 WORDTAG O titles
5 WORDTAG O medicine
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympics
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Slovak
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Hungarian
6 WORDTAG I-ORG SK
6 WORDTAG I-ORG America
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Santos
7 WORDTAG O catch
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sao
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Paulo
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Sao
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Paulo
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Rio
8 WORDTAG I-LOC de
5 WORDTAG O usual
7 WORDTAG O hot
8 WORDTAG I-PER Perry
5 WORDTAG I-PER Larry
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magdalena
8 WORDTAG I-PER Maleeva
9 WORDTAG O cement
11 WORDTAG O tough
9 WORDTAG I-PER Olsza
7 WORDTAG I-PER Barbara
6 WORDTAG O ranking
6 WORDTAG O mind
7 WORDTAG O original
5 WORDTAG O MONDAY
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephanie
10 WORDTAG I-PER Oncins
13 WORDTAG O 6-
5 WORDTAG I-PER Elena
6 WORDTAG O 3-2
5 WORDTAG O .466
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bonds
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sosa
5 WORDTAG I-PER Boer
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Madrid
5 WORDTAG I-LOC ZIMBABWE
5 WORDTAG I-PER Strang
6 WORDTAG I-PER Whittall
5 WORDTAG I-PER Brandes
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hogg
5 WORDTAG I-PER Reiffel
5 WORDTAG I-PER Flower
14 WORDTAG O filed
10 WORDTAG O existing
6 WORDTAG O ferry
5 WORDTAG O boats
18 WORDTAG O voting
21 WORDTAG O municipal
6 WORDTAG O irregularities
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Election
7 WORDTAG O consider
5 WORDTAG O 600,000
7 WORDTAG O Ambassador
5 WORDTAG O cast
9 WORDTAG O ballot
5 WORDTAG O voter
10 WORDTAG O appointed
5 WORDTAG O compromise
21 WORDTAG O settlement
5 WORDTAG O insistence
6 WORDTAG O quit
5 WORDTAG O recover
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Zastava
5 WORDTAG O factory
6 WORDTAG O wages
5 WORDTAG O settlements
5 WORDTAG O 5.5
8 WORDTAG O controllers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Raichev
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tass
5 WORDTAG O eye
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mostostal
11 WORDTAG O premium
5 WORDTAG O 2.6
5 WORDTAG I-LOC JOSE
6 WORDTAG O kidnappers
6 WORDTAG O tourist
5 WORDTAG O photographs
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Rican
10 WORDTAG O peso
6 WORDTAG O limit
10 WORDTAG O Dealers
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hashimoto
7 WORDTAG I-ORG de
6 WORDTAG O credit
6 WORDTAG O auctions
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Auckland
8 WORDTAG O gunman
121 WORDTAG O 1996-08-27
12 WORDTAG O gun
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Singapore
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Petroleum
7 WORDTAG O contracts
6 WORDTAG O Spot
7 WORDTAG O liquidity
6 WORDTAG O deposed
5 WORDTAG I-PER Specter
8 WORDTAG O resign
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Sudan
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Airways
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Airbus
6 WORDTAG O surrender
7 WORDTAG O asylum
5 WORDTAG O dozens
8 WORDTAG O grade
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Midwest
14 WORDTAG O 6.0
5 WORDTAG O 859
5 WORDTAG O tree
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Office
5 WORDTAG O bounce
5 WORDTAG O fairly
7 WORDTAG O hog
6 WORDTAG O sparked
15 WORDTAG I-PER Gore
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gingrich
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Convention
5 WORDTAG O re-election
20 WORDTAG O coalition
7 WORDTAG O justice
5 WORDTAG O painted
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Republicans
5 WORDTAG O praised
7 WORDTAG I-PER Reeve
9 WORDTAG O politicians
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gephardt
9 WORDTAG I-PER Reagan
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Republican
6 WORDTAG O legislature
8 WORDTAG O abortion
9 WORDTAG O nomination
7 WORDTAG O gas
5 WORDTAG O handgun
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Karachi
8 WORDTAG O fob
5 WORDTAG O ARA
6 WORDTAG O sentiment
6 WORDTAG O bids
5 WORDTAG O frost
10 WORDTAG O 4.0
12 WORDTAG O 5.0
7 WORDTAG O moisture
6 WORDTAG O 32.0
8 WORDTAG O 12.0
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brush
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Wellman
5 WORDTAG O suits
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Salomon
8 WORDTAG O margins
7 WORDTAG O versus
5 WORDTAG O CALL
5 WORDTAG O CONFIRMED
6 WORDTAG I-PER Chelsea
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Wall
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Street
8 WORDTAG I-PER Tapie
5 WORDTAG O instructions
5 WORDTAG O procedure
19 WORDTAG O francs
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Rabobank
10 WORDTAG O epidemic
13 WORDTAG O debate
13 WORDTAG I-PER Banharn
5 WORDTAG O fix
13 WORDTAG O unq
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ekeus
5 WORDTAG I-ORG THE
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamils
5 WORDTAG I-ORG LTTE
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tankan
6 WORDTAG O franc
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqis
5 WORDTAG O diverted
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Stansted
7 WORDTAG O explosives
5 WORDTAG O larger
7 WORDTAG O festival
6 WORDTAG I-PER Thomson
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ata-ur-Rehman
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cozma
11 WORDTAG O lei
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bucharest
5 WORDTAG O tunnel
7 WORDTAG O 12-15
5 WORDTAG O TUESDAY
6 WORDTAG O 85th
6 WORDTAG I-PER Cyprien
6 WORDTAG I-PER Moura
5 WORDTAG O STAGE
5 WORDTAG I-MISC NETHERLANDS
6 WORDTAG O kilometre
