31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blackburn
16 WORDTAG I-LOC BRUSSELS
125 WORDTAG O 1996-08-22
1093 WORDTAG O The
31 WORDTAG I-ORG European
45 WORDTAG I-ORG Commission
1846 WORDTAG O said
2036 WORDTAG O on
285 WORDTAG O Thursday
553 WORDTAG O it
2 WORDTAG O disagreed
840 WORDTAG O with
5 WORDTAG O advice
9 WORDTAG O consumers
1 WORDTAG O shun
53 WORDTAG O until
6 WORDTAG O scientists
11 WORDTAG O determine
45 WORDTAG O whether
13 WORDTAG O mad
12 WORDTAG O cow
35 WORDTAG O disease
71 WORDTAG O can
525 WORDTAG O be
2 WORDTAG O transmitted
12 WORDTAG O sheep
142 WORDTAG I-LOC Germany
1496 WORDTAG O 's
7 WORDTAG O representative
7221 WORDTAG O the
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
8 WORDTAG O veterinary
22 WORDTAG O committee
2 WORDTAG I-PER Werner
2 WORDTAG I-PER Zwingmann
255 WORDTAG O Wednesday
78 WORDTAG O should
26 WORDTAG O buy
2 WORDTAG O sheepmeat
757 WORDTAG O from
42 WORDTAG O countries
132 WORDTAG O other
144 WORDTAG O than
133 WORDTAG I-LOC Britain
9 WORDTAG O scientific
1095 WORDTAG O was
1 WORDTAG O clearer
2178 WORDTAG O "
137 WORDTAG O We
106 WORDTAG O do
97 WORDTAG O n't
61 WORDTAG O support
92 WORDTAG O any
40 WORDTAG O such
3 WORDTAG O recommendation
114 WORDTAG O because
163 WORDTAG O we
28 WORDTAG O see
6 WORDTAG O grounds
1406 WORDTAG O for
7275 WORDTAG O ,
50 WORDTAG O chief
106 WORDTAG O spokesman
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nikolaus
17 WORDTAG I-PER van
9 WORDTAG I-PER der
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pas
199 WORDTAG O told
2994 WORDTAG O a
85 WORDTAG O news
6 WORDTAG O briefing
209 WORDTAG O He
32 WORDTAG O further
10 WORDTAG O study
8 WORDTAG O required
2789 WORDTAG O and
98 WORDTAG O if
62 WORDTAG O found
767 WORDTAG O that
29 WORDTAG O action
24 WORDTAG O needed
41 WORDTAG O taken
716 WORDTAG O by
10 WORDTAG O proposal
282 WORDTAG O last
89 WORDTAG O month
3 WORDTAG O Farm
7 WORDTAG O Commissioner
4 WORDTAG I-PER Franz
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fischler
36 WORDTAG O ban
2 WORDTAG O brains
2 WORDTAG O spleens
5 WORDTAG O spinal
2 WORDTAG O cords
29 WORDTAG O human
8 WORDTAG O animal
21 WORDTAG O food
6 WORDTAG O chains
6 WORDTAG O highly
7 WORDTAG O specific
1 WORDTAG O precautionary
18 WORDTAG O move
4 WORDTAG O protect
25 WORDTAG O health
15 WORDTAG O proposed
1 WORDTAG I-MISC EU-wide
16 WORDTAG O measures
471 WORDTAG O after
32 WORDTAG O reports
122 WORDTAG I-LOC France
159 WORDTAG O under
3 WORDTAG O laboratory
25 WORDTAG O conditions
143 WORDTAG O could
29 WORDTAG O contract
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Bovine
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Spongiform
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Encephalopathy
2846 WORDTAG O (
11 WORDTAG I-MISC BSE
2846 WORDTAG O )
356 WORDTAG O --
155 WORDTAG O But
53 WORDTAG O agreed
7 WORDTAG O review
538 WORDTAG O his
9 WORDTAG O standing
1 WORDTAG O mational
124 WORDTAG O officials
12 WORDTAG O questioned
4 WORDTAG O justified
602 WORDTAG O as
122 WORDTAG O there
125 WORDTAG O only
6 WORDTAG O slight
19 WORDTAG O risk
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Spanish
121 WORDTAG O Minister
1 WORDTAG I-PER Loyola
26 WORDTAG I-PER de
1 WORDTAG I-PER Palacio
561 WORDTAG O had
83 WORDTAG O earlier
38 WORDTAG O accused
930 WORDTAG O at
507 WORDTAG O an
17 WORDTAG O farm
14 WORDTAG O ministers
131 WORDTAG O '
86 WORDTAG O meeting
3617 WORDTAG O of
4 WORDTAG O causing
1 WORDTAG O unjustified
3 WORDTAG O alarm
105 WORDTAG O through
13 WORDTAG O dangerous
1 WORDTAG O generalisation
5 WORDTAG O Only
7 WORDTAG O backed
1 WORDTAG O multidisciplinary
2 WORDTAG O committees
346 WORDTAG O are
74 WORDTAG O due
2 WORDTAG O re-examine
56 WORDTAG O issue
75 WORDTAG O early
110 WORDTAG O next
57 WORDTAG O make
2 WORDTAG O recommendations
26 WORDTAG O senior
2 WORDTAG O Sheep
501 WORDTAG O have
35 WORDTAG O long
368 WORDTAG O been
31 WORDTAG O known
2 WORDTAG O scrapie
3 WORDTAG O brain-wasting
23 WORDTAG O similar
330 WORDTAG O which
689 WORDTAG O is
28 WORDTAG O believed
3 WORDTAG O transferred
12 WORDTAG O cattle
18 WORDTAG O feed
5 WORDTAG O containing
7 WORDTAG O waste
19 WORDTAG O farmers
24 WORDTAG O denied
10 WORDTAG O danger
346 WORDTAG O their
389 WORDTAG O but
11 WORDTAG O expressed
17 WORDTAG O concern
258 WORDTAG O government
15 WORDTAG O avoid
36 WORDTAG O might
4 WORDTAG O influence
34 WORDTAG O across
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Europe
12 WORDTAG O What
8 WORDTAG O extremely
1 WORDTAG O careful
28 WORDTAG O how
52 WORDTAG O going
80 WORDTAG O take
75 WORDTAG O lead
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Welsh
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Farmers
3 WORDTAG I-ORG '
1 WORDTAG I-ORG NFU
27 WORDTAG O chairman
50 WORDTAG I-PER John
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lloyd
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jones
2 WORDTAG I-ORG BBC
2 WORDTAG I-ORG radio
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bonn
557 WORDTAG O has
37 WORDTAG O led
15 WORDTAG O efforts
33 WORDTAG O public
15 WORDTAG O consumer
10 WORDTAG O confidence
3 WORDTAG O collapsed
3390 WORDTAG O in
36 WORDTAG O March
54 WORDTAG O report
4 WORDTAG O suggested
3 WORDTAG O humans
7 WORDTAG O illness
8 WORDTAG O eating
2 WORDTAG O contaminated
10 WORDTAG O beef
5 WORDTAG O imported
2 WORDTAG O 47,600
293 WORDTAG O year
27 WORDTAG O nearly
84 WORDTAG O half
38 WORDTAG O total
13 WORDTAG O imports
207 WORDTAG O It
31 WORDTAG O brought
2 WORDTAG O 4,275
82 WORDTAG O tonnes
3 WORDTAG O mutton
157 WORDTAG O some
197 WORDTAG O 10
303 WORDTAG O percent
20 WORDTAG O overall
1 WORDTAG O Rare
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hendrix
2 WORDTAG O song
11 WORDTAG O draft
4 WORDTAG O sells
14 WORDTAG O almost
362 WORDTAG O $
2 WORDTAG O 17,000
93 WORDTAG I-LOC LONDON
198 WORDTAG O A
8 WORDTAG O rare
1 WORDTAG O handwritten
309 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S.
2 WORDTAG O guitar
1 WORDTAG O legend
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jimi
28 WORDTAG O sold
14 WORDTAG O auction
53 WORDTAG O late
1 WORDTAG O musician
3 WORDTAG O favourite
1 WORDTAG O possessions
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Florida
7 WORDTAG O restaurant
18 WORDTAG O paid
1 WORDTAG O 10,925
23 WORDTAG O pounds
1 WORDTAG O 16,935
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Ai
1 WORDTAG I-MISC n't
1 WORDTAG I-MISC no
1 WORDTAG I-MISC telling
1 WORDTAG O penned
5 WORDTAG O piece
61 WORDTAG I-LOC London
10 WORDTAG O hotel
2 WORDTAG O stationery
3 WORDTAG O 1966
84 WORDTAG O At
74 WORDTAG O end
20 WORDTAG O January
4 WORDTAG O 1967
3 WORDTAG O concert
42 WORDTAG I-MISC English
55 WORDTAG O city
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Nottingham
582 WORDTAG O he
10 WORDTAG O threw
5 WORDTAG O sheet
24 WORDTAG O paper
160 WORDTAG O into
5 WORDTAG O audience
100 WORDTAG O where
1 WORDTAG O retrieved
3 WORDTAG O fan
2 WORDTAG O Buyers
214 WORDTAG O also
14 WORDTAG O snapped
314 WORDTAG O up
55 WORDTAG O 16
7 WORDTAG O items
531 WORDTAG O were
58 WORDTAG O put
109 WORDTAG O former
3 WORDTAG O girlfriend
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kathy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Etchingham
439 WORDTAG O who
8 WORDTAG O lived
111 WORDTAG O him
2 WORDTAG O 1969
86 WORDTAG O They
20 WORDTAG O included
21 WORDTAG O black
1 WORDTAG O lacquer
11 WORDTAG O mother
1 WORDTAG O pearl
1 WORDTAG O inlaid
6 WORDTAG O box
31 WORDTAG O used
7 WORDTAG O store
21 WORDTAG O drugs
3 WORDTAG O anonymous
52 WORDTAG I-MISC Australian
1 WORDTAG O purchaser
19 WORDTAG O bought
1 WORDTAG O 5,060
1 WORDTAG O 7,845
1 WORDTAG O guitarist
37 WORDTAG O died
1 WORDTAG O overdose
2 WORDTAG O 1970
8 WORDTAG O aged
37 WORDTAG O 27
91 WORDTAG I-LOC China
66 WORDTAG O says
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Taiwan
1 WORDTAG O spoils
6 WORDTAG O atmosphere
83 WORDTAG O talks
9 WORDTAG I-LOC BEIJING
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Taipei
2 WORDTAG O spoiling
2 WORDTAG O resumption
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Strait
68 WORDTAG O visit
39 WORDTAG I-LOC Ukraine
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Taiwanese
3 WORDTAG O Vice
109 WORDTAG O President
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lien
2 WORDTAG I-PER Chan
284 WORDTAG O this
147 WORDTAG O week
3 WORDTAG O infuriated
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Beijing
2 WORDTAG O Speaking
45 WORDTAG O hours
25 WORDTAG I-MISC Chinese
127 WORDTAG O state
16 WORDTAG O media
144 WORDTAG O time
36 WORDTAG O right
2 WORDTAG O engage
71 WORDTAG O political
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Foreign
29 WORDTAG I-ORG Ministry
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Guofang
79 WORDTAG I-ORG Reuters
687 WORDTAG O :
10 WORDTAG O necessary
31 WORDTAG O opening
4 WORDTAG O disrupted
46 WORDTAG O authorities
15 WORDTAG O State
49 WORDTAG O quoted
52 WORDTAG O top
5 WORDTAG O negotiator
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tang
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shubei
5 WORDTAG O telling
9 WORDTAG O visiting
124 WORDTAG O group
8 WORDTAG O rivals
37 WORDTAG O hold
8 WORDTAG O Now
349 WORDTAG O two
19 WORDTAG O sides
44 WORDTAG O ...
3 WORDTAG O hostility
7 WORDTAG O overseas
5 WORDTAG O edition
5 WORDTAG I-ORG People
34 WORDTAG I-ORG 's
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Daily
74 WORDTAG O saying
72 WORDTAG O foreign
37 WORDTAG O ministry
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Shen
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Television
13 WORDTAG O interview
10 WORDTAG O read
8 WORDTAG O comments
56 WORDTAG O gave
164 WORDTAG O no
30 WORDTAG O details
10 WORDTAG O why
11 WORDTAG O considered
1 WORDTAG O considers
6 WORDTAG O renegade
22 WORDTAG O province
11 WORDTAG O opposed
128 WORDTAG O all
6 WORDTAG O gain
4 WORDTAG O greater
71 WORDTAG O international
3 WORDTAG O recognition
18 WORDTAG O rival
25 WORDTAG O island
3 WORDTAG O practical
3 WORDTAG O steps
15 WORDTAG O towards
24 WORDTAG O goal
1 WORDTAG O Consultations
80 WORDTAG O held
83 WORDTAG O set
1 WORDTAG O format
109 WORDTAG O official
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Xinhua
52 WORDTAG O agency
23 WORDTAG O executive
10 WORDTAG O vice
24 WORDTAG I-ORG Association
14 WORDTAG I-ORG for
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Relations
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Across
10 WORDTAG I-ORG the
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Taiwan
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Straits
99 WORDTAG O July
19 WORDTAG O car
9 WORDTAG O registrations
2 WORDTAG O 14.2
56 WORDTAG O pct
13 WORDTAG O yr
220 WORDTAG O /
5 WORDTAG I-LOC FRANKFURT
1 WORDTAG O first-time
7 WORDTAG O motor
9 WORDTAG O vehicles
3 WORDTAG O jumped
2 WORDTAG O year-earlier
35 WORDTAG O period
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Federal
2 WORDTAG I-ORG office
1 WORDTAG I-ORG motor
1 WORDTAG I-ORG vehicles
48 WORDTAG O office
1 WORDTAG O 356,725
199 WORDTAG O new
10 WORDTAG O cars
9 WORDTAG O registered
121 WORDTAG O 1996
1 WORDTAG O 304,850
16 WORDTAG O passenger
1 WORDTAG O 15,613
4 WORDTAG O trucks
29 WORDTAG O figures
4 WORDTAG O represent
1 WORDTAG O 13.6
22 WORDTAG O increase
3 WORDTAG O 2.2
6 WORDTAG O decline
63 WORDTAG O 1995
1 WORDTAG O Motor-bike
11 WORDTAG O registration
33 WORDTAG O rose
1 WORDTAG O 32.7
39 WORDTAG O growth
5 WORDTAG O partly
19 WORDTAG O increased
75 WORDTAG O number
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Germans
13 WORDTAG O buying
14 WORDTAG O abroad
92 WORDTAG O while
6 WORDTAG O manufacturers
20 WORDTAG O domestic
49 WORDTAG O demand
9 WORDTAG O weak
21 WORDTAG O federal
3 WORDTAG O Almost
11 WORDTAG O posted
17 WORDTAG O gains
13 WORDTAG O numbers
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Volkswagen
14 WORDTAG I-ORG AG
163 WORDTAG O won
1 WORDTAG O 77,719
15 WORDTAG O slightly
154 WORDTAG O more
42 WORDTAG O quarter
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Opel
9 WORDTAG O together
5 WORDTAG I-ORG General
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Motors
45 WORDTAG O came
216 WORDTAG O second
50 WORDTAG O place
1 WORDTAG O 49,269
1 WORDTAG O 16.4
15 WORDTAG O figure
7 WORDTAG O Third
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Ford
1 WORDTAG O 35,563
186 WORDTAG O or
2 WORDTAG O 11.7
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Seat
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Porsche
5 WORDTAG O fewer
23 WORDTAG O compared
1 WORDTAG O 3,420
1 WORDTAG O 5522
46 WORDTAG O fell
1 WORDTAG O 554
1 WORDTAG O 643
1 WORDTAG I-MISC GREEK
1 WORDTAG O SOCIALISTS
1 WORDTAG O GIVE
1 WORDTAG O GREEN
1 WORDTAG O LIGHT
27 WORDTAG O TO
7 WORDTAG O PM
25 WORDTAG O FOR
1 WORDTAG O ELECTIONS
10 WORDTAG I-LOC ATHENS
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Greek
3 WORDTAG O socialist
76 WORDTAG O party
5 WORDTAG O bureau
5 WORDTAG O green
15 WORDTAG O light
56 WORDTAG O Prime
9 WORDTAG I-PER Costas
8 WORDTAG I-PER Simitis
8 WORDTAG O snap
77 WORDTAG O elections
306 WORDTAG O its
44 WORDTAG O general
18 WORDTAG O secretary
4 WORDTAG I-PER Skandalidis
45 WORDTAG O reporters
14 WORDTAG O announcement
17 WORDTAG O cabinet
46 WORDTAG O later
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitris
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kontogiannis
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Athens
70 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsroom
7 WORDTAG O +301
7 WORDTAG O 3311812-4
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BayerVB
19 WORDTAG O sets
21 WORDTAG I-MISC C$
71 WORDTAG O 100
280 WORDTAG O million
2 WORDTAG O six-year
24 WORDTAG O bond
47 WORDTAG O following
45 WORDTAG O announced
35 WORDTAG O manager
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toronto
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dominion
3 WORDTAG O BORROWER
2 WORDTAG I-ORG BAYERISCHE
2 WORDTAG I-ORG VEREINSBANK
4 WORDTAG O AMT
4 WORDTAG O MLN
3 WORDTAG O COUPON
1 WORDTAG O 6.625
4 WORDTAG O MATURITY
1 WORDTAG O 24.SEP.02
3 WORDTAG O TYPE
3 WORDTAG O STRAIGHT
4 WORDTAG O ISS
6 WORDTAG O PRICE
1 WORDTAG O 100.92
6 WORDTAG O PAY
6 WORDTAG O DATE
1 WORDTAG O 24.SEP.96
2 WORDTAG O FULL
2 WORDTAG O FEES
1 WORDTAG O 1.875
2 WORDTAG O REOFFER
1 WORDTAG O 99.32
2 WORDTAG O SPREAD
1 WORDTAG O +20
5 WORDTAG O BP
2 WORDTAG O MOODY
1 WORDTAG O AA1
4 WORDTAG O LISTING
1 WORDTAG O LUX
1 WORDTAG O FREQ
11 WORDTAG O =
7 WORDTAG I-ORG S&P
2 WORDTAG O DENOMS
2 WORDTAG O K
2 WORDTAG O 1-10-100
4 WORDTAG O SALE
2 WORDTAG O LIMITS
4 WORDTAG I-LOC US
10 WORDTAG I-LOC UK
1 WORDTAG I-LOC CA
2 WORDTAG O NEG
2 WORDTAG O PLG
4 WORDTAG O NO
2 WORDTAG O CRS
2 WORDTAG O DEFLT
3 WORDTAG O FORCE
2 WORDTAG O MAJ
2 WORDTAG O GOV
2 WORDTAG O LAW
16 WORDTAG I-MISC GERMAN
3 WORDTAG O HOME
2 WORDTAG O CTRY
3 WORDTAG O TAX
2 WORDTAG O PROVS
2 WORDTAG O STANDARD
2 WORDTAG O MGT
2 WORDTAG O UND
1 WORDTAG O 0.275
2 WORDTAG O SELL
2 WORDTAG O CONC
1 WORDTAG O 1.60
2 WORDTAG O PRAECIP
1 WORDTAG O UNDERLYING
3 WORDTAG O GOVT
3 WORDTAG O BOND
6 WORDTAG O 7.0
37 WORDTAG O PCT
1 WORDTAG O SEPT
7 WORDTAG O 2001
7 WORDTAG O NOTES
2 WORDTAG O IS
1 WORDTAG O JOINT
3 WORDTAG O LEAD
4 WORDTAG O MANAGER
24 WORDTAG I-ORG London
14 WORDTAG O +44
21 WORDTAG O 171
20 WORDTAG O 542
3 WORDTAG O 7658
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Venantius
24 WORDTAG O 300
5 WORDTAG O 1999
2 WORDTAG O FRN
1 WORDTAG O floating-rate
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Lehman
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Brothers
20 WORDTAG I-ORG International
1 WORDTAG I-ORG VENANTIUS
4 WORDTAG I-ORG AB
2 WORDTAG I-MISC SWEDISH
1 WORDTAG O NATIONAL
1 WORDTAG O MORTGAGE
1 WORDTAG O AGENCY
1243 WORDTAG O -
2 WORDTAG O 12.5
1 WORDTAG O 21.JAN.99
1 WORDTAG O BASE
1 WORDTAG I-ORG 3M
1 WORDTAG O LIBOR
1 WORDTAG O S23.SEP.96
8 WORDTAG O LAST
1 WORDTAG O AA3
1 WORDTAG O 99.956
2 WORDTAG O AA+
1 WORDTAG O S
2 WORDTAG O SHORT
55 WORDTAG O FIRST
1 WORDTAG I-LOC JP
1 WORDTAG I-LOC FR
1 WORDTAG O YES
1 WORDTAG O IPMA
972 WORDTAG O 2
19 WORDTAG I-MISC ENGLISH
1 WORDTAG I-LOC SWEDEN
392 WORDTAG O 5
1 WORDTAG O ISSUED
2 WORDTAG O OFF
1 WORDTAG O EMTN
1 WORDTAG O PROGRAMME
1 WORDTAG O 8863
3 WORDTAG O Port
2 WORDTAG O update
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Syria
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Lloyds
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Shipping
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Intelligence
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Service
1 WORDTAG I-LOC LATTAKIA
34 WORDTAG O Aug
10 WORDTAG O waiting
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lattakia
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tartous
1 WORDTAG O presently
63 WORDTAG O 24
63 WORDTAG I-LOC Israel
8 WORDTAG O plays
117 WORDTAG O down
10 WORDTAG O fears
62 WORDTAG O war
1 WORDTAG I-PER Colleen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Siegel
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JERUSALEM
2 WORDTAG O outgoing
84 WORDTAG O peace
40 WORDTAG O current
2 WORDTAG O tensions
136 WORDTAG O between
18 WORDTAG O appeared
9 WORDTAG O storm
2 WORDTAG O teacup
2 WORDTAG I-PER Itamar
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rabinovich
12 WORDTAG O ambassador
27 WORDTAG I-LOC Washington
8 WORDTAG O conducted
1 WORDTAG O unfruitful
21 WORDTAG O negotiations
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Israel
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Radio
17 WORDTAG O looked
42 WORDTAG O like
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Damascus
19 WORDTAG O wanted
23 WORDTAG O talk
12 WORDTAG O rather
15 WORDTAG O fight
6 WORDTAG O appears
35 WORDTAG O me
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Syrian
3 WORDTAG O priority
84 WORDTAG O still
2 WORDTAG O negotiate
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Syrians
2 WORDTAG O confused
306 WORDTAG O they
8 WORDTAG O definitely
5 WORDTAG O tense
7 WORDTAG O assessment
25 WORDTAG O here
1 WORDTAG O essentially
2 WORDTAG O winding
31 WORDTAG O term
416 WORDTAG O will
5 WORDTAG O replaced
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eliahu
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ben-Elissar
49 WORDTAG I-MISC Israeli
8 WORDTAG O envoy
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Egypt
9 WORDTAG O right-wing
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Likud
6 WORDTAG O politician
36 WORDTAG O sent
26 WORDTAG O message
7 WORDTAG O via
10 WORDTAG O committed
21 WORDTAG O open
37 WORDTAG O without
2 WORDTAG O preconditions
2 WORDTAG O slammed
3 WORDTAG O creating
59 WORDTAG O what
60 WORDTAG O called
4 WORDTAG O launching
1 WORDTAG O hysterical
38 WORDTAG O campaign
236 WORDTAG O against
47 WORDTAG O television
91 WORDTAG O reported
16 WORDTAG O recently
43 WORDTAG O test
13 WORDTAG O fired
2 WORDTAG O missile
19 WORDTAG O arms
3 WORDTAG O purchases
3 WORDTAG O defensive
3 WORDTAG O purposes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hafez
1 WORDTAG I-PER al-
1 WORDTAG I-PER Assad
9 WORDTAG O ready
9 WORDTAG O enter
37 WORDTAG O Foreign
50 WORDTAG I-PER David
12 WORDTAG I-PER Levy
2 WORDTAG O Tension
4 WORDTAG O mounted
133 WORDTAG O since
10 WORDTAG I-PER Benjamin
25 WORDTAG I-PER Netanyahu
76 WORDTAG O took
86 WORDTAG O June
1 WORDTAG O vowing
6 WORDTAG O retain
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Golan
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Heights
1 WORDTAG B-LOC Israel
9 WORDTAG O captured
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Middle
27 WORDTAG I-LOC East
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Israeli-Syrian
2 WORDTAG O deadlocked
271 WORDTAG O over
23 WORDTAG O 1991
30 WORDTAG O despite
38 WORDTAG O previous
1 WORDTAG O willingness
2 WORDTAG O concessions
2 WORDTAG O Peace
20 WORDTAG O February
3 WORDTAG O voices
27 WORDTAG O coming
291 WORDTAG O out
19 WORDTAG O bad
536 WORDTAG O not
55 WORDTAG O good
25 WORDTAG O full
1 WORDTAG O expressions
1 WORDTAG O declarations
32 WORDTAG O must
2 WORDTAG O worrying
1 WORDTAG O artificial
63 WORDTAG O very
49 WORDTAG O those
2 WORDTAG O spread
20 WORDTAG O become
5 WORDTAG O prisoners
20 WORDTAG O expect
31 WORDTAG O face
8 WORDTAG O answer
67 WORDTAG O our
51 WORDTAG O want
5 WORDTAG I-PER God
1 WORDTAG O forbid
28 WORDTAG O No
260 WORDTAG O one
3 WORDTAG O benefits
3 WORDTAG O wars
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Channel
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Two
1 WORDTAG O calming
6 WORDTAG O signal
24 WORDTAG O source
2 WORDTAG O spokesmen
7 WORDTAG O confirm
2 WORDTAG O messages
1 WORDTAG O reassure
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cairo
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
57 WORDTAG I-LOC States
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Moscow
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Polish
18 WORDTAG O diplomat
2 WORDTAG O denies
5 WORDTAG O nurses
4 WORDTAG O stranded
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Libya
3 WORDTAG I-LOC TUNIS
3 WORDTAG O tabloid
4 WORDTAG O refusing
4 WORDTAG O exit
3 WORDTAG O visas
32 WORDTAG O trying
44 WORDTAG O return
108 WORDTAG O home
37 WORDTAG O working
2 WORDTAG I-MISC North
45 WORDTAG I-MISC African
68 WORDTAG O country
43 WORDTAG O This
7 WORDTAG O true
5 WORDTAG O Up
27 WORDTAG O today
3 WORDTAG O knowledge
4 WORDTAG O nurse
25 WORDTAG O kept
169 WORDTAG O her
31 WORDTAG O received
4 WORDTAG O complaint
35 WORDTAG O embassy
19 WORDTAG O charge
1 WORDTAG O d'affaires
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Tripoli
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tadeusz
2 WORDTAG I-PER Awdankiewicz
17 WORDTAG O telephone
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Poland
7 WORDTAG O labour
330 WORDTAG O would
11 WORDTAG O send
89 WORDTAG O team
3 WORDTAG O investigate
6 WORDTAG O probe
9 WORDTAG O prompted
3 WORDTAG O complaining
180 WORDTAG O about
45 WORDTAG O work
1 WORDTAG O non-payment
2 WORDTAG O salaries
30 WORDTAG O estimated
13 WORDTAG O 800
33 WORDTAG O Two
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Iranian
55 WORDTAG O opposition
54 WORDTAG O leaders
60 WORDTAG O meet
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Baghdad
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hassan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hafidh
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BAGHDAD
29 WORDTAG O An
6 WORDTAG O exile
25 WORDTAG O based
68 WORDTAG I-LOC Iraq
6 WORDTAG O vowed
3 WORDTAG O extend
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Iran
33 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurdish
54 WORDTAG O rebels
7 WORDTAG O attacked
45 WORDTAG O troops
2 WORDTAG O deep
12 WORDTAG O inside
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Mujahideen
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Khalq
105 WORDTAG O statement
63 WORDTAG O leader
3 WORDTAG I-PER Massoud
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rajavi
26 WORDTAG O met
4 WORDTAG O Secretary-General
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdistan
19 WORDTAG I-ORG Democratic
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Party
104 WORDTAG I-ORG of
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Iran
2 WORDTAG I-ORG KDPI
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rastegar
3 WORDTAG O voiced
25 WORDTAG O rebel
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurds
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Rajavi
1 WORDTAG O emphasised
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Resistance
25 WORDTAG O continue
6 WORDTAG O stand
40 WORDTAG O side
1 WORDTAG O compatriots
4 WORDTAG O resistance
20 WORDTAG O movement
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Iranian
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kurdistan
2 WORDTAG O signals
29 WORDTAG O level
16 WORDTAG O cooperation
1 WORDTAG O oppositions
5 WORDTAG O heavily
2 WORDTAG O bombarded
6 WORDTAG O targets
53 WORDTAG O northern
6 WORDTAG O pursuit
31 WORDTAG O guerrillas
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqi
25 WORDTAG O areas
25 WORDTAG O outside
37 WORDTAG O control
2 WORDTAG O bordering
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Iraqi
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdish
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Patriotic
25 WORDTAG I-ORG PUK
17 WORDTAG I-ORG KDP
41 WORDTAG O main
14 WORDTAG O factions
46 WORDTAG O forces
8 WORDTAG O ousted
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Kuwait
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
15 WORDTAG I-MISC War
1 WORDTAG O Clashes
25 WORDTAG O parties
23 WORDTAG O broke
53 WORDTAG O weekend
70 WORDTAG O most
15 WORDTAG O serious
41 WORDTAG O fighting
1 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.-sponsored
36 WORDTAG O ceasefire
5 WORDTAG O shelling
16 WORDTAG O positions
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Qasri
38 WORDTAG O region
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Suleimaniya
53 WORDTAG O near
27 WORDTAG O border
74 WORDTAG O days
82 WORDTAG O killed
15 WORDTAG O wounded
38 WORDTAG O attack
11 WORDTAG O Both
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Turkey
1 WORDTAG O mount
21 WORDTAG O air
23 WORDTAG O land
5 WORDTAG O strikes
38 WORDTAG O own
6 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.-led
28 WORDTAG O force
46 WORDTAG O southern
2 WORDTAG O protects
32 WORDTAG O possible
25 WORDTAG O attacks
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Saudi
5 WORDTAG O riyal
31 WORDTAG O rates
20 WORDTAG O steady
20 WORDTAG O quiet
20 WORDTAG O summer
57 WORDTAG O trade
2 WORDTAG I-LOC MANAMA
17 WORDTAG O spot
53 WORDTAG O dollar
4 WORDTAG O interbank
7 WORDTAG O deposit
9 WORDTAG O mainly
21 WORDTAG O dealers
6 WORDTAG O kingdom
56 WORDTAG O There
8 WORDTAG O changes
143 WORDTAG O market
3 WORDTAG O holidays
18 WORDTAG O dealer
1 WORDTAG O 3.7504
1 WORDTAG O 06
1 WORDTAG I-MISC One-month
1 WORDTAG O deposits
1 WORDTAG O 5-1/2
1 WORDTAG O 3/8
201 WORDTAG O three
56 WORDTAG O months
1 WORDTAG O 5-5/8
84 WORDTAG O 1/2
117 WORDTAG O six
1 WORDTAG O 5-3/4
5 WORDTAG O 5/8
1 WORDTAG I-MISC One-year
12 WORDTAG O funds
1 WORDTAG O 5-7/8
2 WORDTAG O approves
47 WORDTAG I-PER Arafat
24 WORDTAG O flight
46 WORDTAG I-LOC West
32 WORDTAG I-LOC Bank
39 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinian
12 WORDTAG I-PER Yasser
9 WORDTAG O permission
10 WORDTAG O fly
18 WORDTAG O territory
14 WORDTAG O ending
10 WORDTAG O brief
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Israeli-PLO
12 WORDTAG O crisis
4 WORDTAG O adviser
25 WORDTAG O problem
95 WORDTAG O president
17 WORDTAG O aircraft
5 WORDTAG O pass
2 WORDTAG O airspace
106 WORDTAG O expected
15 WORDTAG O travel
149 WORDTAG O before
192 WORDTAG O Monday
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nabil
4 WORDTAG I-PER Abu
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rdainah
27 WORDTAG O scheduled
35 WORDTAG O prime
55 WORDTAG O minister
6 WORDTAG I-PER Shimon
15 WORDTAG I-PER Peres
59 WORDTAG O town
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Ramallah
5 WORDTAG O venue
13 WORDTAG O changed
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Gaza
2 WORDTAG O clearance
4 WORDTAG O helicopters
18 WORDTAG O stop
8 WORDTAG O keeping
1 WORDTAG O grounded
3 WORDTAG O subsequently
10 WORDTAG O cancelled
8 WORDTAG I-ORG PLO
5 WORDTAG O civilian
6 WORDTAG O affairs
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Allenby
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bridge
5 WORDTAG O crossing
24 WORDTAG I-LOC Jordan
23 WORDTAG O decided
7 WORDTAG O flying
10 WORDTAG O lifted
4 WORDTAG O busy
8 WORDTAG O schedule
32 WORDTAG O free
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinians
5 WORDTAG O barred
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Erez
1 WORDTAG O checkpoint
34 WORDTAG O planned
1 WORDTAG O overflying
7 WORDTAG O helicopter
17 WORDTAG O attempt
4 WORDTAG O bar
13 WORDTAG O defeated
54 WORDTAG O May
2 WORDTAG O undermine
4 WORDTAG O authority
4 WORDTAG O conduct
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Afghan
5 WORDTAG I-LOC UAE
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
9 WORDTAG O guards
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hilary
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gush
5 WORDTAG I-LOC DUBAI
11 WORDTAG O Three
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Arab
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Emirates
95 WORDTAG I-MISC Russian
6 WORDTAG O hostages
5 WORDTAG O escaped
8 WORDTAG O militia
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Afghanistan
42 WORDTAG O few
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Abu
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Dhabi
11 WORDTAG O Our
4 WORDTAG O touch
9 WORDTAG O Their
4 WORDTAG O issuing
102 WORDTAG O them
10 WORDTAG O documents
2 WORDTAG O homeland
1 WORDTAG O objection
85 WORDTAG O added
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamic
2 WORDTAG O overpowered
68 WORDTAG O seven
1 WORDTAG O aircrew
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Sharjah
181 WORDTAG O Friday
18 WORDTAG O board
2 WORDTAG O captivity
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kandahar
18 WORDTAG O hand
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Red
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Crescent
7 WORDTAG O possibly
212 WORDTAG O Tuesday
1 WORDTAG O silent
22 WORDTAG O When
42 WORDTAG O asked
98 WORDTAG O back
75 WORDTAG O capital
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul
30 WORDTAG O That
10 WORDTAG O headquarters
7 WORDTAG O controlled
3 WORDTAG I-PER Burhanuddin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rabbani
4 WORDTAG O overthrow
46 WORDTAG O men
2 WORDTAG O 20s
15 WORDTAG O currently
106 WORDTAG O did
4 WORDTAG O elaborate
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Russians
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Aerostan
23 WORDTAG O firm
9 WORDTAG O republic
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tatarstan
11 WORDTAG O hostage
1 WORDTAG B-MISC MiG-19
3 WORDTAG O fighter
31 WORDTAG O forced
9 WORDTAG O cargo
37 WORDTAG O plane
97 WORDTAG O August
9 WORDTAG O shipment
4 WORDTAG O ammunition
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Albania
12 WORDTAG O evidence
59 WORDTAG O military
14 WORDTAG O crew
2 WORDTAG O nationality
1 WORDTAG O coincidental
3 WORDTAG O Numerous
16 WORDTAG O diplomatic
7 WORDTAG O attempts
36 WORDTAG O failed
23 WORDTAG O armed
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Kalashnikov
2 WORDTAG O automatic
4 WORDTAG O rifles
18 WORDTAG O doing
7 WORDTAG O regular
3 WORDTAG O maintenance
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Ilyushin
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 76
66 WORDTAG O left
155 WORDTAG O Sunday
10 WORDTAG I-PER Saddam
5 WORDTAG O meets
88 WORDTAG I-LOC Russia
6 WORDTAG I-PER Zhirinovsky
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hussein
1 WORDTAG O ultra-nationalist
6 WORDTAG I-PER Vladimir
8 WORDTAG O maintain
4 WORDTAG O friendship
13 WORDTAG O newspapers
2 WORDTAG O stressed
80 WORDTAG O during
2 WORDTAG O keenness
4 WORDTAG O papers
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Liberal
1 WORDTAG I-ORG party
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Duma
44 WORDTAG O parliament
8 WORDTAG O calling
12 WORDTAG O immediate
7 WORDTAG O lifting
7 WORDTAG O embargo
13 WORDTAG O imposed
20 WORDTAG O 1990
1 WORDTAG O invasion
33 WORDTAG O press
36 WORDTAG O help
40 WORDTAG I-ORG U.N.
13 WORDTAG O sanctions
17 WORDTAG O blamed
3 WORDTAG O delaying
8 WORDTAG O establishment
10 WORDTAG O ties
1 WORDTAG O namely
50 WORDTAG O economic
12 WORDTAG O resume
17 WORDTAG O visited
17 WORDTAG O twice
15 WORDTAG O Last
34 WORDTAG O October
15 WORDTAG O invited
11 WORDTAG O attend
5 WORDTAG O referendum
8 WORDTAG O presidency
6 WORDTAG O extended
134 WORDTAG O years
24 WORDTAG O PRESS
24 WORDTAG O DIGEST
71 WORDTAG O 22
22 WORDTAG O These
41 WORDTAG O leading
34 WORDTAG O stories
19 WORDTAG O verified
37 WORDTAG O these
36 WORDTAG O does
16 WORDTAG O vouch
16 WORDTAG O accuracy
1 WORDTAG I-ORG THAWRA
4 WORDTAG O liberal
7 WORDTAG O democratic
24 WORDTAG I-MISC Turkish
78 WORDTAG O part
7 WORDTAG O fair
19 WORDTAG O November
2 WORDTAG I-LOC IRAQ
1 WORDTAG O shipload
104 WORDTAG O 12
6 WORDTAG O rice
8 WORDTAG O arrives
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Umm
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Qasr
17 WORDTAG O port
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Gulf
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Lebanon
3 WORDTAG I-LOC BEIRUT
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Beirut
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AN-NAHAR
1 WORDTAG O Confrontation
1 WORDTAG O escalating
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hizbollah
3 WORDTAG I-PER Hariri
7 WORDTAG O threats
10 WORDTAG O serve
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AS-SAFIR
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
9 WORDTAG O Speaker
2 WORDTAG I-PER Berri
9 WORDTAG O preparing
3 WORDTAG O Parliamentary
17 WORDTAG O battle
10 WORDTAG O ..
2 WORDTAG O lists
9 WORDTAG O prepared
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AL-ANWAR
1 WORDTAG O Continued
3 WORDTAG O criticism
30 WORDTAG O law
5 WORDTAG O violation
6 WORDTAG O incidents
7 WORDTAG O occurred
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Mount
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AD-DIYAR
5 WORDTAG O Financial
85 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistan
24 WORDTAG O step
45 WORDTAG O election
3 WORDTAG O incomplete
15 WORDTAG O list
2 WORDTAG I-ORG NIDA'A
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AL-WATAN
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Maronite
2 WORDTAG O Patriarch
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sfeir
1 WORDTAG O sorrow
11 WORDTAG O violations
4 WORDTAG I-ORG CME
14 WORDTAG O live
2 WORDTAG O feeder
10 WORDTAG O calls
18 WORDTAG O range
11 WORDTAG O mixed
29 WORDTAG I-LOC CHICAGO
1 WORDTAG O Early
15 WORDTAG O futures
2 WORDTAG O ranged
1 WORDTAG O 0.200
7 WORDTAG O cent
44 WORDTAG O higher
1 WORDTAG O 0.100
59 WORDTAG O lower
6 WORDTAG O livestock
28 WORDTAG O analysts
23 WORDTAG O continued
33 WORDTAG O strong
1 WORDTAG O tone
37 WORDTAG O cash
32 WORDTAG O markets
8 WORDTAG O prompt
1 WORDTAG O Outlook
7 WORDTAG O bullish
1 WORDTAG O cattle-on-feed
1 WORDTAG O lend
1 WORDTAG O bull
4 WORDTAG O spreading
13 WORDTAG O However
30 WORDTAG O likely
59 WORDTAG O prices
2 WORDTAG O drift
18 WORDTAG O evening
46 WORDTAG O ahead
9 WORDTAG O Cash
52 WORDTAG O record
7 WORDTAG O amount
2 WORDTAG O feedlot
19 WORDTAG O traded
1 WORDTAG O Kindercare
18 WORDTAG O debt
47 WORDTAG O hit
3 WORDTAG O Q1
73 WORDTAG O results
1 WORDTAG I-LOC MONTGOMERY
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Ala
1 WORDTAG I-ORG KinderCare
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Learning
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Centers
61 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc
2 WORDTAG O buyback
7 WORDTAG O mean
4 WORDTAG O extraordinary
45 WORDTAG O loss
5 WORDTAG O 1.2
14 WORDTAG O fiscal
42 WORDTAG O 1997
388 WORDTAG O first
127 WORDTAG O company
43 WORDTAG O began
1418 WORDTAG O 1
86 WORDTAG O 30
17 WORDTAG O par
20 WORDTAG O value
9 WORDTAG O outstanding
1 WORDTAG O 10-3/8
4 WORDTAG O notes
1 WORDTAG O 31.5
9 WORDTAG I-PER Philip
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maslowe
28 WORDTAG O financial
18 WORDTAG O officer
1 WORDTAG O preschool
18 WORDTAG O child
10 WORDTAG O care
19 WORDTAG O offered
9 WORDTAG O opportunity
9 WORDTAG O reduce
2 WORDTAG O weighted
35 WORDTAG O average
32 WORDTAG O interest
20 WORDTAG O costs
11 WORDTAG O improve
37 WORDTAG O future
4 WORDTAG O flows
28 WORDTAG O earnings
5 WORDTAG O RESEARCH
5 WORDTAG O ALERT
15 WORDTAG O starts
1 WORDTAG I-ORG SNET
19 WORDTAG O analyst
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blake
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bath
35 WORDTAG O started
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southern
49 WORDTAG I-ORG New
3 WORDTAG I-ORG England
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Telecommunciations
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp
6 WORDTAG O outperform
9 WORDTAG O rating
2 WORDTAG O 12-month
53 WORDTAG O price
13 WORDTAG O target
25 WORDTAG O 45
6 WORDTAG O estimate
1 WORDTAG O 3.09
71 WORDTAG O per
43 WORDTAG O share
30 WORDTAG O immediately
37 WORDTAG O available
44 WORDTAG O closed
1 WORDTAG O 38-1/2
2 WORDTAG I-PER E.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Auchard
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Wall
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Street
1 WORDTAG I-ORG bureau
1 WORDTAG O 212-859-1736
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Gateway
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Data
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Sciences
5 WORDTAG O Q2
53 WORDTAG O net
9 WORDTAG O rises
1 WORDTAG I-LOC PHOENIX
12 WORDTAG O Summary
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Consolidated
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Financial
171 WORDTAG O In
8 WORDTAG O Thousands
6 WORDTAG O except
14 WORDTAG O data
8 WORDTAG O Six
2 WORDTAG O Months
2 WORDTAG O Ended
2 WORDTAG O Quarter
14 WORDTAG O Jul
45 WORDTAG O 31
6 WORDTAG O Income
1 WORDTAG O Statement
5 WORDTAG O Data
26 WORDTAG O Total
11 WORDTAG O Revenue
1 WORDTAG O 10,756
1 WORDTAG O 13,102
1 WORDTAG O 7,961
1 WORDTAG O 5,507
2 WORDTAG O Software
2 WORDTAG O 2,383
1 WORDTAG O 1,558
1 WORDTAG O 1,086
1 WORDTAG O 1,074
1 WORDTAG O Services
1 WORDTAG O 1,154
1 WORDTAG O 692
1 WORDTAG O 624
1 WORDTAG O 465
6 WORDTAG O Operating
1 WORDTAG O 906
1 WORDTAG O 962
5 WORDTAG O 599
1 WORDTAG O 515
24 WORDTAG O Net
1 WORDTAG O 821
1 WORDTAG O 512
2 WORDTAG O 565
2 WORDTAG O 301
2 WORDTAG O Earnings
2 WORDTAG O Per
2 WORDTAG O Share
1 WORDTAG O 0.31
1 WORDTAG O 0.34
3 WORDTAG O 0.19
4 WORDTAG O 0.20
7 WORDTAG O Jan
4 WORDTAG O Balance
2 WORDTAG O Sheet
2 WORDTAG O Working
1 WORDTAG O Capital
1 WORDTAG O 5,755
1 WORDTAG O 881
1 WORDTAG O Equivalents
1 WORDTAG O 2,386
5 WORDTAG O 93
1 WORDTAG O Assets
1 WORDTAG O 14,196
1 WORDTAG O 7,138
2 WORDTAG O Shareholders
1 WORDTAG O Equity
1 WORDTAG O 5,951
1 WORDTAG O 1,461
3 WORDTAG O socialists
36 WORDTAG O give
8 WORDTAG O backing
1 WORDTAG O chooses
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Le
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Monde
30 WORDTAG I-LOC PARIS
12 WORDTAG O afternoon
29 WORDTAG O daily
6 WORDTAG O dated
44 WORDTAG O 23
2 WORDTAG O FRONT
2 WORDTAG O PAGE
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Africans
14 WORDTAG O seeking
2 WORDTAG O renew
2 WORDTAG O obtain
10 WORDTAG O residence
40 WORDTAG O rights
60 WORDTAG O say
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alain
8 WORDTAG I-PER Juppe
8 WORDTAG O proposals
1 WORDTAG O insufficient
1 WORDTAG O hunger
38 WORDTAG O strike
3 WORDTAG O enters
1 WORDTAG O 49th
106 WORDTAG O day
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Paris
17 WORDTAG O church
14 WORDTAG O rally
2 WORDTAG O attracts
8 WORDTAG O 8,000
1 WORDTAG O sympathisers
1 WORDTAG I-ORG FLNC
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Corsican
5 WORDTAG O nationalist
3 WORDTAG O announces
14 WORDTAG O truce
44 WORDTAG O night
2 WORDTAG O BUSINESS
2 WORDTAG O PAGES
1 WORDTAG O Shutdown
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bally
67 WORDTAG I-MISC French
1 WORDTAG O factories
137 WORDTAG O points
1 WORDTAG O shoe
31 WORDTAG O industry
1 WORDTAG O undercut
1 WORDTAG O low-wage
19 WORDTAG O competition
9 WORDTAG O failure
26 WORDTAG O keep
1 WORDTAG O abreast
6 WORDTAG O trends
14 WORDTAG O Secretary
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sud-PTT
20 WORDTAG O union
4 WORDTAG I-ORG France
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Telecom
4 WORDTAG O elements
9 WORDTAG O social
14 WORDTAG O unrest
45 WORDTAG O weeks
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Paris
4 WORDTAG O +33
24 WORDTAG O 42
114 WORDTAG O 21
26 WORDTAG O 53
18 WORDTAG O 81
1 WORDTAG O Well
4 WORDTAG O repairs
8 WORDTAG O lift
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Heidrun
42 WORDTAG O oil
17 WORDTAG O output
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Statoil
3 WORDTAG I-LOC OSLO
2 WORDTAG O plugged
16 WORDTAG O water
3 WORDTAG O injection
5 WORDTAG O wells
1 WORDTAG O oilfield
120 WORDTAG O off
1 WORDTAG I-MISC mid-Norway
6 WORDTAG O reopened
6 WORDTAG O operator
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Den
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Norske
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Stats
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Oljeselskap
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AS
3 WORDTAG O accounted
2 WORDTAG O dip
8 WORDTAG O 30,000
10 WORDTAG O barrels
6 WORDTAG O bpd
3 WORDTAG O roughly
1 WORDTAG O 220,000
24 WORDTAG O according
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Status
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Weekly
1 WORDTAG O newsletter
1 WORDTAG O reperforated
1 WORDTAG O gravel
2 WORDTAG O pumped
1 WORDTAG O reservoir
1 WORDTAG O plugging
22 WORDTAG O problems
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Oslo
61 WORDTAG O newsroom
1 WORDTAG O +47
69 WORDTAG O 50
17 WORDTAG O 41
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Finnish
33 WORDTAG O April
11 WORDTAG O surplus
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
91 WORDTAG O billion
9 WORDTAG O markka
4 WORDTAG I-ORG NCB
6 WORDTAG I-LOC HELSINKI
42 WORDTAG I-LOC Finland
1 WORDTAG O 3.83
1 WORDTAG O 3.43
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Customs
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Board
28 WORDTAG O exports
4 WORDTAG O year-on-year
5 WORDTAG O Trade
9 WORDTAG O balance
32 WORDTAG O 96
4 WORDTAG O Jan-April
9 WORDTAG O 95
2 WORDTAG O Imports
1 WORDTAG O 10,663
1 WORDTAG O 10,725
1 WORDTAG O 43,430
1 WORDTAG O 40,989
3 WORDTAG O Exports
1 WORDTAG O 14,494
1 WORDTAG O 14,153
1 WORDTAG O 56,126
1 WORDTAG O 56,261
1 WORDTAG O +3,831
1 WORDTAG O +3,428
1 WORDTAG O +12,696
1 WORDTAG O +15,272
1 WORDTAG O January-April
5 WORDTAG O import
13 WORDTAG O revised
1 WORDTAG O 39,584
14 WORDTAG O export
1 WORDTAG O 55,627
43 WORDTAG I-ORG Bank
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Finland
5 WORDTAG O 3.2
2 WORDTAG O projected
3 WORDTAG O 14.5
2 WORDTAG O 11.3
8 WORDTAG O monthly
4 WORDTAG O statistics
2 WORDTAG O lagging
56 WORDTAG O behind
12 WORDTAG O customs
2 WORDTAG O procedures
220 WORDTAG O when
15 WORDTAG O joined
51 WORDTAG O start
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Helsinki
3 WORDTAG O +358
945 WORDTAG O 0
3 WORDTAG O 680
2 WORDTAG O 245
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Dutch
4 WORDTAG O raises
3 WORDTAG O tap
18 WORDTAG O sale
2 WORDTAG O 99.95
26 WORDTAG I-LOC AMSTERDAM
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Finance
13 WORDTAG O raised
50 WORDTAG O sales
2 WORDTAG O 5.75
99 WORDTAG O September
3 WORDTAG O 2002
1 WORDTAG O 99.90
1 WORDTAG O Tap
86 WORDTAG O being
1 WORDTAG O 07.00
49 WORDTAG I-MISC GMT
2 WORDTAG O 15.00
3 WORDTAG O notice
2 WORDTAG O 2.3
21 WORDTAG O guilders
61 WORDTAG O close
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Amsterdam
13 WORDTAG O +31
100 WORDTAG O 20
14 WORDTAG O 504
10 WORDTAG O 5000
3 WORDTAG O tells
20 WORDTAG I-LOC BONN
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Agriculture
3 WORDTAG O meat
6 WORDTAG O animals
3 WORDTAG O Until
8 WORDTAG O cleared
1 WORDTAG O panels
14 WORDTAG O done
12 WORDTAG O quickly
2 WORDTAG O preference
2 WORDTAG I-ORG ZDF
307 WORDTAG O I
6 WORDTAG O concrete
24 WORDTAG O too
48 WORDTAG O many
7 WORDTAG O holes
26 WORDTAG O know
5 WORDTAG O filled
7 WORDTAG O ensure
11 WORDTAG O protection
4 WORDTAG O tops
1 WORDTAG O priorities
6 WORDTAG O dealing
6 WORDTAG O erupted
3 WORDTAG O acknowledged
1 WORDTAG O rethink
29 WORDTAG O use
11 WORDTAG O suspect
3 WORDTAG O tissue
5 WORDTAG O experts
4 WORDTAG O banning
34 WORDTAG O members
33 WORDTAG O given
20 WORDTAG O question
1 WORDTAG O studied
1 WORDTAG O separately
3 WORDTAG O perfectly
4 WORDTAG O safe
3 WORDTAG O eat
25 WORDTAG O After
16 WORDTAG O admitted
8 WORDTAG O link
6 WORDTAG O fatal
6 WORDTAG O equivalent
6 WORDTAG O worldwide
2 WORDTAG O summit
1 WORDTAG O progressive
11 WORDTAG O takes
2 WORDTAG O parallel
1 WORDTAG O eradicate
9 WORDTAG O GOLF
14 WORDTAG O SCORES
131 WORDTAG O AT
6 WORDTAG I-MISC WORLD
3 WORDTAG I-MISC SERIES
8 WORDTAG I-MISC OF
3 WORDTAG I-MISC GOLF
7 WORDTAG I-LOC AKRON
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Ohio
13 WORDTAG O Scores
4 WORDTAG O 2.1
3 WORDTAG I-MISC NEC
48 WORDTAG I-MISC World
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Series
20 WORDTAG I-MISC of
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Golf
122 WORDTAG O round
2 WORDTAG O 7,149
3 WORDTAG O yard
105 WORDTAG O 70
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Firestone
3 WORDTAG I-LOC C.C
25 WORDTAG O course
52 WORDTAG O players
28 WORDTAG O unless
18 WORDTAG O stated
66 WORDTAG O 66
51 WORDTAG I-PER Paul
4 WORDTAG I-PER Goydos
7 WORDTAG I-PER Billy
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mayfair
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hidemichi
3 WORDTAG I-PER Tanaka
87 WORDTAG I-LOC Japan
75 WORDTAG O 68
23 WORDTAG I-PER Steve
4 WORDTAG I-PER Stricker
91 WORDTAG O 69
6 WORDTAG I-PER Justin
4 WORDTAG I-PER Leonard
58 WORDTAG I-PER Mark
4 WORDTAG I-PER Brooks
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tim
3 WORDTAG I-PER Herron
4 WORDTAG I-PER Duffy
4 WORDTAG I-PER Waldorf
12 WORDTAG I-PER Davis
3 WORDTAG I-PER Love
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anders
3 WORDTAG I-PER Forsbrand
81 WORDTAG I-LOC Sweden
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nick
3 WORDTAG I-PER Faldo
3 WORDTAG I-PER Cook
6 WORDTAG I-PER Phil
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mickelson
14 WORDTAG I-PER Greg
10 WORDTAG I-PER Norman
130 WORDTAG I-LOC Australia
85 WORDTAG O 71
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ernie
5 WORDTAG I-PER Els
76 WORDTAG I-LOC South
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Africa
19 WORDTAG I-PER Scott
3 WORDTAG I-PER Hoch
58 WORDTAG O 72
4 WORDTAG I-PER Clarence
12 WORDTAG I-PER Rose
3 WORDTAG I-PER Loren
3 WORDTAG I-PER Roberts
9 WORDTAG I-PER Fred
3 WORDTAG I-PER Funk
8 WORDTAG I-PER Sven
3 WORDTAG I-PER Struver
23 WORDTAG I-PER Alexander
3 WORDTAG I-PER Cejka
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hal
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sutton
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tom
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lehman
52 WORDTAG O 73
3 WORDTAG I-PER D.A.
3 WORDTAG I-PER Weibring
6 WORDTAG I-PER Brad
3 WORDTAG I-PER Bryant
14 WORDTAG I-PER Craig
3 WORDTAG I-PER Parry
16 WORDTAG I-PER Stewart
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ginn
4 WORDTAG I-PER Corey
3 WORDTAG I-PER Pavin
3 WORDTAG I-PER Stadler
3 WORDTAG I-PER O'Meara
3 WORDTAG I-PER Couples
53 WORDTAG O 74
3 WORDTAG I-PER Stankowski
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costantino
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rocca
98 WORDTAG I-LOC Italy
55 WORDTAG O 75
21 WORDTAG I-PER Jim
3 WORDTAG I-PER Furyk
3 WORDTAG I-PER Satoshi
3 WORDTAG I-PER Higashi
4 WORDTAG I-PER Willie
3 WORDTAG I-PER Wood
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shigeki
3 WORDTAG I-PER Maruyama
28 WORDTAG O 76
3 WORDTAG I-PER McCarron
24 WORDTAG O 77
17 WORDTAG I-PER Wayne
3 WORDTAG I-PER Westner
3 WORDTAG I-PER Schneiter
12 WORDTAG O 79
3 WORDTAG I-PER Watson
3 WORDTAG I-PER Seiki
3 WORDTAG I-PER Okuda
132 WORDTAG O SOCCER
1 WORDTAG I-ORG GLORIA
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BISTRITA
17 WORDTAG O BEAT
25 WORDTAG O 2-1
14 WORDTAG I-ORG F.C.
1 WORDTAG I-ORG VALLETTA
1 WORDTAG I-LOC BISTRITA
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloria
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bistrita
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Romania
335 WORDTAG O beat
28 WORDTAG O halftime
25 WORDTAG O 1-1
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Valletta
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malta
94 WORDTAG I-MISC Cup
2 WORDTAG I-MISC winners
120 WORDTAG O match
24 WORDTAG O leg
16 WORDTAG O preliminary
23 WORDTAG O Scorers
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ilie
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lazar
4 WORDTAG O 32nd
2 WORDTAG I-PER Eugen
2 WORDTAG I-PER Voica
4 WORDTAG O 84th
9 WORDTAG I-ORG La
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbert
2 WORDTAG I-PER Agius
8 WORDTAG O 24th
52 WORDTAG O Attendance
9 WORDTAG O 4-2
25 WORDTAG O aggregate
6 WORDTAG O qualified
3 WORDTAG I-PER REUTER
3 WORDTAG O HORSE
8 WORDTAG O RACING
1 WORDTAG I-PER PIVOTAL
3 WORDTAG O ENDS
1 WORDTAG O 25-YEAR
2 WORDTAG O WAIT
1 WORDTAG O TRAINER
1 WORDTAG I-PER PRESCOTT
67 WORDTAG I-LOC YORK
124 WORDTAG I-LOC England
5 WORDTAG O Sir
4 WORDTAG I-PER Prescott
17 WORDTAG O landed
70 WORDTAG O victory
68 WORDTAG O 25
2 WORDTAG O trainer
4 WORDTAG O sprinter
3 WORDTAG I-PER Pivotal
2 WORDTAG O 100-30
22 WORDTAG O chance
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Nunthorpe
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Stakes
2 WORDTAG O three-year-old
1 WORDTAG O partnered
14 WORDTAG O veteran
14 WORDTAG I-PER George
2 WORDTAG I-PER Duffield
1 WORDTAG O snatched
33 WORDTAG O short
42 WORDTAG O head
3 WORDTAG O verdict
1 WORDTAG O stride
5 WORDTAG O deny
2 WORDTAG I-PER Eveningperformance
2 WORDTAG O 16-1
5 WORDTAG O trained
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henry
2 WORDTAG I-PER Candy
2 WORDTAG O ridden
19 WORDTAG I-PER Chris
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rutter
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hever
2 WORDTAG I-PER Golf
3 WORDTAG O 11-4
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Prix
2 WORDTAG I-MISC de
1 WORDTAG I-MISC l
12 WORDTAG I-MISC '
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Abbaye
24 WORDTAG O winner
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Longchamp
16 WORDTAG O finished
107 WORDTAG O third
2 WORDTAG O lengths
42 WORDTAG O away
23 WORDTAG O 7-4
4 WORDTAG I-PER Mind
4 WORDTAG I-PER Games
36 WORDTAG O fourth
1 WORDTAG I-PER Royal
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ascot
46 WORDTAG O may
81 WORDTAG O now
14 WORDTAG O aimed
81 WORDTAG O season
10 WORDTAG O sprint
57 WORDTAG O race
5 WORDTAG O reluctant
62 WORDTAG O go
1 WORDTAG O enclosure
29 WORDTAG O result
1 WORDTAG O photo-finish
1 WORDTAG O Twenty-five
23 WORDTAG O never
72 WORDTAG O so
17 WORDTAG O thought
29 WORDTAG O better
8 WORDTAG O wait
12 WORDTAG O bit
10 WORDTAG O longer
4 WORDTAG O sad
15 WORDTAG O am
1 WORDTAG O godfather
12 WORDTAG O daughter
2 WORDTAG O Like
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jack
2 WORDTAG I-PER Berry
9 WORDTAG O gone
8 WORDTAG O search
9 WORDTAG O success
78 WORDTAG O around
1 WORDTAG O profession
1 WORDTAG O I`m
7 WORDTAG O disappointed
16 WORDTAG O feel
1 WORDTAG O suicidal
70 WORDTAG O well
2 WORDTAG O furlongs
84 WORDTAG O metres
106 WORDTAG O just
1 WORDTAG O quicken
1 WORDTAG O NUNTHORPE
1 WORDTAG O STAKES
99 WORDTAG O RESULTS
24 WORDTAG O Result
1 WORDTAG O two-year-olds
1 WORDTAG O upwards
61 WORDTAG O run
112 WORDTAG O five
47 WORDTAG O km
94 WORDTAG O 1.
95 WORDTAG O 2.
95 WORDTAG O 3.
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jason
7 WORDTAG I-PER Weaver
8 WORDTAG O Eight
10 WORDTAG O ran
1 WORDTAG O Favourite
4 WORDTAG O 4th
1 WORDTAG O Distances
1 WORDTAG O 1-1/4
2 WORDTAG O Winner
15 WORDTAG O owned
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Cheveley
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Park
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Stud
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Newmarket
2 WORDTAG O Value
1 WORDTAG O 72,464
7 WORDTAG O sterling
1 WORDTAG O 112,200
31 WORDTAG O TENNIS
5 WORDTAG I-MISC TOSHIBA
5 WORDTAG I-MISC CLASSIC
5 WORDTAG I-LOC CARLSBAD
16 WORDTAG I-LOC California
7 WORDTAG O 1996-08-21
85 WORDTAG O Results
5 WORDTAG O 450,000
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Toshiba
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Classic
34 WORDTAG O tennis
54 WORDTAG O tournament
25 WORDTAG O prefix
24 WORDTAG O denotes
28 WORDTAG O seeding
15 WORDTAG O Second
11 WORDTAG I-PER Arantxa
19 WORDTAG I-PER Sanchez
11 WORDTAG I-PER Vicario
110 WORDTAG I-LOC Spain
5 WORDTAG I-PER Naoko
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kijimuta
17 WORDTAG O 1-6
117 WORDTAG O 6-4
117 WORDTAG O 6-3
581 WORDTAG O 4
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kimiko
7 WORDTAG I-PER Date
3 WORDTAG I-PER Yone
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kamio
100 WORDTAG O 6-2
63 WORDTAG O 7-5
4 WORDTAG I-PER Sandrine
4 WORDTAG I-PER Testud
259 WORDTAG O 7
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ai
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sugiyama
19 WORDTAG O 4-6
155 WORDTAG O 8
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nathalie
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tauziat
3 WORDTAG I-PER Shi-Ting
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wang
4 WORDTAG I-MISC HAMLET
20 WORDTAG I-MISC CUP
4 WORDTAG I-LOC COMMACK
95 WORDTAG I-LOC New
38 WORDTAG I-LOC York
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Waldbaum
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Hamlet
55 WORDTAG I-PER Michael
16 WORDTAG I-PER Chang
7 WORDTAG I-PER Sergi
6 WORDTAG I-PER Bruguera
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joyce
930 WORDTAG O 3
4 WORDTAG I-PER Richey
4 WORDTAG I-PER Reneberg
22 WORDTAG O 3-6
47 WORDTAG I-PER Martin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damm
57 WORDTAG I-LOC Czech
62 WORDTAG I-LOC Republic
343 WORDTAG O 6
2 WORDTAG I-PER Younes
7 WORDTAG I-PER El
3 WORDTAG I-PER Aynaoui
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Morocco
14 WORDTAG O 5-7
15 WORDTAG O 3-0
11 WORDTAG O retired
5 WORDTAG I-PER Karol
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kucera
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovakia
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hicham
3 WORDTAG I-PER Arazi
74 WORDTAG O 7-6
1 WORDTAG I-PER DALGLISH
1 WORDTAG O SAD
2 WORDTAG O OVER
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BLACKBURN
1 WORDTAG O PARTING
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kenny
4 WORDTAG I-PER Dalglish
11 WORDTAG O spoke
1 WORDTAG O sadness
17 WORDTAG O leaving
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackburn
37 WORDTAG O club
22 WORDTAG O premier
65 WORDTAG O league
27 WORDTAG O title
2 WORDTAG O 1994-95
2 WORDTAG O parted
5 WORDTAG O mutual
2 WORDTAG O consent
1 WORDTAG O ex-manager
7 WORDTAG O confessed
50 WORDTAG O taking
85 WORDTAG O division
63 WORDTAG O local
58 WORDTAG O newspaper
28 WORDTAG O holiday
62 WORDTAG O same
12 WORDTAG O opinion
1 WORDTAG O albeit
36 WORDTAG O little
32 WORDTAG O If
25 WORDTAG O opened
50 WORDTAG O my
3 WORDTAG O mouth
7 WORDTAG O stayed
45 WORDTAG O way
9 WORDTAG O let
53 WORDTAG O get
16 WORDTAG O job
4 WORDTAG O conclusion
60 WORDTAG O then
40 WORDTAG O past
112 WORDTAG O 15
24 WORDTAG O director
5 WORDTAG O football
50 WORDTAG O CRICKET
6 WORDTAG I-MISC COUNTY
7 WORDTAG I-MISC CHAMPIONSHIP
5 WORDTAG O Close
65 WORDTAG O play
16 WORDTAG O scores
13 WORDTAG O four-day
2 WORDTAG B-MISC County
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Championship
21 WORDTAG O cricket
91 WORDTAG O matches
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Weston-super-Mare
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Durham
23 WORDTAG O 326
22 WORDTAG I-PER D.
3 WORDTAG I-PER Cox
15 WORDTAG I-PER S.
9 WORDTAG I-PER Campbell
52 WORDTAG O ;
23 WORDTAG I-PER G.
3 WORDTAG O 7-73
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Somerset
1 WORDTAG O 236-4
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
3 WORDTAG I-PER Lathwell
8 WORDTAG O 85
1 WORDTAG O Firsy
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Colchester
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloucestershire
8 WORDTAG O 280
17 WORDTAG I-PER J.
17 WORDTAG I-PER Russell
40 WORDTAG O 63
32 WORDTAG I-PER A.
3 WORDTAG I-PER Symonds
23 WORDTAG O 52
3 WORDTAG I-PER Cowan
2 WORDTAG O 5-68
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Essex
1 WORDTAG O 72-0
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cardiff
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Kent
1 WORDTAG O 128-1
7 WORDTAG I-PER Walker
34 WORDTAG O 59
4 WORDTAG I-PER Fulton
89 WORDTAG O v
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Glamorgan
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Leicester
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicestershire
2 WORDTAG O 343-8
18 WORDTAG I-PER P.
3 WORDTAG I-PER Simmons
6 WORDTAG O 108
4 WORDTAG I-PER Nixon
64 WORDTAG O 67
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Northampton
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Sussex
1 WORDTAG O 368-7
20 WORDTAG I-PER N.
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lenham
6 WORDTAG O 145
5 WORDTAG I-PER V.
2 WORDTAG I-PER Drakes
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wells
19 WORDTAG O 51
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Northamptonshire
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Trent
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Nottinghamshire
2 WORDTAG O 392-6
3 WORDTAG I-PER Archer
4 WORDTAG O 143
3 WORDTAG I-PER Dowman
5 WORDTAG O 107
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Surrey
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Worcester
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Warwickshire
1 WORDTAG O 255-9
6 WORDTAG I-PER Giles
19 WORDTAG O 57
6 WORDTAG I-PER W.
25 WORDTAG I-PER Khan
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Worcestershire
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Headingley
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yorkshire
1 WORDTAG O 305-5
16 WORDTAG I-PER C.
13 WORDTAG I-PER White
5 WORDTAG I-PER Moxon
4 WORDTAG I-PER Vaughan
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Lancashire
21 WORDTAG I-LOC ENGLAND
14 WORDTAG O V
20 WORDTAG I-LOC PAKISTAN
7 WORDTAG O FINAL
13 WORDTAG O TEST
8 WORDTAG O SCOREBOARD
8 WORDTAG O Scoreboard
71 WORDTAG O final
20 WORDTAG I-LOC The
19 WORDTAG I-LOC Oval
75 WORDTAG O innings
11 WORDTAG I-PER Atherton
74 WORDTAG O b
28 WORDTAG I-PER Waqar
28 WORDTAG I-PER Younis
28 WORDTAG I-PER Mushtaq
49 WORDTAG I-PER Ahmed
16 WORDTAG O 44
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hussain
40 WORDTAG O c
18 WORDTAG I-PER Saeed
17 WORDTAG I-PER Anwar
13 WORDTAG I-PER Thorpe
7 WORDTAG O lbw
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mohammad
37 WORDTAG I-PER Akram
33 WORDTAG O 54
12 WORDTAG I-PER Crawley
3 WORDTAG O 94
8 WORDTAG I-PER Knight
47 WORDTAG O 17
21 WORDTAG I-PER Lewis
34 WORDTAG I-PER Wasim
4 WORDTAG I-PER I.
9 WORDTAG I-PER Salisbury
16 WORDTAG O Extras
1 WORDTAG O lb-11
3 WORDTAG O w-1
3 WORDTAG O nb-8
36 WORDTAG O wickets
5 WORDTAG O 278
15 WORDTAG O Fall
2 WORDTAG O 1-64
2 WORDTAG O 2-85
2 WORDTAG O 3-116
2 WORDTAG O 4-205
2 WORDTAG O 5-248
2 WORDTAG O 6-273
15 WORDTAG O To
15 WORDTAG O bat
19 WORDTAG I-PER R.
28 WORDTAG I-PER Croft
17 WORDTAG I-PER Cork
26 WORDTAG I-PER Mullally
16 WORDTAG O Bowling
30 WORDTAG O date
1 WORDTAG O 25-8-61-1
1 WORDTAG O 20-6-70-2
2 WORDTAG O 12-1-41-1
2 WORDTAG O 27-5-78-2
19 WORDTAG I-PER Aamir
22 WORDTAG I-PER Sohail
2 WORDTAG O 6-1-17-0
15 WORDTAG I-PER Ijaz
12 WORDTAG I-PER Inzamam-ul-Haq
13 WORDTAG I-PER Salim
13 WORDTAG I-PER Malik
12 WORDTAG I-PER Asif
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mujtaba
13 WORDTAG I-PER Moin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Akam
1 WORDTAG I-PER FERGUSON
2 WORDTAG O BACK
48 WORDTAG O IN
5 WORDTAG I-MISC SCOTTISH
8 WORDTAG O SQUAD
13 WORDTAG O AFTER
2 WORDTAG O MONTHS
4 WORDTAG I-LOC GLASGOW
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Everton
3 WORDTAG I-PER Duncan
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ferguson
40 WORDTAG O scored
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Manchester
48 WORDTAG I-ORG United
13 WORDTAG O picked
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Scottish
30 WORDTAG O squad
4 WORDTAG O 20-month
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Glasgow
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Rangers
23 WORDTAG O striker
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ally
2 WORDTAG I-PER McCoist
51 WORDTAG O another
60 WORDTAG O man
17 WORDTAG O form
1 WORDTAG O hat-tricks
117 WORDTAG O four
29 WORDTAG O named
17 WORDTAG O qualifier
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Austria
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vienna
9 WORDTAG O served
18 WORDTAG O jail
1 WORDTAG O head-butting
4 WORDTAG O opponent
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Scotland
5 WORDTAG O caps
19 WORDTAG O December
44 WORDTAG O 1994
14 WORDTAG I-PER Brown
19 WORDTAG O 've
3 WORDTAG O watched
2 WORDTAG O bang
24 WORDTAG O great
12 WORDTAG O scoring
15 WORDTAG O moment
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Celtic
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jackie
3 WORDTAG I-PER McNamara
9 WORDTAG O successful
3 WORDTAG O under-21
2 WORDTAG O earns
1 WORDTAG O call-up
1 WORDTAG O 100-2
2 WORDTAG O LUNCH
14 WORDTAG O ON
3 WORDTAG O DAY
48 WORDTAG O OF
9 WORDTAG O THIRD
8 WORDTAG O lunch
1 WORDTAG I-PER KEANE
2 WORDTAG O SIGNS
1 WORDTAG O FOUR-YEAR
2 WORDTAG O CONTRACT
10 WORDTAG O WITH
13 WORDTAG I-LOC MANCHESTER
1 WORDTAG I-LOC UNITED
36 WORDTAG I-LOC Ireland
19 WORDTAG O midfielder
3 WORDTAG I-PER Roy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Keane
40 WORDTAG O signed
4 WORDTAG O four-year
1 WORDTAG I-MISC F.A.
35 WORDTAG O champions
58 WORDTAG O deal
76 WORDTAG O game
2 WORDTAG O delighted
22 WORDTAG I-PER Alex
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CANADIAN
26 WORDTAG I-MISC OPEN
13 WORDTAG I-LOC TORONTO
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Canadian
71 WORDTAG I-MISC Open
14 WORDTAG I-PER Daniel
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nestor
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Canada
34 WORDTAG I-PER Thomas
14 WORDTAG I-PER Muster
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mikael
9 WORDTAG I-PER Tillstrom
5 WORDTAG I-PER Goran
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ivanisevic
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Croatia
14 WORDTAG O 6-7
3 WORDTAG O 3-7
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ferreira
4 WORDTAG I-PER Jiri
3 WORDTAG I-PER Novak
15 WORDTAG I-PER Marcelo
9 WORDTAG I-PER Rios
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Chile
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kenneth
4 WORDTAG I-PER Carlsen
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Denmark
7 WORDTAG I-PER MaliVai
12 WORDTAG I-PER Washington
3 WORDTAG I-PER Corretja
21 WORDTAG I-PER Todd
3 WORDTAG I-PER Renzo
3 WORDTAG I-PER Furlan
9 WORDTAG O 7-3
17 WORDTAG I-PER Philippoussis
13 WORDTAG I-PER Marc
7 WORDTAG I-PER Rosset
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Switzerland
11 WORDTAG O 8-6
167 WORDTAG O 9
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cedric
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pioline
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gregory
1 WORDTAG I-PER Carraz
11 WORDTAG O 7-1
12 WORDTAG I-PER Patrick
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
120 WORDTAG O 11
7 WORDTAG I-PER Alberto
4 WORDTAG I-PER Berasategui
75 WORDTAG O 6-1
8 WORDTAG I-PER Petr
6 WORDTAG I-PER Korda
8 WORDTAG I-PER Francisco
3 WORDTAG I-PER Clavet
5 WORDTAG I-PER Vacek
119 WORDTAG O 13
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stoltenberg
2 WORDTAG O 13-11
9 WORDTAG I-PER Woodbridge
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sebastien
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lareau
10 WORDTAG I-PER O'Brien
3 WORDTAG I-PER Byron
7 WORDTAG I-PER Black
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Zimbabwe
11 WORDTAG O 7-2
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bohdan
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ulihrach
14 WORDTAG I-PER Andrea
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gaudenzi
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henman
3 WORDTAG I-PER Woodruff
5 WORDTAG O walkover
1 WORDTAG I-PER MILLNS
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BOLAND
3 WORDTAG I-LOC CAPE
3 WORDTAG I-LOC TOWN
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
10 WORDTAG O provincial
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Boland
11 WORDTAG O fast
2 WORDTAG O bowler
3 WORDTAG I-PER Millns
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Millns
1 WORDTAG O toured
1 WORDTAG O 1992/93
3 WORDTAG O replaces
3 WORDTAG O all-rounder
1 WORDTAG I-PER Phillip
1 WORDTAG I-PER DeFreitas
7 WORDTAG O professional
8 WORDTAG I-MISC EUROPEAN
1 WORDTAG I-MISC WINNERS
5 WORDTAG I-LOC TIRANA
55 WORDTAG I-MISC European
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Winners
14 WORDTAG O qualifying
75 WORDTAG O soccer
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tirana
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Flamurtari
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vlore
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chemlon
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Humenne
29 WORDTAG O 0-0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lubarskij
2 WORDTAG O 50th
67 WORDTAG O minute
1 WORDTAG I-PER Valkucak
8 WORDTAG O 54th
10 WORDTAG O 5,000
105 WORDTAG O win
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bistrita
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Valletta
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chorzow
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ruch
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chorzow
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Llansantffraid
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Wales
46 WORDTAG O 1-0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arkadiusz
2 WORDTAG I-PER Bak
3 WORDTAG O 1st
2 WORDTAG O 55th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arwel
7 WORDTAG O 47th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Miroslav
1 WORDTAG O 62nd
4 WORDTAG O 63rd
2 WORDTAG O 6,500
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Larnaca
3 WORDTAG I-ORG AEK
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Larnaca
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Cyprus
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kotaik
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Abovyan
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Armenia
31 WORDTAG O 2-0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zoran
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kundic
4 WORDTAG O 28th
2 WORDTAG I-PER Klimis
2 WORDTAG I-PER Alexandrou
2 WORDTAG O 41st
1 WORDTAG I-PER Milenko
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kovasevic
5 WORDTAG O 60th
24 WORDTAG O penalty
1 WORDTAG I-PER Koprinovic
3 WORDTAG O 82nd
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pavlos
1 WORDTAG I-PER Markou
6 WORDTAG O 5-1
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Siauliai
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kareda
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Siauliai
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Lithuania
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sion
1 WORDTAG O agrregate
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Vinnytsya
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Nyva
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Vinnytsya
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Tallinna
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sadam
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Estonia
10 WORDTAG O 3,000
6 WORDTAG O Aggregate
12 WORDTAG O score
13 WORDTAG O 2-2
57 WORDTAG O goals
27 WORDTAG O rule
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bergen
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Norway
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Shelbourne
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mons
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ivar
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mjelde
19 WORDTAG O 10th
10 WORDTAG I-PER Jan
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ove
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pedersen
1 WORDTAG O 72nd
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rutherford
4 WORDTAG O 5th
1 WORDTAG O 2,189
7 WORDTAG O 5-2
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Sofia
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Levski
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Sofia
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Bulgaria
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Olimpija
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovenia
3 WORDTAG O Scorer
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ilian
1 WORDTAG I-PER Simeonov
6 WORDTAG O 58th
9 WORDTAG O 25,000
8 WORDTAG O 4-3
5 WORDTAG O penalties
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vaduz
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Liechtenstein
2 WORDTAG I-ORG RAF
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Riga
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Latvia
1 WORDTAG I-PER Daniele
1 WORDTAG I-PER Polverino
7 WORDTAG O 90th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Agrins
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zarins
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Luxembourg
2 WORDTAG I-ORG US
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Luxembourg
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Varteks
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Varazdin
1 WORDTAG I-PER Drazen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Beser
1 WORDTAG I-PER Miljenko
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mumler
2 WORDTAG O 78th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jamir
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cvetko
3 WORDTAG O 87th
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Torshavn
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Havnar
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Boltfelag
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Faroe
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Islands
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dynamo
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Batumi
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Georgia
4 WORDTAG O 0-2
1 WORDTAG O 9-0
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Prague
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Sparta
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Prague
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Glentoran
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Northern
11 WORDTAG O 4-0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gunda
6 WORDTAG O 26th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lumir
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mistr
5 WORDTAG O 19th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Horst
1 WORDTAG I-PER Siegl
3 WORDTAG O 48th
6 WORDTAG O 80th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zdenek
1 WORDTAG I-PER Svoboda
3 WORDTAG O 76th
4 WORDTAG I-PER Gabriel
6 WORDTAG O 86th
1 WORDTAG O 10-1
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Edinburgh
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hearts
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Star
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Belgrade
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Yugoslavia
4 WORDTAG I-PER Dave
1 WORDTAG I-PER McPherson
4 WORDTAG O 44th
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Vinko
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Marinovic
5 WORDTAG O 59th
1 WORDTAG O 15,062
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rishon-Lezion
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Hapoel
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Ironi
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Constructorul
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Chisinau
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Moldova
1 WORDTAG O 3-3
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Anjalonkoski
1 WORDTAG I-ORG MyPa-47
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Karabach
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Agdam
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Azerbaijan
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mypa-47
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Skopje
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sloga
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Jugomagnat
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Macedonia
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Kispest
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Honved
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Hungary
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Add
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Rishon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Moshe
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sabag
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nissan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kapeta
4 WORDTAG I-PER Tomas
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cibola
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Constructorol
4 WORDTAG I-PER Sergei
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rogachev
4 WORDTAG O 42nd
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gennadi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Skidan
6 WORDTAG O 1,500
1 WORDTAG I-LOC GOTHENBURG
4 WORDTAG O PUT
1 WORDTAG I-ORG FERENCVAROS
10 WORDTAG O OUT
3 WORDTAG I-MISC EURO
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BUDAPEST
2 WORDTAG I-ORG IFK
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Gothenburg
18 WORDTAG O drew
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Ferencvaros
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Champions
25 WORDTAG O tie
128 WORDTAG O played
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Gothenburg
12 WORDTAG O 4-1
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ferenc
2 WORDTAG I-PER Horvath
7 WORDTAG O 15th
5 WORDTAG I-PER Andreas
4 WORDTAG I-PER Andersson
4 WORDTAG O 9,000
2 WORDTAG I-MISC BRAZILIAN
8 WORDTAG O CHAMPIONSHIP
3 WORDTAG I-LOC RIO
3 WORDTAG I-LOC DE
3 WORDTAG I-LOC JANEIRO
3 WORDTAG O midweek
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Brazilian
47 WORDTAG O championship
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Bahia
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Atletico
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Paranaense
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Corinthians
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Guarani
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Coritiba
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Mineiro
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Cruzeiro
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Vitoria
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Flamengo
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventude
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Goias
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Sport
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Recife
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Gremio
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Bragantino
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Palmeiras
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Vasco
3 WORDTAG I-ORG da
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Gama
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Portuguesa
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Parana
1 WORDTAG I-PER NEWCOMBE
1 WORDTAG O PONDERS
1 WORDTAG O HIS
1 WORDTAG I-MISC DAVIS
2 WORDTAG O FUTURE
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SYDNEY
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Davis
29 WORDTAG O captain
7 WORDTAG I-PER Newcombe
3 WORDTAG O signalled
17 WORDTAG O resignation
3 WORDTAG O loses
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Wimbledon
68 WORDTAG O champion
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Davis
31 WORDTAG O coach
11 WORDTAG I-PER Tony
2 WORDTAG I-PER Roche
9 WORDTAG O determined
6 WORDTAG O events
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Split
9 WORDTAG O lose
14 WORDTAG O look
15 WORDTAG O giving
9 WORDTAG O someone
7 WORDTAG O else
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Sydney
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Telegraph
100 WORDTAG O world
1 WORDTAG O clay
1 WORDTAG O 20-22
11 WORDTAG O Under
12 WORDTAG O leadership
4 WORDTAG O relegated
2 WORDTAG O elite
1 WORDTAG O 26-time
12 WORDTAG O winners
8 WORDTAG O slipped
1 WORDTAG O rank
5 WORDTAG O Since
1 WORDTAG I-PER Neale
3 WORDTAG I-PER Fraser
1 WORDTAG O tandem
9 WORDTAG O doubles
9 WORDTAG O partner
13 WORDTAG O wins
16 WORDTAG O losses
5 WORDTAG O selected
5 WORDTAG O semifinalist
41 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympic
4 WORDTAG I-PER Woodforde
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Croatians
1 WORDTAG O boasts
4 WORDTAG O conceded
1 WORDTAG O hard-pressed
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Croatian
1 WORDTAG O breath
2 WORDTAG O absolute
37 WORDTAG O best
15 WORDTAG O described
3 WORDTAG O toughest
7 WORDTAG O faced
6 WORDTAG O 1986
10 WORDTAG O beaten
2 WORDTAG O finalists
59 WORDTAG O ago
3 WORDTAG O guidance
4 WORDTAG O BADMINTON
3 WORDTAG I-MISC MALAYSIAN
4 WORDTAG I-LOC KUALA
4 WORDTAG I-LOC LUMPUR
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Malaysian
3 WORDTAG O badminton
56 WORDTAG O Men
59 WORDTAG O singles
5 WORDTAG O 9/16
2 WORDTAG I-PER Luo
2 WORDTAG I-PER Yigang
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hwang
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sun-ho
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Korea
3 WORDTAG O 15-3
6 WORDTAG O 15-7
3 WORDTAG I-PER Wong
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malaysia
6 WORDTAG I-PER Abdul
1 WORDTAG I-PER Samad
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ismail
1 WORDTAG O 16-18
4 WORDTAG O 15-2
4 WORDTAG O 17-14
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kantharoopan
5 WORDTAG O 3/4
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jeroen
17 WORDTAG I-PER Van
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dijk
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Netherlands
11 WORDTAG O 15-11
1 WORDTAG O 18-14
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wijaya
3 WORDTAG I-PER Indra
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Indonesia
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pang
4 WORDTAG I-PER Chen
12 WORDTAG O 15-6
1 WORDTAG O 6-15
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hu
2 WORDTAG I-PER Zhilan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nunung
1 WORDTAG I-PER Subandoro
1 WORDTAG O 5-15
1 WORDTAG O 18-15
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hermawan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Susanto
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fung
1 WORDTAG I-PER Permadi
8 WORDTAG O 15-8
13 WORDTAG O 15-12
54 WORDTAG O Women
4 WORDTAG O 2nd
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cindana
2 WORDTAG O 11-3
1 WORDTAG I-PER 1ama
1 WORDTAG I-PER Margit
1 WORDTAG I-PER Borg
5 WORDTAG O 11-6
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sun
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jian
3 WORDTAG I-PER Marina
1 WORDTAG I-PER Andrievskaqya
4 WORDTAG O 11-8
3 WORDTAG O 11-2
1 WORDTAG I-PER Meluawati
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chia
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fong
2 WORDTAG O 11-1
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gong
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zhichao
3 WORDTAG I-PER Liu
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lufung
2 WORDTAG O 6-11
3 WORDTAG O 11-7
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zeng
1 WORDTAG I-PER Yaqiong
2 WORDTAG I-PER Li
1 WORDTAG I-PER Feng
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Zealand
1 WORDTAG O 11-9
2 WORDTAG I-PER Christine
1 WORDTAG I-PER Magnusson
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ishwari
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boopathy
1 WORDTAG O 10-12
2 WORDTAG I-PER Zhang
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ning
1 WORDTAG I-PER Olivia
1 WORDTAG O REVISED
1 WORDTAG O MEN
26 WORDTAG O 'S
6 WORDTAG O DRAW
38 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.
73 WORDTAG I-LOC NEW
3 WORDTAG O Revised
38 WORDTAG O draw
15 WORDTAG O championships
15 WORDTAG O beginning
6 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S
7 WORDTAG I-LOC National
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Tennis
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Centre
1 WORDTAG O Draw
8 WORDTAG I-PER Pete
16 WORDTAG I-PER Sampras
64 WORDTAG O vs.
11 WORDTAG I-PER Adrian
4 WORDTAG I-PER Voinea
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magnus
3 WORDTAG I-PER Larsson
2 WORDTAG I-PER Volkov
44 WORDTAG O vs
9 WORDTAG O Qualifier
12 WORDTAG I-PER Andrei
2 WORDTAG I-PER Olhovskiy
6 WORDTAG I-PER Roberto
2 WORDTAG I-PER Carretero
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jordi
2 WORDTAG I-PER Burillo
7 WORDTAG O ------------------------
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jonas
2 WORDTAG I-PER Bjorkman
8 WORDTAG I-PER Christian
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rudd
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rikl
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sjeng
2 WORDTAG I-PER Schalken
2 WORDTAG I-PER Schaller
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grant
2 WORDTAG I-PER Stafford
4 WORDTAG I-PER Guy
2 WORDTAG I-PER Forget
8 WORDTAG I-PER Fernando
2 WORDTAG I-PER Meligeni
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Brazil
4 WORDTAG I-PER Yevgeny
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kafelnikov
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chesnokov
2 WORDTAG I-PER Draper
2 WORDTAG I-PER Galo
2 WORDTAG I-PER Blanco
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johansson
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hendrik
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dreekman
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rusedski
20 WORDTAG I-PER Medvedev
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jean-Philippe
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fleurian
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kroslak
102 WORDTAG O 14
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costa
1 WORDTAG I-PER Younnes
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shuzo
2 WORDTAG I-PER Matsuoka
3 WORDTAG I-PER Doug
2 WORDTAG I-PER Flach
4 WORDTAG I-PER Mats
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wilander
2 WORDTAG I-PER Haarhuis
2 WORDTAG I-PER Tebbutt
11 WORDTAG I-PER Jonathan
3 WORDTAG I-PER Stark
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bernd
2 WORDTAG I-PER Karbacher
9 WORDTAG I-PER Stefan
8 WORDTAG I-PER Edberg
21 WORDTAG I-PER Richard
5 WORDTAG I-PER Krajicek
11 WORDTAG I-PER Andre
9 WORDTAG I-PER Agassi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mauricio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hadad
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombia
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marcos
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ondruska
3 WORDTAG I-PER Felix
3 WORDTAG I-PER Mantilla
16 WORDTAG I-PER Carlos
3 WORDTAG I-PER Moya
2 WORDTAG I-PER Humphries
3 WORDTAG I-PER Siemerink
2 WORDTAG I-PER Carl-Uwe
2 WORDTAG I-PER Steeb
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wheaton
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kevin
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kim
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nicolas
3 WORDTAG I-PER Lapentti
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Ecuador
4 WORDTAG I-PER Karim
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alami
9 WORDTAG I-PER Enqvist
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
2 WORDTAG I-PER Simian
3 WORDTAG I-PER Guillaume
3 WORDTAG I-PER Raoux
2 WORDTAG I-PER Filip
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dewulf
71 WORDTAG I-LOC Belgium
3 WORDTAG I-PER Knowles
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Bahamas
2 WORDTAG I-PER Filippini
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Uruguay
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kris
3 WORDTAG I-PER Goossens
17 WORDTAG I-PER Stich
3 WORDTAG I-PER Chuck
5 WORDTAG I-PER Adams
8 WORDTAG I-PER Javier
3 WORDTAG I-PER Frana
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Argentina
3 WORDTAG I-PER Courier
3 WORDTAG I-PER Grabb
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sandon
2 WORDTAG I-PER Stolle
5 WORDTAG I-PER Stefano
2 WORDTAG I-PER Pescosolido
3 WORDTAG I-PER Arnaud
3 WORDTAG I-PER Boetsch
2 WORDTAG I-PER Pereira
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Venezuela
4 WORDTAG I-PER Gustafsson
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jeff
4 WORDTAG I-PER Tarango
3 WORDTAG I-PER Radulescu
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jared
4 WORDTAG I-PER Palmer
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hernan
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gumy
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nicklas
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kulti
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jakob
3 WORDTAG I-PER Hlasek
2 WORDTAG I-PER Cecil
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mamiit
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vince
1 WORDTAG I-PER Spadea
2 WORDTAG I-PER Prinosil
2 WORDTAG I-PER Carbonell
33 WORDTAG O BASEBALL
4 WORDTAG I-ORG ORIOLES
1 WORDTAG I-PER DAVEY
3 WORDTAG I-PER JOHNSON
1 WORDTAG O HOSPITALIZED
11 WORDTAG I-LOC BALTIMORE
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Baltimore
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Orioles
2 WORDTAG I-PER Davey
22 WORDTAG I-PER Johnson
8 WORDTAG O miss
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Seattle
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Mariners
31 WORDTAG O hospital
3 WORDTAG O irregular
2 WORDTAG O heartbeat
1 WORDTAG O 53-year-old
2 WORDTAG O hospitalized
1 WORDTAG O experiencing
1 WORDTAG O dizziness
8 WORDTAG O treated
4 WORDTAG O observed
1 WORDTAG O physician
4 WORDTAG O Dr.
16 WORDTAG I-PER William
1 WORDTAG I-PER Goldiner
17 WORDTAG O adding
36 WORDTAG O released
1 WORDTAG O bench
8 WORDTAG I-PER Andy
2 WORDTAG I-PER Etchebarren
8 WORDTAG O manage
8 WORDTAG O absence
12 WORDTAG I-ORG California
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Angels
2 WORDTAG O skipper
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Columbia
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Presbyterian
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Hospital
13 WORDTAG O blood
3 WORDTAG O clot
2 WORDTAG O calf
59 WORDTAG O eight
5 WORDTAG O seasons
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Baltimore
1 WORDTAG O off-season
3 WORDTAG O replacing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Regan
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Cincinnati
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Reds
20 WORDTAG I-MISC National
49 WORDTAG I-MISC League
3 WORDTAG O guided
33 WORDTAG I-ORG York
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Mets
106 WORDTAG O games
7 WORDTAG O pull
27 WORDTAG O within
2 WORDTAG O slumping
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yankees
55 WORDTAG I-MISC American
5 WORDTAG I-MISC East
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Division
16 WORDTAG I-MISC MAJOR
41 WORDTAG I-MISC LEAGUE
40 WORDTAG O STANDINGS
7 WORDTAG O WEDNESDAY
14 WORDTAG O GAMES
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Baseball
32 WORDTAG O standings
32 WORDTAG O tabulate
102 WORDTAG O lost
38 WORDTAG O winning
25 WORDTAG O percentage
8 WORDTAG I-MISC AMERICAN
16 WORDTAG I-MISC EASTERN
48 WORDTAG I-MISC DIVISION
23 WORDTAG O W
27 WORDTAG O L
20 WORDTAG O GB
30 WORDTAG I-ORG NEW
30 WORDTAG I-ORG YORK
1 WORDTAG O .576
17 WORDTAG I-ORG BALTIMORE
25 WORDTAG O 58
3 WORDTAG O .536
16 WORDTAG I-ORG BOSTON
59 WORDTAG O 64
9 WORDTAG O .496
15 WORDTAG I-ORG TORONTO
5 WORDTAG O .457
16 WORDTAG I-ORG DETROIT
13 WORDTAG O 82
1 WORDTAG O .349
47 WORDTAG O 28
16 WORDTAG I-MISC CENTRAL
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CLEVELAND
4 WORDTAG O .598
30 WORDTAG I-ORG CHICAGO
2 WORDTAG O .539
17 WORDTAG I-ORG MINNESOTA
14 WORDTAG O .500
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MILWAUKEE
57 WORDTAG O 60
5 WORDTAG O .469
16 WORDTAG I-ORG KANSAS
17 WORDTAG I-ORG CITY
1 WORDTAG O .453
44 WORDTAG O 18
16 WORDTAG I-MISC WESTERN
15 WORDTAG I-ORG TEXAS
2 WORDTAG O .575
16 WORDTAG I-ORG SEATTLE
29 WORDTAG O 61
4 WORDTAG O .512
15 WORDTAG I-ORG OAKLAND
38 WORDTAG O 62
2 WORDTAG O .481
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CALIFORNIA
1 WORDTAG O .460
7 WORDTAG O THURSDAY
22 WORDTAG O AUGUST
16 WORDTAG O SCHEDULE
8 WORDTAG I-LOC BOSTON
7 WORDTAG I-LOC KANSAS
15 WORDTAG I-LOC CITY
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MINNESOTA
8 WORDTAG I-MISC NATIONAL
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ATLANTA
23 WORDTAG O 46
1 WORDTAG O .632
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MONTREAL
4 WORDTAG O .461
14 WORDTAG I-ORG FLORIDA
15 WORDTAG I-ORG PHILADELPHIA
1 WORDTAG O .409
15 WORDTAG I-ORG HOUSTON
3 WORDTAG O .535
17 WORDTAG I-ORG ST
15 WORDTAG I-ORG LOUIS
2 WORDTAG O .532
6 WORDTAG O .504
16 WORDTAG I-ORG CINCINNATI
14 WORDTAG I-ORG PITTSBURGH
1 WORDTAG O .421
29 WORDTAG I-ORG SAN
14 WORDTAG I-ORG DIEGO
6 WORDTAG O .543
17 WORDTAG I-ORG LOS
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ANGELES
1 WORDTAG O .524
15 WORDTAG I-ORG COLORADO
44 WORDTAG O 65
15 WORDTAG I-ORG FRANCISCO
3 WORDTAG O .435
8 WORDTAG I-LOC COLORADO
7 WORDTAG I-LOC ATLANTA
8 WORDTAG I-LOC HOUSTON
5 WORDTAG I-LOC LOS
5 WORDTAG I-LOC ANGELES
21 WORDTAG I-LOC SAN
9 WORDTAG I-LOC FRANCISCO
7 WORDTAG O Baseball
8 WORDTAG O CAPS
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Chicago
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Milwaukee
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Oakland
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Texas
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Toronto
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Florida
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Pittsburgh
52 WORDTAG I-ORG St
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Louis
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Philadelphia
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Montreal
1 WORDTAG I-PER GREER
1 WORDTAG O HOMER
1 WORDTAG O 10TH
1 WORDTAG O LIFTS
2 WORDTAG O PAST
1 WORDTAG I-ORG INDIANS
5 WORDTAG I-LOC CLEVELAND
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rusty
4 WORDTAG I-PER Greer
9 WORDTAG O two-run
26 WORDTAG O homer
26 WORDTAG O inning
8 WORDTAG O rallied
2 WORDTAG O 10-8
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cleveland
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Indians
5 WORDTAG O rubber
9 WORDTAG O three-game
31 WORDTAG O series
17 WORDTAG O With
10 WORDTAG O pitch
4 WORDTAG I-PER Julian
3 WORDTAG I-PER Tavarez
1 WORDTAG O 4-7
4 WORDTAG O right-field
4 WORDTAG O fence
1 WORDTAG O off-speed
26 WORDTAG O tried
3 WORDTAG O swing
24 WORDTAG O big
13 WORDTAG O crowd
2 WORDTAG O intense
33 WORDTAG O shot
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ivan
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rodriguez
20 WORDTAG O double
2 WORDTAG O catcher
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mickey
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cochrane
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johnny
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bench
7 WORDTAG I-PER Terry
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kennedy
1 WORDTAG O catchers
39 WORDTAG O 40
39 WORDTAG O nine
9 WORDTAG O meetings
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Western
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Jacobs
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Field
3 WORDTAG O joining
19 WORDTAG O teams
2 WORDTAG I-MISC A.L.
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Central
10 WORDTAG O extra
22 WORDTAG O ninth
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lofton
23 WORDTAG O single
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vosberg
4 WORDTAG O blew
5 WORDTAG O save
29 WORDTAG O got
19 WORDTAG O allowing
40 WORDTAG O hits
5 WORDTAG O walks
7 WORDTAG O strikeouts
2 WORDTAG O 2/3
5 WORDTAG O scoreless
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dean
6 WORDTAG O 30th
4 WORDTAG I-PER Cal
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ripken
2 WORDTAG O fifth-inning
7 WORDTAG O solo
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bobby
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bonilla
10 WORDTAG O three-run
16 WORDTAG O seventh
43 WORDTAG O power
3 WORDTAG O surging
1 WORDTAG O 10-5
58 WORDTAG O runs
31 WORDTAG O fifth
2 WORDTAG O 5-5
11 WORDTAG O bottom
4 WORDTAG O 21st
6 WORDTAG O starter
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sterling
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hitchcock
1 WORDTAG O 12-6
8 WORDTAG O blast
2 WORDTAG I-PER Randy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cy
4 WORDTAG I-PER Young
49 WORDTAG O allowed
10 WORDTAG O relief
3 WORDTAG O appearances
2 WORDTAG O disabled
13 WORDTAG I-MISC RBI
35 WORDTAG O cut
1 WORDTAG I-PER Erickson
1 WORDTAG O 8-10
1 WORDTAG O laboured
27 WORDTAG O straight
8 WORDTAG O homers
20 WORDTAG O dropped
10 WORDTAG O row
8 WORDTAG O became
2 WORDTAG O shortstop
8 WORDTAG O major-league
12 WORDTAG O history
21 WORDTAG O 34
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hoiles
3 WORDTAG O 22nd
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dickson
10 WORDTAG O scattered
3 WORDTAG O 1/3
12 WORDTAG O debut
3 WORDTAG I-PER Chili
3 WORDTAG O belted
29 WORDTAG O each
2 WORDTAG O plate
8 WORDTAG I-PER Derek
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jeter
7 WORDTAG O settled
3 WORDTAG O 27th
2 WORDTAG O pitcher
4 WORDTAG O tying
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jimmy
2 WORDTAG I-PER Key
1 WORDTAG O 9-10
1 WORDTAG O baserunners
14 WORDTAG O interim
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Boston
15 WORDTAG I-PER Mike
2 WORDTAG I-PER Stanley
4 WORDTAG O bases-loaded
3 WORDTAG O eighth-inning
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Sox
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Athletics
10 WORDTAG O owns
1 WORDTAG O .367
19 WORDTAG O career
4 WORDTAG O batting
5 WORDTAG O bases
6 WORDTAG O loaded
1 WORDTAG O 33-for-90
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mo
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vaughn
43 WORDTAG O went
1 WORDTAG O 3-for-3
14 WORDTAG O walk
5 WORDTAG O stole
2 WORDTAG O collected
1 WORDTAG O 116th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Brosius
9 WORDTAG O homered
17 WORDTAG O drove
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Detroit
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ausmus
9 WORDTAG O capped
2 WORDTAG O four-run
15 WORDTAG O eighth
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Tigers
3 WORDTAG O reeling
9 WORDTAG I-ORG White
11 WORDTAG O consecutive
2 WORDTAG O dropping
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kansas
19 WORDTAG I-LOC City
16 WORDTAG I-PER Juan
5 WORDTAG I-PER Guzman
2 WORDTAG O tossed
1 WORDTAG O complete-game
2 WORDTAG O six-hitter
1 WORDTAG O league-best
2 WORDTAG I-MISC ERA
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Blue
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Jays
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Royals
5 WORDTAG O span
9 WORDTAG O earned
3 WORDTAG O lowered
1 WORDTAG O 2.99
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Minnesota
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jaha
5 WORDTAG O five-run
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Brewers
2 WORDTAG O 10-7
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Twins
20 WORDTAG I-PER Jose
2 WORDTAG I-PER Valentin
1 WORDTAG I-PER COCU
2 WORDTAG O DOUBLE
1 WORDTAG O EARNS
28 WORDTAG I-ORG PSV
17 WORDTAG O WIN
5 WORDTAG I-PER Cocu
1 WORDTAG O spur
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Eindhoven
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NEC
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nijmegen
1 WORDTAG O bicycle
7 WORDTAG O kick
75 WORDTAG O minutes
3 WORDTAG I-PER Arthur
2 WORDTAG I-PER Numan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Luc
5 WORDTAG I-PER Nilis
4 WORDTAG O scorer
1 WORDTAG O marksmen
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Ajax
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Amsterdam
21 WORDTAG O defence
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NAC
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Breda
14 WORDTAG I-MISC DUTCH
46 WORDTAG O DIVISION
9 WORDTAG O SUMMARY
1 WORDTAG O Van
1 WORDTAG O Eykeren
1 WORDTAG O Numan
13 WORDTAG O 11th
2 WORDTAG O 67th
26 WORDTAG O Halftime
5 WORDTAG O 1-2
15 WORDTAG O RESULT
1 WORDTAG O SHARPSHOOTER
1 WORDTAG I-PER KNUP
3 WORDTAG I-MISC SWISS
7 WORDTAG I-LOC GENEVA
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Galatasaray
4 WORDTAG I-PER Knup
46 WORDTAG O 26
3 WORDTAG O internationals
5 WORDTAG O recalled
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Baku
3 WORDTAG O overlooked
2 WORDTAG I-PER Artur
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jorge
6 WORDTAG O finals
4 WORDTAG I-PER Rolf
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fringer
10 WORDTAG O clearly
1 WORDTAG O 19-man
12 WORDTAG O progress
6 WORDTAG O beyond
6 WORDTAG O phase
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Euro
6 WORDTAG I-MISC 96
7 WORDTAG O Squad
4 WORDTAG O Goalkeepers
8 WORDTAG I-PER Marco
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pascolo
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Cagliari
2 WORDTAG I-PER Pascal
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zuberbuehler
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Grasshoppers
4 WORDTAG O Defenders
1 WORDTAG I-PER Henchoz
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hottiger
1 WORDTAG I-PER Yvan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Quentin
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ramon
3 WORDTAG I-PER Vega
4 WORDTAG I-PER Raphael
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wicky
4 WORDTAG O Midfielders
3 WORDTAG I-PER Alexandre
1 WORDTAG I-PER Comisetti
8 WORDTAG I-PER Antonio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Esposito
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fournier
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Stuttgart
4 WORDTAG I-PER Christophe
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ohrel
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lausanne
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sylvestre
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sesa
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Servette
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ciriaco
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sforza
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Inter
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Milan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Murat
1 WORDTAG I-PER Yakin
2 WORDTAG O Strikers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kubilay
1 WORDTAG I-PER Turkyilmaz
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bonvin
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chapuisat
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Borussia
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Dortmund
12 WORDTAG O ATHLETICS
2 WORDTAG O IT
7 WORDTAG O RECORD
7 WORDTAG O 40,000
1 WORDTAG O BEERS
15 WORDTAG O THE
1 WORDTAG O HOUSE
1 WORDTAG O Spectators
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Brussels
14 WORDTAG O grand
7 WORDTAG O prix
1 WORDTAG O incentive
1 WORDTAG O cheer
6 WORDTAG O athletes
4 WORDTAG O performances
5 WORDTAG O glass
3 WORDTAG O beer
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Belgian
1 WORDTAG O brewery
28 WORDTAG O pay
3 WORDTAG O drinks
4 WORDTAG O goes
11 WORDTAG O organisers
3 WORDTAG O expensive
18 WORDTAG O rounds
11 WORDTAG O ever
48 WORDTAG O already
8 WORDTAG O records
13 WORDTAG O broken
48 WORDTAG O women
19 WORDTAG O 1,000
13 WORDTAG O ROUND
4 WORDTAG I-LOC STUTTGART
34 WORDTAG O Leading
7 WORDTAG O golf
5 WORDTAG I-PER Broadhurst
10 WORDTAG I-PER Raymond
22 WORDTAG I-PER Ian
7 WORDTAG I-PER Woosnam
2 WORDTAG I-PER Bernhard
2 WORDTAG I-PER Langer
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ronan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rafferty
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lanner
4 WORDTAG I-PER Riley
3 WORDTAG I-PER Eamonn
3 WORDTAG I-PER Darcy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Per
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nyman
2 WORDTAG I-PER Claydon
7 WORDTAG I-PER Roe
4 WORDTAG I-PER Retief
4 WORDTAG I-PER Goosen
9 WORDTAG I-PER Carl
3 WORDTAG I-PER Suneson
12 WORDTAG I-PER Stephen
3 WORDTAG I-PER Field
6 WORDTAG I-PER Lawrie
4 WORDTAG I-PER Pyman
10 WORDTAG I-PER Max
1 WORDTAG I-PER Anglert
3 WORDTAG I-PER Miles
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tunnicliff
2 WORDTAG I-PER Cevaer
3 WORDTAG I-PER Des
3 WORDTAG I-PER Smyth
5 WORDTAG I-PER Carter
10 WORDTAG I-PER Lee
3 WORDTAG I-PER Westwood
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chalmers
8 WORDTAG I-PER Miguel
9 WORDTAG I-PER Angel
3 WORDTAG I-PER Bjorn
3 WORDTAG I-PER Roca
3 WORDTAG I-PER Derrick
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cooper
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hawksworth
3 WORDTAG I-PER Padraig
3 WORDTAG I-PER Harrington
1 WORDTAG I-PER Welch
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gogele
2 WORDTAG I-PER McGinley
13 WORDTAG I-PER Gary
2 WORDTAG I-PER Orr
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jose-Maria
2 WORDTAG I-PER Canizares
4 WORDTAG I-PER Jonzon
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eales
16 WORDTAG I-PER Williams
10 WORDTAG I-PER Andrew
3 WORDTAG I-PER Coltart
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lomas
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rivero
29 WORDTAG I-PER Robert
3 WORDTAG I-PER Karlsson
6 WORDTAG I-PER Marcus
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wills
12 WORDTAG I-PER Pedro
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linhart
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jamie
1 WORDTAG I-PER Spence
2 WORDTAG I-PER Price
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pinero
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mouland
3 WORDTAG I-ORG UEFA
1 WORDTAG O REWARDS
2 WORDTAG O THREE
1 WORDTAG O COUNTRIES
1 WORDTAG O FAIR
2 WORDTAG O PLAY
3 WORDTAG O rewarded
10 WORDTAG O additional
2 WORDTAG O 1997-98
6 WORDTAG I-MISC UEFA
8 WORDTAG O headed
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Fair
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Play
5 WORDTAG O rankings
1 WORDTAG O 1995-96
2 WORDTAG O 8.62
2 WORDTAG O 8.61
2 WORDTAG O 8.57
4 WORDTAG O formula
13 WORDTAG O account
7 WORDTAG O factors
48 WORDTAG O including
7 WORDTAG O red
4 WORDTAG O yellow
1 WORDTAG O cards
4 WORDTAG O coaching
3 WORDTAG O spectators
2 WORDTAG O behaviour
2 WORDTAG O clubs
43 WORDTAG O national
7 WORDTAG O allocated
8 WORDTAG O places
65 WORDTAG O 4.
1 WORDTAG O 8.56
64 WORDTAG O 5.
1 WORDTAG O 8.54
64 WORDTAG O 6.
1 WORDTAG O 8.52
53 WORDTAG O 7.
1 WORDTAG O 8.45
50 WORDTAG O 8.
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Belarus
1 WORDTAG O 8.39
37 WORDTAG O 9.
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Iceland
1 WORDTAG O 8.35
33 WORDTAG O 10.
4 WORDTAG O 8.30
8 WORDTAG O 13.
2 WORDTAG O 8.29
6 WORDTAG O 15.
1 WORDTAG O 8.24
7 WORDTAG O 16.
2 WORDTAG O 8.22
4 WORDTAG O 18.
1 WORDTAG O 8.20
3 WORDTAG O 19.
1 WORDTAG O 8.18
3 WORDTAG O 20.
1 WORDTAG O 8.17
2 WORDTAG O 21.
2 WORDTAG O 8.15
2 WORDTAG O 23.
2 WORDTAG O 8.12
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Portugal
1 WORDTAG O 25.
1 WORDTAG O 8.10
3 WORDTAG O 26.
3 WORDTAG O 8.09
1 WORDTAG O 29.
1 WORDTAG O 8.07
1 WORDTAG O 30.
1 WORDTAG O 8.06
1 WORDTAG O 31.
2 WORDTAG O 8.05
1 WORDTAG O 32.
1 WORDTAG O 8.03
2 WORDTAG O 33.
3 WORDTAG O 8.02
1 WORDTAG O 35.
1 WORDTAG O 7.98
1 WORDTAG O 36.
1 WORDTAG O 7.95
2 WORDTAG O 37.
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Greece
2 WORDTAG O 7.89
1 WORDTAG O 39.
1 WORDTAG O 7.85
1 WORDTAG O 40.
1 WORDTAG O 7.83
1 WORDTAG O 41.
1 WORDTAG O 7.80
1 WORDTAG O 42.
1 WORDTAG O 7.77
1 WORDTAG O 43.
1 WORDTAG O 7.75
1 WORDTAG O 44.
1 WORDTAG O 7.73
1 WORDTAG O 45.
2 WORDTAG O 7.40
2 WORDTAG O POLICE
1 WORDTAG O COMMANDOS
1 WORDTAG O HAND
2 WORDTAG I-MISC AUSTRALIANS
12 WORDTAG O MATCH
14 WORDTAG I-LOC COLOMBO
4 WORDTAG O Armed
224 WORDTAG O police
3 WORDTAG O commandos
2 WORDTAG O patrolled
25 WORDTAG O ground
36 WORDTAG O tour
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Sri
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Lanka
5 WORDTAG O youth
13 WORDTAG O limited
35 WORDTAG O overs
11 WORDTAG O includes
71 WORDTAG I-LOC India
11 WORDTAG O promised
15 WORDTAG O presence
2 WORDTAG O sniffer
3 WORDTAG O dogs
2 WORDTAG O plainclothes
10 WORDTAG O policemen
2 WORDTAG O trouble-free
27 WORDTAG O making
2 WORDTAG O boycotting
3 WORDTAG O fixture
20 WORDTAG O ethnic
27 WORDTAG O violence
2 WORDTAG O warm-up
2 WORDTAG O 251
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ricky
4 WORDTAG I-PER Ponting
2 WORDTAG O 119
7 WORDTAG O balls
4 WORDTAG O sixes
5 WORDTAG O fours
4 WORDTAG O retiring
4 WORDTAG O replied
1 WORDTAG O 246
1 WORDTAG I-PER Geoff
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marsh
1 WORDTAG O impressed
1 WORDTAG O competitiveness
105 WORDTAG O made
2 WORDTAG O sweat
2 WORDTAG O ONE
2 WORDTAG I-MISC ROMANIAN
2 WORDTAG O DIES
1 WORDTAG O BUS
2 WORDTAG O CRASH
1 WORDTAG I-LOC BULGARIA
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SOFIA
26 WORDTAG O One
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Romanian
15 WORDTAG O others
30 WORDTAG O injured
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Romanian-registered
16 WORDTAG O bus
9 WORDTAG O collided
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Bulgarian
4 WORDTAG O buses
3 WORDTAG O o'clock
42 WORDTAG O morning
27 WORDTAG O road
11 WORDTAG O towns
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rousse
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Veliko
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tarnovo
31 WORDTAG O woman
12 WORDTAG I-PER Maria
18 WORDTAG O 35
13 WORDTAG O accident
3 WORDTAG O investigated
2 WORDTAG O 359-2-84561
4 WORDTAG I-ORG OFFICIAL
4 WORDTAG I-ORG JOURNAL
4 WORDTAG O CONTENTS
5 WORDTAG I-ORG OJ
2 WORDTAG O 211
30 WORDTAG O *
10 WORDTAG O Note
5 WORDTAG O contents
6 WORDTAG O displayed
4 WORDTAG O reverse
34 WORDTAG O order
5 WORDTAG O printed
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Journal
2 WORDTAG O Corrigendum
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Commission
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Regulation
4 WORDTAG I-ORG EC
1 WORDTAG O 1464/96
1 WORDTAG O relating
6 WORDTAG O invitation
19 WORDTAG O tender
1 WORDTAG O levies
7 WORDTAG O refunds
14 WORDTAG O white
4 WORDTAG O sugar
1 WORDTAG O OJ
3 WORDTAG O 187
1 WORDTAG O 26.7.1996
1 WORDTAG O 658/96
10 WORDTAG O certain
1 WORDTAG O granting
1 WORDTAG O compensatory
5 WORDTAG O payments
24 WORDTAG O system
5 WORDTAG O producers
4 WORDTAG O arable
1 WORDTAG O crops
4 WORDTAG O 91
1 WORDTAG O 12.4.1996
1 WORDTAG O 1663/96
2 WORDTAG O establishing
4 WORDTAG O standard
9 WORDTAG O values
2 WORDTAG O determining
4 WORDTAG O entry
1 WORDTAG O fruit
2 WORDTAG O vegetables
5 WORDTAG O END
4 WORDTAG O DOCUMENT
4 WORDTAG I-ORG In
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Home
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Health
21 WORDTAG O appeal
3 WORDTAG O payment
2 WORDTAG O denial
1 WORDTAG I-LOC MINNETONKA
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Minn
30 WORDTAG I-ORG U.S.
4 WORDTAG I-ORG District
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Court
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Minneapolis
43 WORDTAG O decision
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Care
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Financing
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Administration
2 WORDTAG I-ORG HCFA
5 WORDTAG O reimbursement
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Medicaid
1 WORDTAG O Administrator
2 WORDTAG O reversed
11 WORDTAG O previously
4 WORDTAG O favorable
7 WORDTAG O regarding
6 WORDTAG O related
16 WORDTAG O community
3 WORDTAG O liaison
7 WORDTAG O personnel
11 WORDTAG O continues
18 WORDTAG O believe
16 WORDTAG O majority
1 WORDTAG O coverable
17 WORDTAG O terms
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Medicare
8 WORDTAG O program
4 WORDTAG O administrator
4 WORDTAG O optimistic
2 WORDTAG O ultimate
9 WORDTAG O resolution
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gildea
5 WORDTAG O recorded
11 WORDTAG O reserve
9 WORDTAG O equal
8 WORDTAG O revenue
1 WORDTAG O Separately
15 WORDTAG O ruled
2 WORDTAG O favor
3 WORDTAG O expenses
1 WORDTAG O 81,000
3 WORDTAG O disputed
1 WORDTAG O distrct
50 WORDTAG O court
5 WORDTAG O dispute
6 WORDTAG O pleased
1 WORDTAG O recognize
12 WORDTAG O significant
6 WORDTAG O toward
3 WORDTAG O disputes
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsdesk
3 WORDTAG O 312-408-8787
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Oppenheimer
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Capital
3 WORDTAG O Oct.
5 WORDTAG O div
2 WORDTAG I-ORG LP
11 WORDTAG O distribution
57 WORDTAG O rate
7 WORDTAG O quarterly
1 WORDTAG O assuming
11 WORDTAG O improved
55 WORDTAG O ended
33 WORDTAG O declared
1 WORDTAG O 0.65
5 WORDTAG O partnership
22 WORDTAG O unit
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Best
9 WORDTAG O sees
1 WORDTAG I-LOC RICHMOND
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Va
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Products
38 WORDTAG I-ORG Co
5 WORDTAG O Chairman
5 WORDTAG O Chief
1 WORDTAG O Executive
4 WORDTAG O second-quarter
1 WORDTAG O 34.6
6 WORDTAG O retailer
16 WORDTAG O annual
25 WORDTAG O even
3 WORDTAG O bankruptcy
1 WORDTAG O consideration
8 WORDTAG O emerged
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Chapter
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 11
2 WORDTAG O 3-1/2
1 WORDTAG O Bankruptcy
20 WORDTAG O always
5 WORDTAG O particularly
71 WORDTAG O you
12 WORDTAG O something
1 WORDTAG O striving
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Richmond-based
1 WORDTAG O 95.7
1 WORDTAG O second-largest
8 WORDTAG O stores
23 WORDTAG O fall
9 WORDTAG O closing
1 WORDTAG O lease
1 WORDTAG O agreements
53 WORDTAG O plan
2 WORDTAG O operates
3 WORDTAG O 169
16 WORDTAG O states
19 WORDTAG O For
35 WORDTAG O 29
1 WORDTAG O 7.1
2 WORDTAG O 0.23
1 WORDTAG O 311.9
1 WORDTAG O Measles
3 WORDTAG O exposure
3 WORDTAG O bowel
103 WORDTAG O 1996-08-23
4 WORDTAG O measles
3 WORDTAG O pregnant
3 WORDTAG O babies
4 WORDTAG I-PER Crohn
1 WORDTAG O debilitating
2 WORDTAG O disorder
9 WORDTAG O researchers
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Swedish
11 WORDTAG O born
2 WORDTAG O mothers
19 WORDTAG O caught
6 WORDTAG O developed
14 WORDTAG O cases
2 WORDTAG O Dr
3 WORDTAG I-PER Wakefield
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Royal
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Free
1 WORDTAG I-LOC School
9 WORDTAG I-LOC of
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Medicine
3 WORDTAG O colleagues
1 WORDTAG O screened
9 WORDTAG O delivered
3 WORDTAG I-LOC University
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Uppsala
3 WORDTAG O 1940
5 WORDTAG O 1949
4 WORDTAG O Four
33 WORDTAG O children
10 WORDTAG O wrote
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lancet
16 WORDTAG O medical
4 WORDTAG O journal
2 WORDTAG O inflammation
6 WORDTAG O sometimes
5 WORDTAG O require
14 WORDTAG O surgery
2 WORDTAG O causes
1 WORDTAG O diarrhoea
1 WORDTAG O abdominal
7 WORDTAG O pain
7 WORDTAG O weight
20 WORDTAG O involved
9 WORDTAG O especially
4 WORDTAG O severe
1 WORDTAG O Exposure
2 WORDTAG O viruses
15 WORDTAG O often
10 WORDTAG O cause
4 WORDTAG O birth
1 WORDTAG O defects
7 WORDTAG O Most
2 WORDTAG O notably
1 WORDTAG O rubella
37 WORDTAG O high
1 WORDTAG O stillborn
5 WORDTAG O baby
10 WORDTAG O All
18 WORDTAG O key
3 WORDTAG I-ORG CBI
13 WORDTAG O industrial
9 WORDTAG O Following
17 WORDTAG O survey
3 WORDTAG O manufacturing
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Confederation
11 WORDTAG I-ORG British
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Industry
1 WORDTAG O MONTHLY
1 WORDTAG O TRENDS
1 WORDTAG O ENQUIRY
8 WORDTAG O AUG
2 WORDTAG O JULY
4 WORDTAG O JUNE
4 WORDTAG O MAY
13 WORDTAG O book
21 WORDTAG O stocks
17 WORDTAG O goods
2 WORDTAG O +17
1 WORDTAG O +19
1 WORDTAG O +25
9 WORDTAG O expectations
2 WORDTAG O +22
1 WORDTAG O +12
1 WORDTAG O +16
2 WORDTAG O +6
4 WORDTAG O +4
2 WORDTAG O replying
11 WORDTAG O above
7 WORDTAG O normal
11 WORDTAG O below
1 WORDTAG O 1,305
30 WORDTAG O companies
5 WORDTAG O representing
2 WORDTAG O industries
4 WORDTAG O accounting
1 WORDTAG O manufactured
12 WORDTAG O employees
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rosemary
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bennett
1 WORDTAG O 7715
1 WORDTAG O shipsales
1 WORDTAG O Secondhand
2 WORDTAG O tonnage
7 WORDTAG O brokers
2 WORDTAG O vessels
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Iron
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Gippsland
10 WORDTAG O built
9 WORDTAG O 1989
1 WORDTAG O 87,241
3 WORDTAG O dwt
5 WORDTAG O buyers
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sairyu
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Maru
5 WORDTAG I-MISC No
4 WORDTAG I-MISC :
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 2
2 WORDTAG O 1982
1 WORDTAG O 60,960
1 WORDTAG O 15.5
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Stainless
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Fighter
1 WORDTAG O 21,718
22 WORDTAG O Some
11 WORDTAG O subject
3 WORDTAG O inspection
2 WORDTAG O Garlic
5 WORDTAG O pills
7 WORDTAG O cholesterol
5 WORDTAG O finds
4 WORDTAG O studies
12 WORDTAG O show
1 WORDTAG O flawed
11 WORDTAG O doctors
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Oxford
13 WORDTAG I-ORG University
176 WORDTAG O people
7 WORDTAG O benefit
1 WORDTAG O significantly
6 WORDTAG O garlic
3 WORDTAG O tablets
4 WORDTAG O 115
27 WORDTAG O levels
5 WORDTAG O 900
1 WORDTAG O milligrams
2 WORDTAG O dried
1 WORDTAG O powder
2 WORDTAG O placebo
3 WORDTAG O differences
29 WORDTAG O groups
9 WORDTAG O receiving
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Royal
4 WORDTAG I-ORG College
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Physicians
3 WORDTAG O Those
1 WORDTAG O low-fat
3 WORDTAG O diet
1 WORDTAG O measured
1 WORDTAG O six-week
4 WORDTAG O findings
1 WORDTAG O accurate
8 WORDTAG O Several
13 WORDTAG O pressure
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Oxford
15 WORDTAG O either
3 WORDTAG O trials
1 WORDTAG O interpreted
1 WORDTAG O incorrectly
16 WORDTAG O special
1 WORDTAG O diets
1 WORDTAG O beforehand
1 WORDTAG O duration
2 WORDTAG O six-month
23 WORDTAG O trial
3 WORDTAG O funded
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Heart
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Foundation
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lichtwer
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Pharma
3 WORDTAG I-ORG GmbH
9 WORDTAG O makes
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Kwai
2 WORDTAG O brand
13 WORDTAG O address
16 WORDTAG O whole
6 WORDTAG O affect
1 WORDTAG O 7950
5 WORDTAG O gives
9 WORDTAG O aid
1 WORDTAG O volcano-hit
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Caribbean
14 WORDTAG O 39
17 WORDTAG O development
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Montserrat
40 WORDTAG O much
9 WORDTAG O population
11 WORDTAG O living
26 WORDTAG O south
7 WORDTAG O fled
3 WORDTAG O volcano
1 WORDTAG O Soufriere
1 WORDTAG O hills
27 WORDTAG O times
3 WORDTAG O 4,500
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Plymouth
3 WORDTAG O evacuated
41 WORDTAG O north
1 WORDTAG O shelters
4 WORDTAG O schools
1 WORDTAG O assistance
15 WORDTAG O provide
17 WORDTAG O track
16 WORDTAG O programme
2 WORDTAG O designated
39 WORDTAG O area
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Overseas
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Development
3 WORDTAG O 8.5
2 WORDTAG O dependent
2 WORDTAG O territories
7 WORDTAG O active
1 WORDTAG O Overseas
1 WORDTAG O Development
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lynda
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chalker
38 WORDTAG O recent
2 WORDTAG O census
9 WORDTAG O shown
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Montserratians
15 WORDTAG O remain
108 WORDTAG O she
3 WORDTAG O Tennis
1 WORDTAG O looms
25 WORDTAG I-PER Bill
3 WORDTAG I-PER Berkrot
7 WORDTAG O World
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Grand
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Slam
32 WORDTAG O seed
4 WORDTAG I-PER Steffi
16 WORDTAG I-PER Graf
5 WORDTAG O aiming
25 WORDTAG O able
3 WORDTAG O ease
40 WORDTAG O major
8 WORDTAG O begins
10 WORDTAG O opens
5 WORDTAG O crown
2 WORDTAG O top-ranked
3 WORDTAG I-PER Yayuk
6 WORDTAG I-PER Basuki
8 WORDTAG O ceremony
3 WORDTAG O revealed
59 WORDTAG O both
7 WORDTAG O holders
1 WORDTAG O Looming
2 WORDTAG O third-round
1 WORDTAG O nemesis
13 WORDTAG O rising
2 WORDTAG O avenged
22 WORDTAG O defeat
2 WORDTAG O 19-year-old
1 WORDTAG O hitter
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Wimbledon
1 WORDTAG O first-week
1 WORDTAG O fireworks
12 WORDTAG O While
3 WORDTAG O stunning
4 WORDTAG O upset
2 WORDTAG O sailing
1 WORDTAG O predictable
5 WORDTAG O semifinal
3 WORDTAG O showdown
10 WORDTAG O star
5 WORDTAG O tested
18 WORDTAG O probably
1 WORDTAG O 28th-ranked
3 WORDTAG I-PER Natasha
4 WORDTAG I-PER Zvereva
6 WORDTAG O repeat
1 WORDTAG O eighth-ranked
8 WORDTAG O landing
1 WORDTAG O Bumping
19 WORDTAG O sixth
7 WORDTAG O avoided
8 WORDTAG O possibility
10 WORDTAG O quarter-finals
2 WORDTAG O lock
1 WORDTAG O horns
1 WORDTAG O semis
1 WORDTAG O Surprise
5 WORDTAG O ranked
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Czech
8 WORDTAG I-PER Monica
12 WORDTAG I-PER Seles
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anne
6 WORDTAG I-PER Miller
10 WORDTAG O victim
1 WORDTAG O Second-ranked
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Austrian
23 WORDTAG O seeded
3 WORDTAG O luck
11 WORDTAG O faces
27 WORDTAG O playing
1 WORDTAG O survives
3 WORDTAG O fifth-seeded
1 WORDTAG O 12th-seeded
2 WORDTAG O Perhaps
33 WORDTAG O yet
6 WORDTAG O unfortunate
8 WORDTAG O first-round
1 WORDTAG O matchup
3 WORDTAG O pits
7 WORDTAG O popular
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Swede
4 WORDTAG O two-time
1 WORDTAG O farewell
2 WORDTAG O one-match
6 WORDTAG O affair
4 WORDTAG O exception
4 WORDTAG O looks
3 WORDTAG O comfortable
1 WORDTAG O likes
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Frenchman
2 WORDTAG O ailing
3 WORDTAG O nursing
2 WORDTAG O rib
21 WORDTAG O injury
2 WORDTAG O path
8 WORDTAG O runner-up
1 WORDTAG O fifth-ranked
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anke
12 WORDTAG I-PER Huber
6 WORDTAG I-PER Conchita
16 WORDTAG I-PER Martinez
3 WORDTAG O eighth-seeded
7 WORDTAG I-PER Lindsay
8 WORDTAG I-PER Davenport
15 WORDTAG O looking
9 WORDTAG O opponents
1 WORDTAG O encounter
1 WORDTAG O 18th-ranked
5 WORDTAG I-PER Amanda
8 WORDTAG I-PER Coetzer
22 WORDTAG O young
1 WORDTAG O talent
4 WORDTAG I-PER Martina
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hingis
4 WORDTAG O 16th
2 WORDTAG O probable
2 WORDTAG O quarter-final
10 WORDTAG O clash
1 WORDTAG O seventh-seeded
6 WORDTAG I-PER Jana
5 WORDTAG I-PER Novotna
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ruxandra
3 WORDTAG I-PER Dragomir
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Sydney
13 WORDTAG O 61-2
9 WORDTAG O 9373-1800
12 WORDTAG I-ORG RTRS
1 WORDTAG O Top-seeded
1 WORDTAG O 123rd-ranked
1 WORDTAG O lefthander
4 WORDTAG O rallies
1 WORDTAG O constantly
1 WORDTAG O attacking
1 WORDTAG O tactic
11 WORDTAG O worked
3 WORDTAG O second-round
1 WORDTAG O bye
17 WORDTAG O along
4 WORDTAG O seeds
1 WORDTAG O second-seeded
1 WORDTAG O 6-7(3-7
5 WORDTAG O unseeded
10 WORDTAG O Other
3 WORDTAG O advancing
1 WORDTAG O seeed
2 WORDTAG O Eighth
2 WORDTAG O eliminated
15 WORDTAG O hour
26 WORDTAG O 55
2 WORDTAG O saved
30 WORDTAG O point
1 WORDTAG O 5-6
3 WORDTAG O third-set
24 WORDTAG O break
6 WORDTAG O compatriot
6 WORDTAG O 13th
1 WORDTAG O fortunate
1 WORDTAG O 9-8
2 WORDTAG O marathon
9 WORDTAG O knew
4 WORDTAG O ranks
34 WORDTAG O service
2 WORDTAG O breaks
1 WORDTAG O lanky
4 WORDTAG O strokes
1 WORDTAG O joking
2 WORDTAG O chipping
1 WORDTAG O charging
8 WORDTAG O serving
1 WORDTAG O volleying
21 WORDTAG O really
3 WORDTAG O timing
2 WORDTAG O baseline
6 WORDTAG O chances
12 WORDTAG O every
31 WORDTAG O come
7 WORDTAG O Playing
1 WORDTAG O lights
9 WORDTAG O maybe
6 WORDTAG O difference
2 WORDTAG O 2-5
22 WORDTAG O deficit
2 WORDTAG O erratically
1 WORDTAG O 44th-ranked
7 WORDTAG O surprise
3 WORDTAG O famous
23 WORDTAG O 32
1 WORDTAG O aces
1 WORDTAG O outplayed
4 WORDTAG O 24-year-old
1 WORDTAG O sixth-ranked
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Indianapolis
5 WORDTAG O quick
1 WORDTAG O getaway
1 WORDTAG O Something
25 WORDTAG O arrived
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Toronto
13 WORDTAG O And
4 WORDTAG O feeling
28 WORDTAG O soon
1 WORDTAG O unfocused
1 WORDTAG O calm
1 WORDTAG O nervy
25 WORDTAG O 'm
9 WORDTAG O fought
1 WORDTAG O tiebreak
3 WORDTAG O serves
6 WORDTAG O hoped
14 WORDTAG O tight
3 WORDTAG O Then
1 WORDTAG O shanked
2 WORDTAG O forehand
1 WORDTAG O 5-all
13 WORDTAG O helped
6 WORDTAG O Soccer
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Korean
4 WORDTAG O pro-soccer
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SEOUL
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Anyang
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Chonnam
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Puchon
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Suwon
39 WORDTAG O Standings
51 WORDTAG O drawn
9 WORDTAG O D
6 WORDTAG O G
5 WORDTAG O F
4 WORDTAG O P
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chonan
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Pohang
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Pusan
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Ulsan
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Chonbuk
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Senegal
3 WORDTAG O cholera
6 WORDTAG O outbreak
9 WORDTAG O kills
2 WORDTAG I-LOC DAKAR
47 WORDTAG O central
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kaolack
1 WORDTAG O 291
3 WORDTAG O Doctor
1 WORDTAG I-PER Masserigne
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ndiaye
20 WORDTAG O staff
1 WORDTAG O overwhelmed
9 WORDTAG O People
1 WORDTAG O rushing
2 WORDTAG O symptoms
11 WORDTAG O appear
3 WORDTAG O deaths
8 WORDTAG O 160
51 WORDTAG O miles
9 WORDTAG O southeast
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Senegalese
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dakar
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Nigerian
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Liberia
3 WORDTAG I-ORG ECOMOG
2 WORDTAG I-LOC MONROVIA
3 WORDTAG O Major
16 WORDTAG O General
4 WORDTAG I-PER Sam
1 WORDTAG I-PER Victor
2 WORDTAG I-PER Malu
15 WORDTAG O commander
1 WORDTAG O peacekeeping
29 WORDTAG O latest
25 WORDTAG O civil
1 WORDTAG I-PER Inienger
18 WORDTAG O officers
3 WORDTAG O handover
9 WORDTAG O dozen
6 WORDTAG O accords
17 WORDTAG O difficult
2 WORDTAG O challenging
5 WORDTAG O painful
1 WORDTAG O Peacekeepers
2 WORDTAG O harassed
2 WORDTAG O assure
2 WORDTAG O sight
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Nations
8 WORDTAG O observers
9 WORDTAG O travelling
22 WORDTAG O western
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tubmanburg
2 WORDTAG O monitor
15 WORDTAG O delayed
15 WORDTAG O shooting
6 WORDTAG O highway
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anthony
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nyakyi
13 WORDTAG O finally
1 WORDTAG O escort
1 WORDTAG I-ORG ULIMO-J
11 WORDTAG O faction
2 WORDTAG O Faction
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Abuja
126 WORDTAG O Saturday
5 WORDTAG O breaking
1 WORDTAG O foresees
6 WORDTAG O disarmament
4 WORDTAG O 60,000
2 WORDTAG O combatants
16 WORDTAG O 10,000
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Economic
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Community
15 WORDTAG I-ORG West
3 WORDTAG I-ORG African
2 WORDTAG I-ORG States
1 WORDTAG O height
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Guinea
5 WORDTAG O prayer
2 WORDTAG I-LOC CONAKRY
7 WORDTAG I-MISC West
3 WORDTAG O broadcast
8 WORDTAG O repeatedly
22 WORDTAG O radio
22 WORDTAG O dead
1 WORDTAG O prosperity
3 WORDTAG O precise
10 WORDTAG O reason
31 WORDTAG O clear
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lansana
4 WORDTAG I-PER Conte
2 WORDTAG O vice-president
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Organisation
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Islamic
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Conference
2 WORDTAG O prepare
1 WORDTAG I-ORG OIC
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Koranic
4 WORDTAG O reading
3 WORDTAG O sessions
7 WORDTAG O prayers
3 WORDTAG O farming
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Badi-Tondon
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Conakry
40 WORDTAG O army
3 WORDTAG O survived
4 WORDTAG O revolt
1 WORDTAG O veiled
2 WORDTAG O topple
21 WORDTAG O ordered
5 WORDTAG O crackdown
3 WORDTAG O corruption
21 WORDTAG O seized
4 WORDTAG O 1984
31 WORDTAG O death
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Marxist
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sekou
4 WORDTAG I-PER Toure
17 WORDTAG O 1993
2 WORDTAG O answers
5 WORDTAG O bottle
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JOHANNESBURG
15 WORDTAG O boy
3 WORDTAG O writing
19 WORDTAG O girl
23 WORDTAG O whose
4 WORDTAG O washed
4 WORDTAG I-PER Nelson
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mandela
30 WORDTAG O old
28 WORDTAG O prison
2 WORDTAG I-PER Carlo
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hoffmann
1 WORDTAG O 11-year-old
1 WORDTAG O jailer
9 WORDTAG O son
4 WORDTAG O beach
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Robben
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Island
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Cape
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Town
8 WORDTAG O winter
1 WORDTAG O storms
25 WORDTAG O letter
5 WORDTAG O ordinary
1 WORDTAG O mail
18 WORDTAG O post
1 WORDTAG I-PER Danielle
3 WORDTAG I-PER Murray
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sandusky
7 WORDTAG O age
1 WORDTAG O penfriend
6 WORDTAG O reply
3 WORDTAG O whoever
1 WORDTAG O flung
4 WORDTAG O journey
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlantic
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Rottweiler
1 WORDTAG O toddler
1 WORDTAG O rottweiler
4 WORDTAG O dog
5 WORDTAG O belonging
4 WORDTAG O elderly
20 WORDTAG O couple
1 WORDTAG O savaged
1 WORDTAG O two-year-old
4 WORDTAG O grandson
3 WORDTAG I-PER Louis
1 WORDTAG I-PER Booy
12 WORDTAG O front
5 WORDTAG O garden
2 WORDTAG O grandparents
23 WORDTAG O house
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Vanderbijlpark
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Johannesburg
20 WORDTAG O His
3 WORDTAG O bloody
14 WORDTAG O body
1 WORDTAG O lying
5 WORDTAG O parents
4 WORDTAG O pick
5 WORDTAG O unclear
1 WORDTAG O Dogs
3 WORDTAG O fierce
14 WORDTAG O enough
2 WORDTAG O scare
1 WORDTAG O burglars
6 WORDTAG O becoming
2 WORDTAG O increasingly
1 WORDTAG O crime-infested
4 WORDTAG O INDICATORS
3 WORDTAG O updated
1 WORDTAG O indicators
2 WORDTAG O CPI
1 WORDTAG O +0.4m
6 WORDTAG O m
1 WORDTAG O 23.0yr
1 WORDTAG O +0.9;+23.6
1 WORDTAG O PPI
1 WORDTAG O +0.7
1 WORDTAG O m;+21.5yr
1 WORDTAG O +1.7;+22.0
2 WORDTAG O Industry
2 WORDTAG O 7.8
1 WORDTAG O m;-0.2yr
1 WORDTAG O +7.3;-3.6
6 WORDTAG O Current
3 WORDTAG O Jan-May
1 WORDTAG O 738
1 WORDTAG O 748
5 WORDTAG I-ORG NBH
2 WORDTAG O 934
1 WORDTAG O 774
2 WORDTAG I-ORG MIT
2 WORDTAG O Jan-June
1 WORDTAG O 1.45
18 WORDTAG O bln
1 WORDTAG O 1.24
3 WORDTAG O Gross
2 WORDTAG O 27,246.5
1 WORDTAG O 28,716.8
2 WORDTAG O 14,390.7
1 WORDTAG O 15,704.3
1 WORDTAG O Unemployment
1 WORDTAG O 10.8
4 WORDTAG O 10.6
2 WORDTAG O Budget
1 WORDTAG O HUF
1 WORDTAG O Jan-July
4 WORDTAG O 102
2 WORDTAG O 122
3 WORDTAG O T-bill
2 WORDTAG O yields
23 WORDTAG O %
1 WORDTAG O 1mo
1 WORDTAG O 22.95
1 WORDTAG O 3mo
1 WORDTAG O 23.02
1 WORDTAG O 6mo
1 WORDTAG O 23.53
1 WORDTAG O 1yr
1 WORDTAG O 24.40
10 WORDTAG O Government
